[
  {
    "id": "chapter1_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elev",
    "back": "student",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "eleven",
      "form2": "elever",
      "form3": "eleverna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lärare",
    "back": "teacher",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lärarelärarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ursäkta.",
    "back": "Excuse me"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kan du säga det en gång till?",
    "back": "Could you repeat that"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag har en fråga.",
    "back": "I have a question"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad betyder det?",
    "back": "What does that mean"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur säger man ... på svenska?",
    "back": "How do you say ... in Swedish"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad heter ... på svenska?",
    "back": "What is ... called in Swedish"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur uttalar man ... ?",
    "back": "How do you pronounce ... "
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag förstår inte.",
    "back": "I don't understand"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur stavar/skriver man ... ?",
    "back": "How do you spell/write ... "
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jaha! Nu förstår jag!",
    "back": "Ah! Now I understand"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Förstår du/ni?",
    "back": "Do you understand"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Har ni några frågor?",
    "back": "Do you have any questions"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Titta på sidan X i textboken/övningsboken.",
    "back": "Look at page X in the textbook/exercise book"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Läs texten på sidan X.",
    "back": "Read the text on page X"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Stäng boken.",
    "back": "Close the book"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Lyssna.",
    "back": "Listen"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Säg efter mig.",
    "back": "Repeat after me"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Skriv!",
    "back": "Write"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Arbeta i par.",
    "back": "Work in pairs"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Prata svenska!",
    "back": "Speak Swedish"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kombinera",
    "back": "combine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kombinerar",
      "form2": "kombinerade",
      "form3": "kombinerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "foto",
    "back": "photo",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotot",
      "form2": "foton",
      "form3": "fotona"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "och",
    "back": "and",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ord",
    "back": "word",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "orden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lampa",
    "back": "lamp",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lampan",
      "form2": "lampaor",
      "form3": "lampaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bok",
    "back": "book",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "boken",
      "form2": "böcker",
      "form3": "böckerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dator",
    "back": "computer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "datorn",
      "form2": "datorer",
      "form3": "datorerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "buss",
    "back": "bus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bussen",
      "form2": "bussar",
      "form3": "bussarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "te",
    "back": "tea",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "teet",
      "form2": "teer",
      "form3": "teerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mobil",
    "back": "cell phone / mobile phone",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mobilen",
      "form2": "mobiler",
      "form3": "mobilerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "penna",
    "back": "pen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pennan",
      "form2": "pennaor",
      "form3": "pennaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaffe",
    "back": "coffee",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lång",
    "back": "long",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vokal",
    "back": "vowel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vokalen",
      "form2": "vokaler",
      "form3": "vokalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "eller",
    "back": "or",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konsonant",
    "back": "consonant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konsonanten",
      "form2": "konsonanter",
      "form3": "konsonanterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "exempel",
    "back": "example",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "exemplet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "exemplen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "namn",
    "back": "name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "namnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "namnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "språk",
    "back": "language",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "språket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "språken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "land",
    "back": "country",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "landet",
      "form2": "länder",
      "form3": "länderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad heter du?",
    "back": "What is your name"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag heter",
    "back": "My name is"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jag",
    "back": "I",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "heta",
    "back": "be called",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "heter",
      "form2": "hette",
      "form3": "hetat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varifrån",
    "back": "from where",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma",
    "back": "come",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kommer",
      "form2": "kom",
      "form3": "kommit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "från",
    "back": "from",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Grekland",
    "back": "Greece",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad talar du för språk?",
    "back": "What languages do you speak"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vad ... för",
    "back": "what"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tala",
    "back": "speak",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "talar",
      "form2": "talade",
      "form3": "talat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grekiska",
    "back": "Greek",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "engelska",
    "back": "English",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fråga",
    "back": "ask",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frågar",
      "form2": "frågade",
      "form3": "frågat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varandra",
    "back": "each other",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "om",
    "back": "about",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "presentation",
    "back": "presentation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "presentationen",
      "form2": "presentationer",
      "form3": "presentationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hej!",
    "back": "Hi"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Turkiet",
    "back": "Turkey",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Spanien",
    "back": "Spain",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nej",
    "back": "no",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spanska",
    "back": "Spanish",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lite",
    "back": "some, a little",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Brasilien",
    "back": "Brazil",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jaha",
    "back": "I see",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "portugisiska",
    "back": "Portuguese",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "så klart",
    "back": "of course"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Du då?",
    "back": "How about you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Franska",
    "back": "French",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pyttelite",
    "back": "a tiny bit",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Turkiska",
    "back": "Turkish",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förstå",
    "back": "understand",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förstår",
      "form2": "förstod",
      "form3": "förstått"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vad bra",
    "back": "that's great"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Trevligt att träffas!",
    "back": "Nice to meet you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Tartu",
    "back": "Tartu",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "var",
    "back": "where",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ligga",
    "back": "lie / be situated",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ligger",
      "form2": "låg",
      "form3": "legat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "i",
    "back": "in",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Estland",
    "back": "Estonia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "okej",
    "back": "okay / OK",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Frankrike",
    "back": "France",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lyssna",
    "back": "listen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lyssnar",
      "form2": "lyssnade",
      "form3": "lyssnat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dialog",
    "back": "dialogue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dialogen",
      "form2": "dialoger",
      "form3": "dialogerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vilken",
    "back": "which",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "vilket",
        "vilka"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ha",
    "back": "have",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "har",
      "form2": "hade",
      "form3": "haft"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betoning",
    "back": "emphasis",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "betoningen",
      "form2": "betoningar",
      "form3": "betoningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ringa in",
    "back": "circle"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "igen",
    "back": "again",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uttala",
    "back": "pronounce",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "uttalaar",
      "form2": "uttalade",
      "form3": "uttalat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inte",
    "back": "not",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "markera",
    "back": "mark",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "markerar",
      "form2": "markerade",
      "form3": "markerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läsa",
    "back": "read",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läsaer",
      "form2": "läsate",
      "form3": "läsat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "öva",
    "back": "practice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "övar",
      "form2": "övade",
      "form3": "övat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "verb",
    "back": "verb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "verbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "verben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ordföljd",
    "back": "word order",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "subjekt",
    "back": "subject",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "subjektet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "subjekten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fokus",
    "back": "focus",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et",
        "–"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "position",
    "back": "position",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "positionen",
      "form2": "positioner",
      "form3": "positionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fundament",
    "back": "sentence initial position",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fundamentet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fundamenten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "påstående",
    "back": "statement",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "påståendet",
      "form2": "påståenden",
      "form3": "påståendena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "före",
    "back": "before",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "efter",
    "back": "after",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fråga",
    "back": "question",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frågan",
      "form2": "frågaor",
      "form3": "frågaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frågeord",
    "back": "question words",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frågeordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "frågeorden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ja- och nej-fråga",
    "back": "yes/no question",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ja- och nej-frågan",
      "form2": "ja- och nej-frågaor",
      "form3": "ja- och nej-frågaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Kanada",
    "back": "Canada",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grupp",
    "back": "group",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gruppen",
      "form2": "grupper",
      "form3": "grupperna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mingla",
    "back": "mingle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minglar",
      "form2": "minglade",
      "form3": "minglat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Iran",
    "back": "Iran",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "presentera",
    "back": "introduce",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "presenterar",
      "form2": "presenterade",
      "form3": "presenterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hon",
    "back": "she",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "han",
    "back": "he",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "den",
    "back": "it",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "det",
    "back": "it",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vi",
    "back": "we",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ni",
    "back": "you (plural)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "they",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "subjektspronomen",
    "back": "subject pronoun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pronomen",
    "back": "pronoun",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pronomenet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "pronomenen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jobba",
    "back": "work",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jobbar",
      "form2": "jobbade",
      "form3": "jobbat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "med",
    "back": "with",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vid",
    "back": "by",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rätt",
    "back": "correct / right",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bild",
    "back": "picture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilden",
      "form2": "bilder",
      "form3": "bilderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läkare",
    "back": "doctor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läkaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "läkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "polis",
    "back": "police officer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "polisen",
      "form2": "poliser",
      "form3": "poliserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "servitör",
    "back": "waiter / waitress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "servitören",
      "form2": "servitörer",
      "form3": "servitörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "advokat",
    "back": "lawyer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "advokaten",
      "form2": "advokater",
      "form3": "advokaterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ingenjör",
    "back": "engineer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ingenjören",
      "form2": "ingenjörer",
      "form3": "ingenjörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kock",
    "back": "chef",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kocken",
      "form2": "kockar",
      "form3": "kockarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tandläkare",
    "back": "dentist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tandläkaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tandläkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frisör",
    "back": "hairdresser",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frisören",
      "form2": "frisörer",
      "form3": "frisörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "webbdesigner",
    "back": "web designer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "webbdesignern",
      "form2": "webbdesigner",
      "form3": "webbdesignerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjuksköterska",
    "back": "nurse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjuksköterskan",
      "form2": "sjuksköterskaor",
      "form3": "sjuksköterskaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pensionär",
    "back": "retiree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pensionären",
      "form2": "pensionärer",
      "form3": "pensionärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "programmerare",
    "back": "programmer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "programmeraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "programmerarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kafé",
    "back": "café",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kaféet",
      "form2": "kaféer",
      "form3": "kaféerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Lycka till!",
    "back": "Good luck"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rekrytering",
    "back": "recruitment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rekryteringen",
      "form2": "rekryteringar",
      "form3": "rekryteringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad kul!",
    "back": "How fun"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "startup",
    "back": "startup",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plugga",
    "back": "study",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pluggar",
      "form2": "pluggade",
      "form3": "pluggat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "jobba extra",
    "back": "work part-time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mening",
    "back": "sentence",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "meningen",
      "form2": "meningar",
      "form3": "meningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "universitet",
    "back": "university",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "universitetet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "universiteten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gift",
    "back": "married",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "–",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sambo",
    "back": "live-in partner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sambon",
      "form2": "sambor",
      "form3": "samborna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "singel",
    "back": "single",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "partner",
    "back": "partner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "partnern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "partnerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barn",
    "back": "child",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "barnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "barnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "son",
    "back": "son",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sonen",
      "form2": "söner",
      "form3": "sönerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dotter",
    "back": "daughter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dottern",
      "form2": "döttrar",
      "form3": "döttrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pojkvän",
    "back": "boyfriend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pojkvännen",
      "form2": "pojkvänner",
      "form3": "pojkvännerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bo ihop",
    "back": "live together"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bo",
    "back": "live",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bor",
      "form2": "bodde",
      "form3": "bott"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ungefär",
    "back": "about / approximately",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gifta sig",
    "back": "get married",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gifta siger",
      "form2": "gifta sige",
      "form3": "gift"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skilja sig",
    "back": "get divorced",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skilja siger",
      "form2": "skilde",
      "form3": "skilt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "år",
    "back": "year",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "året",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "åren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "person",
    "back": "person",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "personen",
      "form2": "personer",
      "form3": "personerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "man",
    "back": "man / husband",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mannen",
      "form2": "män",
      "form3": "männen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvinna",
    "back": "woman",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvinnan",
      "form2": "kvinnaor",
      "form3": "kvinnaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fru",
    "back": "wife",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frun",
      "form2": "fruar",
      "form3": "fruarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pojke",
    "back": "boy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pojken",
      "form2": "pojkear",
      "form3": "pojkearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flicka",
    "back": "girl",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flickan",
      "form2": "flickaor",
      "form3": "flickaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "katt",
    "back": "cat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "katten",
      "form2": "katter",
      "form3": "katterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "översätta",
    "back": "translate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "översättaer",
      "form2": "översättasatte",
      "form3": "översättasatt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "alfabet",
    "back": "alphabet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "alfabetet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "alfabeten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "efternamn",
    "back": "last name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "efternamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "efternamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stava",
    "back": "spell",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stavar",
      "form2": "stavade",
      "form3": "stavat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter1_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter1",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bank",
    "back": "bank",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "banken",
      "form2": "banker",
      "form3": "bankerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tjena!",
    "back": "Hi"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur mår du?",
    "back": "How are you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "må",
    "back": "feel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mår",
      "form2": "mådde",
      "form3": "mått"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bra",
    "back": "fine, well",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bara bra",
    "back": "I'm fine, well"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tack",
    "back": "thank you",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur är läget?",
    "back": "How are things? / How's it going"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läge",
    "back": "situation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läget",
      "form2": "lägen",
      "form3": "lägena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det är lugnt.",
    "back": "Great. / Okay"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lugn",
    "back": "cool, calm",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Själv då?",
    "back": "How about you? / And you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "själv",
    "back": "self (myself, yourself, etc.)",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det är fint!",
    "back": "It's fine"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Allt bra med dig?",
    "back": "How are you? / How are things with you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ja, absolut!",
    "back": "Yes, definitely! / Of course"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Tja!",
    "back": "Hey! / Hi",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "= Tjena!"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur är det med dig?",
    "back": "How are you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "riktigt",
    "back": "really",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "faktiskt",
    "back": "actually",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jo, det är okej.",
    "back": "Well, it's okay"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det är mycket på jobbet.",
    "back": "There's a lot going on at work"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Nja, sådär.",
    "back": "Well, so-so"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "God morgon!",
    "back": "Good morning"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Nja, inget vidare.",
    "back": "Well, not great"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättetrött",
    "back": "really tired",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Oj då!",
    "back": "Oh"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dricka",
    "back": "drink",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "drickaer",
      "form2": "drack",
      "form3": "druckit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lite",
    "back": "a little, a bit",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaffe",
    "back": "coffee",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jobbig",
    "back": "tough",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoppas",
    "back": "hope",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag är förkyld.",
    "back": "I have a cold"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åh",
    "back": "oh",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Krya på dig!",
    "back": "Get well"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "intonation",
    "back": "intonation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "intonationen",
      "form2": "intonationer",
      "form3": "intonationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slut",
    "back": "end",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slutet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sluten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fras",
    "back": "phrase",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frasen",
      "form2": "fraser",
      "form3": "fraserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gå",
    "back": "go",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "går",
      "form2": "gick",
      "form3": "gått"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ton",
    "back": "pitch",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tonen",
      "form2": "toner",
      "form3": "tonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "upp",
    "back": "up",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ner",
    "back": "down",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "placera",
    "back": "place",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "placerar",
      "form2": "placerade",
      "form3": "placerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "här",
    "back": "here",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nedanför",
    "back": "below",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hälsa",
    "back": "greet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hälsar",
      "form2": "hälsade",
      "form3": "hälsat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "annan",
    "back": "another",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "annat",
        "andra"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "retur",
    "back": "return",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "returen",
      "form2": "returer",
      "form3": "returerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pepp",
    "back": "pep",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "peppet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "peppen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ta hand om dig!",
    "back": "Take care"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "längta (-r, -de, -t) efter",
    "back": "long for, yearn for",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i sommar",
    "back": "this summer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "intresserad av",
    "back": "interested in"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "deckare",
    "back": "crime novel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "deckaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "deckarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jazz",
    "back": "jazz",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "it-ingenjör",
    "back": "IT engineer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "it-ingenjören",
      "form2": "it-ingenjörer",
      "form3": "it-ingenjörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Syrien",
    "back": "Syria",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvällskurs",
    "back": "evening course",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvällskursen",
      "form2": "kvällskurser",
      "form3": "kvällskurserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arkitektur",
    "back": "architecture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arkitekturen",
      "form2": "arkitekturer",
      "form3": "arkitekturerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trivas",
    "back": "thrive, be happy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trivs",
      "form2": "trivdes",
      "form3": "trivts"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mormor",
    "back": "grandmother (maternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mormodern",
      "form2": "mormödrar",
      "form3": "mormödrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morfar",
    "back": "grandfather (maternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "morfadern",
      "form2": "morfäder",
      "form3": "morfäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tillsammans",
    "back": "together",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sport",
    "back": "sport",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "träna",
    "back": "exercise",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tränar",
      "form2": "tränade",
      "form3": "tränat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "karate",
    "back": "karate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sportig",
    "back": "athletic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "åka snowboard",
    "back": "go snowboarding"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på vintern",
    "back": "in the winter"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "spela volleyboll",
    "back": "play volleyball"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sol",
    "back": "sun",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "värme",
    "back": "warmth",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mat",
    "back": "food",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvudsats",
    "back": "main clause",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudsatsen",
      "form2": "huvudsatser",
      "form3": "huvudsatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konjunktion",
    "back": "conjunction",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konjunktionen",
      "form2": "konjunktioner",
      "form3": "konjunktionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "så",
    "back": "so",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stryka (stryker, strök, strukit) under",
    "back": "underline",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fest",
    "back": "party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "festen",
      "form2": "fester",
      "form3": "festerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vän",
    "back": "friend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vännen",
      "form2": "vänner",
      "form3": "vännerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter2_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter2",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klasskompis",
    "back": "classmate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klasskompisen",
      "form2": "klasskompisar",
      "form3": "klasskompisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "räkna",
    "back": "count",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "räknar",
      "form2": "räknade",
      "form3": "räknat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "siffra",
    "back": "digit, number",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "siffran",
      "form2": "siffraor",
      "form3": "siffraorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plats",
    "back": "place",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "platsen",
      "form2": "platser",
      "form3": "platserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kasta",
    "back": "throw, roll",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kastar",
      "form2": "kastade",
      "form3": "kastat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tärning",
    "back": "dice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tärningen",
      "form2": "tärningar",
      "form3": "tärningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minus",
    "back": "minus",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nummer",
    "back": "number",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "numret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "numren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gata",
    "back": "street",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gatan",
      "form2": "gataor",
      "form3": "gataorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hur många",
    "back": "how many"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "telefonnummer",
    "back": "telephone number",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "telefonnumret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "telefonnumren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ringa",
    "back": "call",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ringaer",
      "form2": "ringade",
      "form3": "ringat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i morgon",
    "back": "tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vilket år är du född?",
    "back": "What year were you born"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "född",
    "back": "born",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-dda"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gammal",
    "back": "old",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fika",
    "back": "have a coffee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fikar",
      "form2": "fikade",
      "form3": "fikat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hur mycket",
    "back": "how much"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ungefär",
    "back": "about, approximately",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skostorlek",
    "back": "shoe size",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skostorleken",
      "form2": "skostorlekar",
      "form3": "skostorlekarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grad",
    "back": "degree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "graden",
      "form2": "grader",
      "form3": "graderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tal",
    "back": "number",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "talet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "talen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur mycket är klockan?",
    "back": "What time is it"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hon/Den är ...",
    "back": "It is .."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klocka",
    "back": "watch, clock",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klockan",
      "form2": "klockaor",
      "form3": "klockaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "halv sju",
    "back": "six thirty"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halv",
    "back": "half",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "över",
    "back": "over",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "kvart i",
    "back": "quarter to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvart",
    "back": "quarter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvarten",
      "form2": "kvartar",
      "form3": "kvartarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prick",
    "back": "exactly",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "precis"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sekund",
    "back": "second",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sekunden",
      "form2": "sekunder",
      "form3": "sekunderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minut",
    "back": "minute",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minuten",
      "form2": "minuter",
      "form3": "minuterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halvtimme",
    "back": "half an hour",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "halvtimmeen",
      "form2": "halvtimmear",
      "form3": "halvtimmearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "timme",
    "back": "hour",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "timmeen",
      "form2": "timmear",
      "form3": "timmearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båt",
    "back": "boat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "båten",
      "form2": "båtar",
      "form3": "båtarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fem i",
    "back": "five to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fem över",
    "back": "five past"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "kvart över",
    "back": "quarter past"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fem över halv",
    "back": "thirty-five past"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrift",
    "back": "writing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skriften",
      "form2": "skrifter",
      "form3": "skrifterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på morgonen",
    "back": "in the morning"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på kvällen",
    "back": "in the evening"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på förmiddagen",
    "back": "before noon"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på eftermiddagen",
    "back": "in the afternoon"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på natten",
    "back": "at night"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fika",
    "back": "coffee break",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t) (vard"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yogaläger",
    "back": "yoga retreat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lägret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lägren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "nästa vecka",
    "back": "next week"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "program",
    "back": "program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "programmet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "programmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vilken tid",
    "back": "what time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "börja",
    "back": "begin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "börjar",
      "form2": "började",
      "form3": "börjat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "först",
    "back": "first",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "örtte",
    "back": "herbal tea",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "örttet",
      "form2": "örtteer",
      "form3": "örtteerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "koffein",
    "back": "caffeine",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Å gud!",
    "back": "Oh God"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snabbkaffe",
    "back": "instant coffee",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lunch",
    "back": "lunch",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lunchen",
      "form2": "luncher",
      "form3": "luncherna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hur dags",
    "back": "what time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "servera",
    "back": "serve",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "serverar",
      "form2": "serverade",
      "form3": "serverat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vegansk",
    "back": "vegan",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "kaffe på maten",
    "back": "coffee after the meal"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "paus",
    "back": "break, pause",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pausen",
      "form2": "pauser",
      "form3": "pauserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sista",
    "back": "last, final",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sluta",
    "back": "end",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slutar",
      "form2": "slutade",
      "form3": "slutat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det låter bra!",
    "back": "That sounds good"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fikapaus",
    "back": "coffee break",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fikapausen",
      "form2": "fikapauser",
      "form3": "fikapauserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frukost",
    "back": "breakfast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frukosten",
      "form2": "frukostar",
      "form3": "frukostarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mellanmål",
    "back": "light snack",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mellanmålet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "mellanmålen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "middag",
    "back": "dinner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "middagen",
      "form2": "middagar",
      "form3": "middagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter3_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter3",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hem",
    "back": "home",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hemmet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hemmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "favoritfik",
    "back": "favourite café, favourite coffee shop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "et",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "favoritfiken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ofta",
    "back": "often",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "älska",
    "back": "love",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "älskar",
      "form2": "älskade",
      "form3": "älskat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "favoritplats",
    "back": "favourite place",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "favoritplatsen",
      "form2": "favoritplatser",
      "form3": "favoritplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glad",
    "back": "happy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "glatt",
        "glada"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stund",
    "back": "moment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stunden",
      "form2": "stunder",
      "form3": "stunderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bagare",
    "back": "baker",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bagaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bagarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "baka",
    "back": "bake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bakar",
      "form2": "bakaade",
      "form3": "bakaade"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fikabröd",
    "back": "pastries",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "et",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fikabröden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ut",
    "back": "out",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "provsmaka",
    "back": "taste, sample",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "provsmakar",
      "form2": "provsmakade",
      "form3": "provsmakat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bulle",
    "back": "roll, bun",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bullen",
      "form2": "bullear",
      "form3": "bullearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaka",
    "back": "cookie, biscuit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kakan",
      "form2": "kakaor",
      "form3": "kakaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smörgås",
    "back": "sandwich",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smörgåsen",
      "form2": "smörgåsar",
      "form3": "smörgåsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kardemummabulle",
    "back": "cardamom bun, cardamom roll",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kardemummabullen",
      "form2": "kardemummabullear",
      "form3": "kardemummabullearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "semla",
    "back": "semla, Swedish cream bun",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "semlan",
      "form2": "semlaor",
      "form3": "semlaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "allt",
    "back": "everything",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "god",
    "back": "good",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "gott",
        "goda"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ligga",
    "back": "be located",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "liggaer",
      "form2": "låg",
      "form3": "legat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjälpa",
    "back": "help",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjälpaer",
      "form2": "hjälpte",
      "form3": "hjälpt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "följa med",
    "back": "join in, come along"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gärna",
    "back": "happily, willingly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "länge",
    "back": "a long time, long",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sak",
    "back": "thing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "saken",
      "form2": "saker",
      "form3": "sakerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stackars",
    "back": "poor, unfortunate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "då",
    "back": "then",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bara",
    "back": "only",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snus",
    "back": "snuff",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "livs",
    "back": "grocery store",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "perfekt",
    "back": "perfect",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "wienerbröd",
    "back": "Danish pastry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "wienerbrödet",
      "form2": "wienerbröden",
      "form3": "wienerbrödena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjälpverb",
    "back": "helping verbs, auxiliary verbs",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjälpverbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hjälpverben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "infinitiv",
    "back": "infinitive",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "infinitivet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "infinitiven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ska",
    "back": "will",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vilja",
    "back": "want",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vill",
      "form2": "ville",
      "form3": "velat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "satsadverbial",
    "back": "adverbial",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "satsadverbialet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "satsadverbialen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "handla",
    "back": "shop, buy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "handlar",
      "form2": "handlaade",
      "form3": "handlaat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "skulle vilja",
    "back": "would like to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Var det bra så?",
    "back": "Will that be all"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kan jag få ...?",
    "back": "Can I have ..."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "javissst",
    "back": "yes, of course",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varsågod",
    "back": "you’re welcome",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Något annat?",
    "back": "Anything else"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "nej tack",
    "back": "no thank you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det var bra så.",
    "back": "That is all"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det blir ... kronor.",
    "back": "That comes to ... kronor"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krona",
    "back": "crown",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kronan",
      "form2": "kronaor",
      "form3": "kronaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blippa",
    "back": "tap, scan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blippar",
      "form2": "blippade",
      "form3": "blippat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kort",
    "back": "card",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kortet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "korten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vill du ha ...?",
    "back": "Do you want ..."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvitto",
    "back": "receipt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvittot",
      "form2": "kvittoon",
      "form3": "kvittoona"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "latte",
    "back": "latte",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "liten",
    "back": "small",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "litet",
        "små"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mellan",
    "back": "medium",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ostsmörgås",
    "back": "cheese sandwich",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ostsmörgåsen",
      "form2": "ostsmörgåsar",
      "form3": "ostsmörgåsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ost",
    "back": "cheese",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "osten",
      "form2": "ostar",
      "form3": "ostarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "precis",
    "back": "exactly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kosta",
    "back": "cost",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kostar",
      "form2": "kostade",
      "form3": "kostat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mer",
    "back": "more",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strax",
    "back": "soon",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tar ni kontanter?",
    "back": "Do you accept cash"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tyvärr",
    "back": "unfortunately",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inga problem",
    "back": "no problem"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betala",
    "back": "pay",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "betalar",
      "form2": "betalade",
      "form3": "betalat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "toppen",
    "back": "super, great",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "demonstrativa pronomen",
    "back": "demonstrative pronouns"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "när",
    "back": "when",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "peka",
    "back": "point",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pekar",
      "form2": "pekade",
      "form3": "pekat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nära",
    "back": "near, close to",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "en bit bort",
    "back": "a short distance away"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontrollera",
    "back": "check, control",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kontrollerar",
      "form2": "kontrollerade",
      "form3": "kontrollerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sök",
    "back": "find, search",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bild",
    "back": "picture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilden",
      "form2": "bilder",
      "form3": "bilderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morotskaka",
    "back": "carrot cake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "morotskakan",
      "form2": "morotskakaor",
      "form3": "morotskakaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chokladboll",
    "back": "chocolate ball",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "chokladbollen",
      "form2": "chokladbollar",
      "form3": "chokladbollarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mazarin",
    "back": "almond pastry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mazarinen",
      "form2": "mazariner",
      "form3": "mazarinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dammsugare",
    "back": "vacuum cleaner (pastry)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dammsugaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "dammsugarearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veganbrownie",
    "back": "vegan brownie",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n",
        "-s"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brownie",
    "back": "brownie",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n",
        "-s"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "räksallad",
    "back": "shrimp salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "räksalladen",
      "form2": "räksallader",
      "form3": "räksalladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "falafelsallad",
    "back": "falafel salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "falafelsalladen",
      "form2": "falafelsallader",
      "form3": "falafelsalladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ostpaj",
    "back": "cheese pie, cheese quiche",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ostpajen",
      "form2": "ostpajer",
      "form3": "ostpajerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pizzabit",
    "back": "pizza slice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pizzabiten",
      "form2": "pizzabitar",
      "form3": "pizzabitarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bryggkaffe",
    "back": "brewed coffee",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glas",
    "back": "glass",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glaset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "glasen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läsk",
    "back": "soft drink, fizzy drink",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "= läskedryck) (-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "päron",
    "back": "pear",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "päronet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "päronen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "paket",
    "back": "package",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "paketet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "paketen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sammansatta ord",
    "back": "compound words"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flera",
    "back": "several",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "första",
    "back": "first",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snusdosa",
    "back": "snuff box",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snusdosan",
      "form2": "snusdosaor",
      "form3": "snusdosaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bokstav",
    "back": "letter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bokstaven",
      "form2": "bokstäver",
      "form3": "bokstäverna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gurka",
    "back": "cucumber",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gurkan",
      "form2": "gurkaor",
      "form3": "gurkaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "druva / vindruva",
    "back": "grape",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "druva / vindruvan",
      "form2": "druva / vindruvaor",
      "form3": "druva / vindruvaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "purjolök",
    "back": "leek",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "purjolöken",
      "form2": "purjolökar",
      "form3": "purjolökarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "citron",
    "back": "lemon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "citronen",
      "form2": "citroner",
      "form3": "citronerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ägg",
    "back": "egg",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ägget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "äggen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plural",
    "back": "plural",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sko",
    "back": "shoe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skon",
      "form2": "skor",
      "form3": "skorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bakelse",
    "back": "pastry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bakelsen",
      "form2": "bakelseer",
      "form3": "bakelseerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "saffransbulle",
    "back": "saffron bun",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "saffransbullen",
      "form2": "saffransbullear",
      "form3": "saffransbullearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mango",
    "back": "mango",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n",
        "-r"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mataffär",
    "back": "grocery store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mataffären",
      "form2": "mataffärer",
      "form3": "mataffärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hylla",
    "back": "shelf",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hyllan",
      "form2": "hyllaor",
      "form3": "hyllaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "till vänster",
    "back": "to the left"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "till höger",
    "back": "to the right"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "rakt fram",
    "back": "straight ahead"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "andra",
    "back": "second",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tredje",
    "back": "third",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjärde",
    "back": "fourth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "femte",
    "back": "fifth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "frukt och grönt",
    "back": "fruit and vegetable section"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frukt",
    "back": "fruit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frukten",
      "form2": "frukter",
      "form3": "frukterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grön",
    "back": "green",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mejeri",
    "back": "dairy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mejeriet",
      "form2": "mejerier",
      "form3": "mejerierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fisk",
    "back": "fish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fisken",
      "form2": "fiskar",
      "form3": "fiskarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter4_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter4",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skaldjur",
    "back": "she",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skaldjuret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skaldjuren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ska vi gå på ...?",
    "back": "Shall we go to ..."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bio",
    "back": "cinema",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "biograf",
    "back": "cinema",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "biografen",
      "form2": "biografer",
      "form3": "biograferna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fredag",
    "back": "Friday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fredagen",
      "form2": "fredagar",
      "form3": "fredagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hänga med",
    "back": "join in"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad ska ni se?",
    "back": "What are you going to see"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "semester",
    "back": "vacation, holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "semestern",
      "form2": "semesterrar",
      "form3": "semesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helvete",
    "back": "hell",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "helvetet",
      "form2": "helveten",
      "form3": "helvetena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skräckfilm",
    "back": "horror movie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skräckfilmen",
      "form2": "skräckfilmer",
      "form3": "skräckfilmerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komedi",
    "back": "comedy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "komedin",
      "form2": "komedier",
      "form3": "komedierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låta",
    "back": "sound",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "låtaer",
      "form2": "lät",
      "form3": "låtit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Var går den?",
    "back": "Where does it play"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Den börjar klockan ...",
    "back": "It starts at .."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta ett glas ...",
    "back": "have a glass of .."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ja, självklart!",
    "back": "Yes, of course"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Inget speciellt.",
    "back": "Nothing special"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur så?",
    "back": "How so"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "biljett",
    "back": "ticket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "biljetten",
      "form2": "biljetter",
      "form3": "biljetterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "drömspel",
    "back": "dream play",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "drömspelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "drömspelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvudroll",
    "back": "leading role, main role",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudrollen",
      "form2": "huvudroller",
      "form3": "huvudrollerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lust",
    "back": "desire",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lusten",
      "form2": "lustar",
      "form3": "lustarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "favorit",
    "back": "favorite",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "favoriten",
      "form2": "favoriter",
      "form3": "favoriterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inte direkt",
    "back": "not really"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad synd!",
    "back": "Too bad"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i stället",
    "back": "instead"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ståupp",
    "back": "stand-up comedy",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kosta",
    "back": "cost",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kostar",
      "form2": "kostade",
      "form3": "kostat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inträde",
    "back": "admission",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inträdet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "inträden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ses",
    "back": "meet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ses",
      "form2": "sågs",
      "form3": "setts"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slutspel",
    "back": "playoffs",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slutspelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "slutspelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mot",
    "back": "against",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Grejt!",
    "back": "Great"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fixa",
    "back": "sort out, buy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fixar",
      "form2": "fixade",
      "form3": "fixat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veckodag",
    "back": "weekday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "veckodagen",
      "form2": "veckodagar",
      "form3": "veckodagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "måndag",
    "back": "Monday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "måndagen",
      "form2": "måndagar",
      "form3": "måndagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tisdag",
    "back": "Tuesday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tisdagen",
      "form2": "tisdagar",
      "form3": "tisdagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "onsdag",
    "back": "Wednesday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "onsdagen",
      "form2": "onsdagar",
      "form3": "onsdagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "torsdag",
    "back": "Thursday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "torsdagen",
      "form2": "torsdagar",
      "form3": "torsdagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lördag",
    "back": "Saturday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lördagen",
      "form2": "lördagar",
      "form3": "lördagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "söndag",
    "back": "Sunday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "söndagen",
      "form2": "söndagar",
      "form3": "söndagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pjäs",
    "back": "play",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pjäsen",
      "form2": "pjäser",
      "form3": "pjäserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "citat",
    "back": "quote, quotation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "citatet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "citaten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "synd om",
    "back": "pity"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "människa",
    "back": "human, person",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "människan",
      "form2": "människor",
      "form3": "människorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "annons",
    "back": "advertisement",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "annonsen",
      "form2": "annonser",
      "form3": "annonserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dansa",
    "back": "dance",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dansar",
      "form2": "dansade",
      "form3": "dansat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjunga",
    "back": "sing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjungaer",
      "form2": "sjöng",
      "form3": "sjungit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framtid",
    "back": "future",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i kväll",
    "back": "tonight"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i morgon",
    "back": "tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "positiv",
    "back": "positive",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "negativ",
    "back": "negative",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bestämma",
    "back": "decide",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bestämmaer",
      "form2": "bestämmade",
      "form3": "bestämmat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "presens futurum",
    "back": "future tense"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "squash",
    "back": "squash",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slappa",
    "back": "relax",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slappar",
      "form2": "slappade",
      "form3": "slappat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad gör du på fritiden?",
    "back": "What do you do in your free time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fritid",
    "back": "free time, spare time",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korrekt",
    "back": "correct",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "övning",
    "back": "exercise",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "övningen",
      "form2": "övningar",
      "form3": "övningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fortsätta",
    "back": "continue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fortsättaer",
      "form2": "fortsatte",
      "form3": "fortsatt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hänga",
    "back": "hang out",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hängaer",
      "form2": "hängade",
      "form3": "hängat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klättra",
    "back": "climb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klättrar",
      "form2": "klättrade",
      "form3": "klättrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejta",
    "back": "skate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtar",
      "form2": "skejtade",
      "form3": "skejtat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klättring",
    "back": "climbing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klättringen",
      "form2": "klättringar",
      "form3": "klättringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bruka",
    "back": "usually",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "brukar",
      "form2": "brukaade",
      "form3": "har brukat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "serie",
    "back": "series",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "serien",
      "form2": "serieer",
      "form3": "serieerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "familj",
    "back": "family",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "familjen",
      "form2": "familjer",
      "form3": "familjerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på landet",
    "back": "in the countryside"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "där",
    "back": "there",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mysa",
    "back": "cozy up",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mysaer",
      "form2": "mysate",
      "form3": "mysat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brädspel",
    "back": "board game",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "brädspelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "brädspelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kolla",
    "back": "watch",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kollar",
      "form2": "kollade",
      "form3": "kollat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dataspel",
    "back": "video game",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dataspelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "dataspelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hund",
    "back": "dog",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hunden",
      "form2": "hundar",
      "form3": "hundarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "göra trick",
    "back": "do tricks"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bowla",
    "back": "bowl",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bowlar",
      "form2": "bowlade",
      "form3": "bowlat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta en AW",
    "back": "go for after-work drinks"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "promenera",
    "back": "walk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "promenerar",
      "form2": "promenerade",
      "form3": "promenerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "park",
    "back": "park",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "parken",
      "form2": "parker",
      "form3": "parkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrattyoga",
    "back": "laughter yoga",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trädgård",
    "back": "garden",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trädgården",
      "form2": "trädgårdar",
      "form3": "trädgårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blomma",
    "back": "flower",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blomman",
      "form2": "blommor",
      "form3": "blommorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grönsak",
    "back": "vegetable",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grönsaken",
      "form2": "grönsaker",
      "form3": "grönsakerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bär",
    "back": "berries",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bäret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bären"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höna",
    "back": "hen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hönan",
      "form2": "hönaor",
      "form3": "hönaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "få",
    "back": "get",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "får",
      "form2": "fick",
      "form3": "fått"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "superekologisk",
    "back": "ultra-organic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekologisk",
    "back": "organic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "loppis",
    "back": "flea market",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "loppisen",
      "form2": "loppisar",
      "form3": "loppisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "åka runt",
    "back": "drive around"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "auktion",
    "back": "auction",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "auktionen",
      "form2": "auktioner",
      "form3": "auktionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samla",
    "back": "collect",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "samlar",
      "form2": "samlade",
      "form3": "samlat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jaga",
    "back": "hunt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jagar",
      "form2": "jagaade",
      "form3": "jagat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fiska",
    "back": "fish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fiskar",
      "form2": "fiskade",
      "form3": "fiskat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bibliotek",
    "back": "library",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "biblioteket",
      "form2": "biblioteken",
      "form3": "bibliotekena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "aldrig",
    "back": "never",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ibland",
    "back": "sometimes",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vid havet",
    "back": "by the sea, at the seaside"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bada",
    "back": "swim",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "badar",
      "form2": "badade",
      "form3": "badat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spela",
    "back": "play",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spelar",
      "form2": "spelade",
      "form3": "spelat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "boule",
    "back": "boules",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "paraplydrink",
    "back": "umbrella drink",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "paraplydrinken",
      "form2": "paraplydrinkar",
      "form3": "paraplydrinkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "härlig",
    "back": "lovely",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "för",
    "back": "because",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fler saker",
    "back": "more things"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotboll",
    "back": "football, soccer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollen",
      "form2": "fotbollar",
      "form3": "fotbollarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "innebandy",
    "back": "floorball",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hockey",
    "back": "ice hockey",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "spela kort",
    "back": "play cards"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trumpet",
    "back": "trumpet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trumpeten",
      "form2": "trumpeter",
      "form3": "trumpeterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skida",
    "back": "ski",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skidan",
      "form2": "skidaor",
      "form3": "skidaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skridsko",
    "back": "skate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skridskon",
      "form2": "skridskoor",
      "form3": "skridskoorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejtboard",
    "back": "skateboard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtboarden",
      "form2": "skejtboardar",
      "form3": "skejtboardarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inlines",
    "back": "inline skates, rollerblades",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "natur",
    "back": "nature",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kyrka",
    "back": "church",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kyrkan",
      "form2": "kyrkaor",
      "form3": "kyrkaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "moské",
    "back": "mosque",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "synagoga",
    "back": "synagogue",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tempel",
    "back": "temple",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "teater",
    "back": "theater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "teatern",
      "form2": "teatrar",
      "form3": "teatrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "opera",
    "back": "opera",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "operan",
      "form2": "operaor",
      "form3": "operaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konsert",
    "back": "concert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konserten",
      "form2": "konserter",
      "form3": "konserterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klubb",
    "back": "club",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klubben",
      "form2": "klubbar",
      "form3": "klubbarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "festival",
    "back": "festival",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "festivalen",
      "form2": "festivaler",
      "form3": "festivalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bar",
    "back": "bar",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "baren",
      "form2": "barer",
      "form3": "barerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "match",
    "back": "match, game",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "matchen",
      "form2": "matcher",
      "form3": "matcherna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "adverbial",
    "back": "adverbial",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sällan",
    "back": "rarely",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "alltid",
    "back": "always",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fundamentposition",
    "back": "initial position",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidsadverbial",
    "back": "temporal adverbial",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frekvens",
    "back": "frequency",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frekvensen",
      "form2": "frekvenser",
      "form3": "frekvenserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hobby",
    "back": "hobby",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hobbyn",
      "form2": "hobbyer",
      "form3": "hobbyerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "laga mat",
    "back": "cook"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "polisserie",
    "back": "cop show, crime drama series",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "polisserien",
      "form2": "polisserier",
      "form3": "polisserierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vilken ... ska vi se?",
    "back": "Which ... should we watch"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framför",
    "back": "in front of",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "streamingtjänst",
    "back": "streaming service",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "streamingtjänsten",
      "form2": "streamingtjänster",
      "form3": "streamingtjänsterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "romantisk",
    "back": "romantic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "historisk",
    "back": "historical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klassisk",
    "back": "classical, classic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läskig",
    "back": "scary",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "handla om",
    "back": "it is about"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hitta",
    "back": "find",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hittar",
      "form2": "hittade",
      "form3": "hittat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kärlek",
    "back": "love",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kärleken",
      "form2": "kärleker",
      "form3": "kärlekarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "efteråt",
    "back": "afterwards",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det blir bra!",
    "back": "Fine"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "adjektiv",
    "back": "adjective",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grundform",
    "back": "infinitive form",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grundformen",
      "form2": "grundformer",
      "form3": "grundformerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inom parentes",
    "back": "in parentheses"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dokumentär",
    "back": "documentary",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dokumentären",
      "form2": "dokumentärer",
      "form3": "dokumentärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konst",
    "back": "art",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konsten",
      "form2": "konster",
      "form3": "konsterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tråkig",
    "back": "boring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fantastisk",
    "back": "fantastic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bakning",
    "back": "baking",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bakningen",
      "form2": "bakningar",
      "form3": "bakningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dålig",
    "back": "bad, ill",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sorglig",
    "back": "sad",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svår",
    "back": "difficult",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad gillar du för ...?",
    "back": "What kind of ... do you like"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "japansk",
    "back": "Japanese",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "genre",
    "back": "genre",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "genren",
      "form2": "genrer",
      "form3": "genrerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "actionfilm",
    "back": "action movie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "actionfilmen",
      "form2": "actionfilmer",
      "form3": "actionfilmerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "science fiction",
    "back": "science fiction"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "drama",
    "back": "drama",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dramat",
      "form2": "dramaer",
      "form3": "dramaerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rysare",
    "back": "thriller, horror",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rysareen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "rysarearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "några gånger",
    "back": "few times"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forskare",
    "back": "researcher",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forskaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "forskarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forska",
    "back": "do research",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forskar",
      "form2": "forskade",
      "form3": "forskat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bioteknik",
    "back": "biotechnology",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "biotekniken",
      "form2": "biotekniker",
      "form3": "bioteknikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hans",
    "back": "his",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Gamla stan",
    "back": "Old Town"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Lutande tornet",
    "back": "The Leaning Tower of Pisa"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vakna av",
    "back": "wake up from"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "duva",
    "back": "pigeon, dove",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "duvan",
      "form2": "duvaor",
      "form3": "duvaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sitta",
    "back": "sit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sittaer",
      "form2": "satt",
      "form3": "suttit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på taket",
    "back": "on the roof"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå upp",
    "back": "go up"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hörn",
    "back": "corner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hörnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hörnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skorpa",
    "back": "rusk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skorpan",
      "form2": "skorpaor",
      "form3": "skorpaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaféägare",
    "back": "café owner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kaféägaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kaféägarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väder",
    "back": "weather",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vädret",
      "form2": "väder",
      "form3": "vädren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "politik",
    "back": "politics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "semesterplan",
    "back": "holiday plan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "semesterplanen",
      "form2": "semesterplaner",
      "form3": "semesterplanerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stad",
    "back": "city, town",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "staden",
      "form2": "städer",
      "form3": "städerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "möte",
    "back": "meeting",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mötet",
      "form2": "möten",
      "form3": "mötena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_187",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "undervisa",
    "back": "teach",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "undervisar",
      "form2": "undervisade",
      "form3": "undervisat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_188",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "speciell",
    "back": "special",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_189",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "turist",
    "back": "tourist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "turisten",
      "form2": "turister",
      "form3": "turisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_190",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "videomöte",
    "back": "video meeting",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "videomötet",
      "form2": "videomöten",
      "form3": "videomötena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_191",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "USA",
    "back": "USA",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_192",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "stänga av",
    "back": "shut off"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_193",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "springa",
    "back": "run",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "springaer",
      "form2": "sprang",
      "form3": "sprungit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_194",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vid floden",
    "back": "by the river"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_195",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "middag",
    "back": "dinner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "middagen",
      "form2": "middagar",
      "form3": "middagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_196",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på vägen hem",
    "back": "on the way home"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_197",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "måne",
    "back": "moon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "månen",
      "form2": "månear",
      "form3": "månearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_198",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sent på kvällen",
    "back": "late in the evening"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_199",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flytta",
    "back": "move",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flyttar",
      "form2": "flyttade",
      "form3": "flyttat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_200",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "preteritum",
    "back": "past tense",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_201",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "special",
    "back": "special",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_202",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "byta ut",
    "back": "replace"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_203",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vampyr",
    "back": "vampire",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vampyren",
      "form2": "vampyrer",
      "form3": "vampyrerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_204",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förkyld",
    "back": "have a cold",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_205",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "meny",
    "back": "menu",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "menyn",
      "form2": "menyer",
      "form3": "menyerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_206",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ny",
    "back": "new",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "nytt",
        "nya"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_207",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yrke",
    "back": "profession",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "yrket",
      "form2": "yrken",
      "form3": "yrkena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_208",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekonomi",
    "back": "accounts, economics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_209",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tema",
    "back": "theme",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "temat",
      "form2": "teman",
      "form3": "temana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter5_210",
    "chapter": "Chapter5",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ung",
    "back": "young",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släkt",
    "back": "relatives",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släkten",
      "form2": "släkter",
      "form3": "släkterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "syskon",
    "back": "sibling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "syskonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "syskonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bror",
    "back": "brother",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "brorn",
      "form2": "bröder",
      "form3": "bröderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förskola",
    "back": "preschool",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förskolan",
      "form2": "förskolaor",
      "form3": "förskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "personlig tränare",
    "back": "personal trainer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båda",
    "back": "both",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svägerska",
    "back": "sister-in-law",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svägerskan",
      "form2": "svägerskaor",
      "form3": "svägerskaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "känna",
    "back": "know",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kännaer",
      "form2": "kännade",
      "form3": "kännat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "syskonbarn",
    "back": "niece/nephew",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "syskonbarnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "syskonbarnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "egen",
    "back": "own",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bonusbarn",
    "back": "stepchild",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bonusbarnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bonusbarnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "väldigt mycket",
    "back": "very much"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förälder",
    "back": "parent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "föräldern",
      "form2": "föräldrar",
      "form3": "föräldrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "omgift",
    "back": "remarried",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plastmamma",
    "back": "stepmother",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "plastmamman",
      "form2": "plastmammaor",
      "form3": "plastmammaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plastikkirurg",
    "back": "plastic surgeon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "plastikkirurgen",
      "form2": "plastikkirurger",
      "form3": "plastikkirurgerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "privat",
    "back": "private",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klinik",
    "back": "clinic",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kliniken",
      "form2": "kliniker",
      "form3": "klinikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stepbonussyskon",
    "back": "step-siblings",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stepbonussyskonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "stepbonussyskonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "många",
    "back": "many",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halvsyskon",
    "back": "half-sibling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "halvsyskonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "halvsyskonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gång",
    "back": "time",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gången",
      "form2": "gånger",
      "form3": "gångerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "få barn",
    "back": "have children, have a child"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "syster",
    "back": "sister",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "systern",
      "form2": "systrar",
      "form3": "systrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "moster",
    "back": "aunt (maternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mostern",
      "form2": "mostrar",
      "form3": "mostrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gifta sig",
    "back": "get married",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gifta siger",
      "form2": "gifta sige",
      "form3": "gift"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fransman",
    "back": "Frenchman",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fransmannen",
      "form2": "fransmän",
      "form3": "fransmännen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "professor",
    "back": "professor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "professorn",
      "form2": "professorer",
      "form3": "professorerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kärnteknik",
    "back": "nuclear technology",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kärntekniken",
      "form2": "kärntekniker",
      "form3": "kärnteknikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kusin",
    "back": "cousin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kusinen",
      "form2": "kusiner",
      "form3": "kusinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ungefär",
    "back": "about, approximately",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på min pappas sida",
    "back": "on my father's side"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ha mycket kontakt",
    "back": "have a lot of contact, be in close contact"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "alla",
    "back": "everyone",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barnbarn",
    "back": "grandchildren",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "barnbarnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "barnbarnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bonusbarnbarn",
    "back": "step-grandchild",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barnbarnsbarn",
    "back": "great-grandchild",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släkting",
    "back": "relative",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släktingen",
      "form2": "släktingar",
      "form3": "släktingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skådespelare",
    "back": "actor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skådespelaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skådespelarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "farbror",
    "back": "uncle (paternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "farbrodern",
      "form2": "farbröder",
      "form3": "farbröderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjökapten",
    "back": "sea captain, ship captain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjökaptenen",
      "form2": "sjökaptener",
      "form3": "sjökaptenerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morfarsfar",
    "back": "maternal great-grandfather",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "morfarsfarn",
      "form2": "morfarsfäder",
      "form3": "morfarsfäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konstnär",
    "back": "artist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konstnären",
      "form2": "konstnärer",
      "form3": "konstnärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "faster",
    "back": "aunt (paternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fastern",
      "form2": "fastrar",
      "form3": "fastrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Nobelpriset",
    "back": "the Nobel Prize",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kemi",
    "back": "chemistry",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "familjeord",
    "back": "family-related words",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "familjeordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "familjeorden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pappa",
    "back": "dad, father",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pappan",
      "form2": "pappaor",
      "form3": "pappaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "far",
    "back": "father",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "farn",
      "form2": "fäder",
      "form3": "fäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mamma",
    "back": "mom, mother",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mamman",
      "form2": "mammaor",
      "form3": "mammaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mor",
    "back": "mother",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "morn",
      "form2": "mödrar",
      "form3": "mödrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släktträd",
    "back": "family tree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släktträdet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "släktträden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "passa in",
    "back": "fit in",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "passa inr",
      "form2": "passa inde",
      "form3": "passa int"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dotter",
    "back": "daughter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dottern",
      "form2": "döttrar",
      "form3": "döttrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "separera",
    "back": "separate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "separerar",
      "form2": "separerade",
      "form3": "separerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "relation",
    "back": "relationship",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "relationen",
      "form2": "relationer",
      "form3": "relationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "familjemedlem",
    "back": "family member",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "familjemedlemmen",
      "form2": "familjemedlemmar",
      "form3": "familjemedlemmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låtsassyskon",
    "back": "step-sibling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "låtsassyskonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "låtsassyskonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "extrapappa",
    "back": "extra dad, bonus dad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "extrapappan",
      "form2": "extrapappaor",
      "form3": "extrapappaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "relativt pronomen",
    "back": "relative pronoun"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Australien",
    "back": "Australia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "psykolog",
    "back": "psychologist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "psykologen",
      "form2": "psykologer",
      "form3": "psykologerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå i skolan",
    "back": "go to school"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skola",
    "back": "school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolan",
      "form2": "skolaor",
      "form3": "skolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yogainstruktör",
    "back": "yoga instructor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "yogainstruktören",
      "form2": "yogainstruktörer",
      "form3": "yogainstruktörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "piano",
    "back": "piano",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pianot",
      "form2": "pianon",
      "form3": "pianona"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jaha, wow!",
    "back": "I see, wow"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ju",
    "back": "you know",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flytta",
    "back": "move",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flyttar",
      "form2": "flyttade",
      "form3": "flyttat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Polen",
    "back": "Poland",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Finland",
    "back": "Finland",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i helgen",
    "back": "this weekend"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helg",
    "back": "weekend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "helgen",
      "form2": "helger",
      "form3": "helgerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Gotland",
    "back": "Gotland, island in the Baltic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jaha, vad trevligt!",
    "back": "I see, that's nice"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hos",
    "back": "at",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "possessiva pronomen",
    "back": "possessive pronouns"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "min",
    "back": "my",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "mitt",
        "mina"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "din",
    "back": "your",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "ditt",
        "dina"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hennes",
    "back": "her",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hen",
    "back": "they/them",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hens",
    "back": "their",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dess",
    "back": "its",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "they",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vår",
    "back": "our",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "er",
    "back": "your",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "deras",
    "back": "their",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvadratmeter",
    "back": "square meters",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvadratmetern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kvadratmetrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sakna",
    "back": "miss",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "saknar",
      "form2": "saknade",
      "form3": "saknat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Indien",
    "back": "India",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korean",
    "back": "Korean",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Sydkorea",
    "back": "South Korea",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inga",
    "back": "no",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ensam",
    "back": "alone",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "ensamma"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hus",
    "back": "house",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "husen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Nobelpristagare",
    "back": "Nobel prize winner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "Nobelpristagaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "Nobelpristagarearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i måndags",
    "back": "last Monday"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stadshus",
    "back": "city hall",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stadshuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "stadshusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Är det sant?",
    "back": "Is it true? Really"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Nobelfesten",
    "back": "the Nobel Banquet",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pris",
    "back": "prize",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "priset",
      "form2": "priser",
      "form3": "priserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Coolt, va?",
    "back": "Cool, right? Isn't it cool"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "cool",
    "back": "cool",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "verkligen",
    "back": "really",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "examen",
    "back": "degree",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "–",
        "examina"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "molekyl",
    "back": "molecule",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "molekylen",
      "form2": "molekyler",
      "form3": "molekylerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "luktsinne",
    "back": "sense of smell",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forskningsstipendium",
    "back": "research grant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forskningsstipendiumet",
      "form2": "forskningsstipendiumer",
      "form3": "forskningsstipendiumerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spännande",
    "back": "exciting, suspenseful",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kemiläxa",
    "back": "chemistry homework",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läxa",
    "back": "homework",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läxan",
      "form2": "läxaor",
      "form3": "läxaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i höstas",
    "back": "last fall, autumn"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höra",
    "back": "hear",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hör",
      "form2": "hörde",
      "form3": "hört"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "otrolig",
    "back": "incredible",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "massa",
    "back": "a lot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "massan",
      "form2": "massaor",
      "form3": "massaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släktmiddag",
    "back": "extended family dinner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släktmiddagen",
      "form2": "släktmiddagar",
      "form3": "släktmiddagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i lördags",
    "back": "last Saturday"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättekul",
    "back": "a lot of fun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättetrevlig",
    "back": "really nice",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prisutdelning",
    "back": "award ceremony",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prisutdelningen",
      "form2": "prisutdelningar",
      "form3": "prisutdelningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kung",
    "back": "king",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kungen",
      "form2": "kungar",
      "form3": "kungarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inte precis",
    "back": "not exactly"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "se",
    "back": "see",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ser",
      "form2": "såg",
      "form3": "sett"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "objektspronomen",
    "back": "object pronoun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mig",
    "back": "me",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dig",
    "back": "you",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "honom",
    "back": "him",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "henne",
    "back": "her",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "den/det",
    "back": "it",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "oss",
    "back": "us",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "er",
    "back": "you",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dem",
    "back": "them",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vilka objektspronomen står tillsammans med fraserna i rutan?",
    "back": "Which object pronouns are used with the phrases in the box"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bil",
    "back": "car",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilen",
      "form2": "bilar",
      "form3": "bilarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vacker",
    "back": "beautiful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-vackra"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dynamit",
    "back": "dynamite",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "december",
    "back": "December",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dö",
    "back": "die",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dör",
      "form2": "dog",
      "form3": "dött"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kemist",
    "back": "chemist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kemisten",
      "form2": "kemisten",
      "form3": "kemisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uppfinnare",
    "back": "inventor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "uppfinnaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "uppfinnarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ogift",
    "back": "unmarried, single",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "testamente",
    "back": "will",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "testamentet",
      "form2": "testamenten",
      "form3": "testamentena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fysik",
    "back": "physics",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fysiken",
      "form2": "fysiker",
      "form3": "fysikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "litteratur",
    "back": "literature",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "litteraturen",
      "form2": "litteraturer",
      "form3": "litteraturerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fred",
    "back": "peace",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "freden",
      "form2": "freder",
      "form3": "frederna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dela",
    "back": "share, give out",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "delar",
      "form2": "delade",
      "form3": "delat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kronprins",
    "back": "crown prince",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kronprinsen",
      "form2": "kronprinsar",
      "form3": "kronprinsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fredspris",
    "back": "peace prize",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "födas",
    "back": "be born",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-",
        "föds",
        "föddes",
        "fötts"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arkitekt",
    "back": "architect",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arkitekten",
      "form2": "arkitekter",
      "form3": "arkitekterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vapenkonstruktör",
    "back": "weapons engineer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vapenkonstruktören",
      "form2": "vapenkonstruktörer",
      "form3": "vapenkonstruktörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekonomisk",
    "back": "economic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "problem",
    "back": "problem",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "problemet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "problemen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Ryssland",
    "back": "Russia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "filosofi",
    "back": "philosophy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ryska",
    "back": "Russian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tyska",
    "back": "German",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "författare",
    "back": "author, writer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "författaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "författarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "17-åring",
    "back": "17-year-old",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "17-åringen",
      "form2": "17-åringar",
      "form3": "17-åringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "göra",
    "back": "do, make",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gör",
      "form2": "gjorde",
      "form3": "gjort"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studieresa",
    "back": "study trip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "studieresan",
      "form2": "studieresaor",
      "form3": "studieresaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Europa",
    "back": "Europe",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "komma i kontakt med",
    "back": "get in touch with"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nitroglycerin",
    "back": "nitroglycerin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nitroglycerinen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "nitroglycerinet"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "affär",
    "back": "business",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "affären",
      "form2": "affärer",
      "form3": "affärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "experimentera",
    "back": "experiment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "experimenterar",
      "form2": "experimenterade",
      "form3": "experimenterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "explosion",
    "back": "explosion",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "explosionen",
      "form2": "explosioner",
      "form3": "explosionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bygga",
    "back": "build",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byggaer",
      "form2": "byggade",
      "form3": "byggat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fabrik",
    "back": "factory",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fabriken",
      "form2": "fabriker",
      "form3": "fabrikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbete",
    "back": "work",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetet",
      "form2": "arbeten",
      "form3": "arbeteena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "patent",
    "back": "patent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "patentet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "patenten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjäna",
    "back": "earn",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tjänar",
      "form2": "tjänade",
      "form3": "tjänat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tjäna pengar",
    "back": "earn money"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äga",
    "back": "own",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ägaer",
      "form2": "ägde",
      "form3": "ägt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "resa",
    "back": "travel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "resaer",
      "form2": "resate",
      "form3": "resat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "miljon",
    "back": "million",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "miljonen",
      "form2": "miljoner",
      "form3": "miljonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i dagens värde",
    "back": "in today's value"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "viktig",
    "back": "important",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "man trodde",
    "back": "it was believed, people believed"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gruva",
    "back": "mine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gruvan",
      "form2": "gruvaor",
      "form3": "gruvaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunnel",
    "back": "tunnel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tunneln",
      "form2": "tunneltunnlar",
      "form3": "tunnlarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väg",
    "back": "road",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vägen",
      "form2": "vägar",
      "form3": "vägarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "järnväg",
    "back": "railway",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "järnvägen",
      "form2": "järnvägar",
      "form3": "järnvägarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bomb",
    "back": "bomb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bomben",
      "form2": "bomber",
      "form3": "bomberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vapen",
    "back": "weapon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vapenet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "vapenen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krig",
    "back": "war",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kriget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "krigen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_187",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fredsaktivist",
    "back": "peace activist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fredsaktivisten",
      "form2": "fredsaktivister",
      "form3": "fredsaktivisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_188",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förbjuda",
    "back": "ban, prohibit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förbjudaer",
      "form2": "förbjöd",
      "form3": "förbjudit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_189",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stoppa",
    "back": "stop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stoppar",
      "form2": "stoppade",
      "form3": "stoppat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_190",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "eftersom",
    "back": "because",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_191",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "farlig",
    "back": "dangerous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_192",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inspirera",
    "back": "inspire",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inspirerar",
      "form2": "inspirerade",
      "form3": "inspirerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_193",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skriva in",
    "back": "include",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skriva iner",
      "form2": "skrev",
      "form3": "skrivit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter6_194",
    "chapter": "Chapter6",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morbror",
    "back": "uncle (maternal)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "morbroder",
      "form2": "morbröder",
      "form3": "morbröderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "intervjua",
    "back": "interview",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "intervjuar",
      "form2": "intervjuade",
      "form3": "intervjuat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "shopping",
    "back": "shopping",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "doftljus",
    "back": "scented candle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "doftljuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "doftljusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krukväxt",
    "back": "potted plant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "krukväxten",
      "form2": "krukväxter",
      "form3": "krukväxterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "orkidé",
    "back": "orchid",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "orkidén",
      "form2": "orkidéer",
      "form3": "orkidéerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gardin",
    "back": "curtain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gardinen",
      "form2": "gardiner",
      "form3": "gardinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vit",
    "back": "white",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ljusgrå",
    "back": "light gray",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ha råd",
    "back": "be able to afford"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "månad",
    "back": "month",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "månaden",
      "form2": "månader",
      "form3": "månaderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kläder",
    "back": "clothes",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rea",
    "back": "sale",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rean",
      "form2": "reaor",
      "form3": "reaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "förra månaden",
    "back": "last month"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halsduk",
    "back": "scarf",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "halsduken",
      "form2": "halsdukar",
      "form3": "halsdukarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "röd",
    "back": "red",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "rött",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "handske",
    "back": "glove",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "handsken",
      "form2": "handskear",
      "form3": "handskearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tappa",
    "back": "lose",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tappar",
      "form2": "tappade",
      "form3": "tappat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "buss",
    "back": "bus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bussen",
      "form2": "bussar",
      "form3": "bussarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i går",
    "back": "yesterday"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "begagnad",
    "back": "used, second-hand",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sneakers",
    "back": "sneakers",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "redan",
    "back": "already",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättemånga",
    "back": "a huge number",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "galen",
    "back": "crazy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "garderob",
    "back": "wardrobe, closet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "garderoben",
      "form2": "garderober",
      "form3": "garderoberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "full",
    "back": "full",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "historisk",
    "back": "historical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kryssning",
    "back": "cruise",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kryssningen",
      "form2": "kryssningar",
      "form3": "kryssningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Karibien",
    "back": "the Caribbean",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spara",
    "back": "save",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sparar",
      "form2": "sparade",
      "form3": "sparat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "villa",
    "back": "villa, house",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "villan",
      "form2": "villaor",
      "form3": "villaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "förra året",
    "back": "last year"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sälja",
    "back": "sell",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "säljaer",
      "form2": "säljade",
      "form3": "säljat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ge bort",
    "back": "give away",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ge bortr",
      "form2": "gav",
      "form3": "ge borttt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "suddgummi",
    "back": "eraser",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "suddgummit",
      "form2": "suddgummin",
      "form3": "suddgummina"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "luktsuddgummi",
    "back": "scented eraser",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordgubbslukt",
    "back": "strawberry scent",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordgubbe",
    "back": "strawberry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordgubben",
      "form2": "jordgubbear",
      "form3": "jordgubbearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lukt",
    "back": "scent, smell",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "husdjur",
    "back": "pet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "husdjuret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "husdjuren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pälsdjur",
    "back": "furry animal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pälsdjuret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "pälsdjuren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "allergisk",
    "back": "allergic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ödla",
    "back": "lizard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ödlan",
      "form2": "ödlaor",
      "form3": "ödlaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lego",
    "back": "LEGO",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rum",
    "back": "room",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rummet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "rummen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tröttna",
    "back": "get tired of",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tröttnar",
      "form2": "tröttnade",
      "form3": "tröttnat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ge",
    "back": "give",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ger",
      "form2": "gav",
      "form3": "gett"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lillkusin",
    "back": "little cousin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lillkusinen",
      "form2": "lillkusiner",
      "form3": "lillkusinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "cykel",
    "back": "bicycle, bike",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "cykeln",
      "form2": "cykelar",
      "form3": "cykelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mountainbike",
    "back": "mountain bike",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mountainbiken",
      "form2": "mountainbikes",
      "form3": "mountainbikesen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spela roll",
    "back": "matter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spela rollr",
      "form2": "spela rollde",
      "form3": "spela rollt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stycke",
    "back": "paragraph",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stycket",
      "form2": "stycken",
      "form3": "styckena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låna",
    "back": "borrow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lånar",
      "form2": "lånade",
      "form3": "lånat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varuhus",
    "back": "department store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "varuhuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "varuhusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "säng",
    "back": "bed",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sängen",
      "form2": "sängar",
      "form3": "sängarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "madrass",
    "back": "mattress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "madrassen",
      "form2": "madrasser",
      "form3": "madrasserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kudde",
    "back": "pillow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kudden",
      "form2": "kuddear",
      "form3": "kuddearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lakan",
    "back": "bedsheets",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lakanet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lakanen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "duntäcke",
    "back": "down duvet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "duntäcket",
      "form2": "duntäcken",
      "form3": "duntäckena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sänglampa",
    "back": "bedside lamp",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sänglampan",
      "form2": "sänglampaor",
      "form3": "sänglampaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kastrull",
    "back": "saucepan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kastrullen",
      "form2": "kastruller",
      "form3": "kastrullerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gryta",
    "back": "pot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grytan",
      "form2": "grytaor",
      "form3": "grytaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sked",
    "back": "spoon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skeden",
      "form2": "skedar",
      "form3": "skedarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gaffel",
    "back": "fork",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gaffeln",
      "form2": "gaffelar",
      "form3": "gaffelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kniv",
    "back": "knife",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kniven",
      "form2": "knivar",
      "form3": "knivarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "flytta ihop",
    "back": "move in together"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kök",
    "back": "kitchen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "köken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "avdelning",
    "back": "department",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "avdelningen",
      "form2": "avdelningar",
      "form3": "avdelningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad kan jag hjälpa er med?",
    "back": "What can I help you with"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sova gott",
    "back": "sleep well",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sova gotter",
      "form2": "sov",
      "form3": "sova gottit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "serie",
    "back": "series",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "serien",
      "form2": "serieer",
      "form3": "serieerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "populär",
    "back": "popular",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skön",
    "back": "pleasant",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hård",
    "back": "hard",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "hårt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mjuk",
    "back": "soft",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pröva",
    "back": "test",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prövar",
      "form2": "prövade",
      "form3": "prövat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prinsessa",
    "back": "princess",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prinsessan",
      "form2": "prinsessaor",
      "form3": "prinsessaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "90-säng",
    "back": "single bed",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "90-sängen",
      "form2": "90-sängar",
      "form3": "90-sängarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ställa ihop",
    "back": "put together",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ställa ihoper",
      "form2": "ställa ihopde",
      "form3": "ställa ihopt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbelsäng",
    "back": "double bed",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dubbelsängen",
      "form2": "dubbelsängar",
      "form3": "dubbelsängarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det låter bra.",
    "back": "That sounds good"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "total",
    "back": "total",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dyr",
    "back": "expensive",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "billig",
    "back": "cheap",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bäst",
    "back": "best",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvalitet",
    "back": "quality",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvaliteten",
      "form2": "kvaliteter",
      "form3": "kvaliteterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "garanti",
    "back": "guarantee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "garantin",
      "form2": "garantier",
      "form3": "garantierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "just nu",
    "back": "right now"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "erbjudande",
    "back": "offer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "erbjudandet",
      "form2": "erbjudanden",
      "form3": "erbjudandena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "specialerbjudande",
    "back": "special offer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utan",
    "back": "without",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "extra kostnad",
    "back": "extra cost"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "egyptisk",
    "back": "Egyptian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bomull",
    "back": "cotton",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "halva priset",
    "back": "half price"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fundera",
    "back": "think",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "funderar",
      "form2": "funderade",
      "form3": "funderat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köksgrejer",
    "back": "kitchen stuff",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köksavdelning",
    "back": "kitchen department",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köksavdelningen",
      "form2": "köksavdelningar",
      "form3": "köksavdelningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "superfin",
    "back": "super nice, very beautiful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pasta",
    "back": "pasta",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snygg",
    "back": "nice, attractive",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köttfärssås",
    "back": "Bolognese",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köttfärssåsen",
      "form2": "köttfärssåser",
      "form3": "köttfärssåserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mellanstorlek",
    "back": "medium size",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mellanstorleken",
      "form2": "mellanstorlekar",
      "form3": "mellanstorlekarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bestick",
    "back": "cutlery",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "besticket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "besticken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "här borta",
    "back": "over here"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "räcka",
    "back": "be enough",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "räckaer",
      "form2": "räckate",
      "form3": "räckat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur ska vi göra med ...?",
    "back": "What should we do about ..."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sova på saken",
    "back": "sleep on it"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "schema",
    "back": "schedule",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "schemat",
      "form2": "scheman",
      "form3": "schemana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jämföra",
    "back": "compare",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jämförar",
      "form2": "jämförade",
      "form3": "jämförat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plagg",
    "back": "piece of clothing, garment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "plagget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "plaggen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ett par byxor",
    "back": "a pair of pants"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jacka",
    "back": "jacket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jackan",
      "form2": "jackaor",
      "form3": "jackaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trosor",
    "back": "women’s underwear",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kalsonger",
    "back": "men’s underwear",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kjol",
    "back": "skirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kjolen",
      "form2": "kjolar",
      "form3": "kjolarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slips",
    "back": "tie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slipsen",
      "form2": "slipsar",
      "form3": "slipsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ett par skor",
    "back": "a pair of shoes"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bh",
    "back": "bra",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bh:n",
      "form2": "bh:ar",
      "form3": "bh:arna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kavaj",
    "back": "suit jacket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kavajen",
      "form2": "kavajer",
      "form3": "kavajerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skjorta",
    "back": "shirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skjortan",
      "form2": "skjortaor",
      "form3": "skjortaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stickad tröja",
    "back": "knitted sweater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stickad tröjan",
      "form2": "stickad tröjaor",
      "form3": "stickad tröjaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strumpa",
    "back": "sock",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "strumpan",
      "form2": "strumpaor",
      "form3": "strumpaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "linne",
    "back": "tank top, camisole",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "linnet",
      "form2": "linnen",
      "form3": "linnena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "t-shirt",
    "back": "t-shirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "t-shirten",
      "form2": "t-shirtar",
      "form3": "t-shirtarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kappa",
    "back": "coat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kappan",
      "form2": "kappaor",
      "form3": "kappaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klänning",
    "back": "dress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klänningen",
      "form2": "klänningar",
      "form3": "klänningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kofta",
    "back": "cardigan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "koftan",
      "form2": "koftaor",
      "form3": "koftaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoodie / luvtröja",
    "back": "hoodie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hoodie / luvtröjan",
      "form2": "hoodie / luvtröjaor",
      "form3": "hoodie / luvtröjaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pyjamas",
    "back": "pyjamas",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pyjamasen",
      "form2": "pyjamaser",
      "form3": "pyjamaserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färg",
    "back": "color",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färgen",
      "form2": "färger",
      "form3": "färgerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "monster",
    "back": "monster",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "monsterret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "monsterren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blå",
    "back": "blue",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vit",
    "back": "white",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grön",
    "back": "green",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grå",
    "back": "grey",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "orange",
    "back": "orange",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "–",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gul",
    "back": "yellow",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brun",
    "back": "brown",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svart",
    "back": "black",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rosa",
    "back": "pink",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prickig",
    "back": "spotted, polka-dot",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blommig",
    "back": "floral",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "randig",
    "back": "striped",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rutig",
    "back": "checkered",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mönstrad",
    "back": "patterned",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motsats",
    "back": "opposite",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "motsatsen",
      "form2": "motsatser",
      "form3": "motsatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bred",
    "back": "wide",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "brett",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjock",
    "back": "fat",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ljus",
    "back": "light",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "modern",
    "back": "modern",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "omodern",
    "back": "outdated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smal",
    "back": "thin",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ful",
    "back": "ugly",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vad har du på dig i dag?",
    "back": "What are you wearing today"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "öppet köp",
    "back": "refund policy"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur mycket får de kosta?",
    "back": "How much can they cost"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Passar de bra?",
    "back": "Do they fit well"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "passa",
    "back": "fit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "passar",
      "form2": "passade",
      "form3": "passat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur mycket kostar den?",
    "back": "How much does it cost"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "en storlek mindre",
    "back": "one size smaller"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vilken storlek har du?",
    "back": "What size are you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Vill du ha hjälp?",
    "back": "Would you like some help"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kan jag hjälpa till?",
    "back": "Can I help you"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prova",
    "back": "try",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "provar",
      "form2": "provade",
      "form3": "provat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ett ögonblick",
    "back": "one moment"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "provrum",
    "back": "fitting room",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "provrummet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "provrummen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "för stora",
    "back": "too large"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bytesrätt",
    "back": "right to exchange",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bytesrätten",
      "form2": "bytesrätter",
      "form3": "bytesrätterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ögonskugga",
    "back": "eye shadow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ögonskuggan",
      "form2": "ögonskuggaor",
      "form3": "ögonskuggaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "då ska vi se",
    "back": "let’s see"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "medlem",
    "back": "member",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "medlemmen",
      "form2": "medlemmar",
      "form3": "medlemmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag tittar bara.",
    "back": "I’m just looking"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Säg till om du behöver hjälp.",
    "back": "Let me know if you need help"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "löparsko",
    "back": "running shoe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "löparskon",
      "form2": "löparskor",
      "form3": "löparskorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kan du hjälpa mig?",
    "back": "Can you help me"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "springa",
    "back": "run",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "springaer",
      "form2": "sprang",
      "form3": "sprungit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skog",
    "back": "forest",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skogen",
      "form2": "skogar",
      "form3": "skogarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "asfalt",
    "back": "asphalt",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "löpband",
    "back": "treadmill",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "löpbandet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "löpbanden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Sitter de bra?",
    "back": "Do they fit well"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konsumentfakta",
    "back": "consumer information",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lämna tillbaka",
    "back": "return",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lämna tillbakar",
      "form2": "lämna tillbakaade",
      "form3": "lämna tillbakat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komparation",
    "back": "comparison",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komparativ",
    "back": "comparative",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "superlativ",
    "back": "superlative",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_187",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kort",
    "back": "short",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_188",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tält",
    "back": "tent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tältet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tälten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_189",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "prata engelska",
    "back": "speak English"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_190",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag läser svenska.",
    "back": "I study Swedish"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_191",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tio",
    "back": "ten",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_192",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "liter",
    "back": "liter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "litern",
      "form2": "litrar",
      "form3": "litrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_193",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "närbutik",
    "back": "local grocery store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "närbutikn",
      "form2": "närbutiker",
      "form3": "närbutikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_194",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "herre",
    "back": "gentleman, man",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "herren",
      "form2": "herrear",
      "form3": "herrearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_195",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gym",
    "back": "gym",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gymmet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "gymmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_196",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skylt",
    "back": "sign",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skylten",
      "form2": "skyltar",
      "form3": "skyltarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_197",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kål",
    "back": "cabbage",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_198",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kär",
    "back": "in love",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_199",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skål",
    "back": "bowl",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skålen",
      "form2": "skålar",
      "form3": "skålarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_200",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skär",
    "back": "pink",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_201",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjuksköterska",
    "back": "nurse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjuksköterskan",
      "form2": "sjuksköterskaor",
      "form3": "sjuksköterskaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_202",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köp",
    "back": "buy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köpet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "köpen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_203",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "resväska",
    "back": "suitcase",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "resväskan",
      "form2": "resväskaor",
      "form3": "resväskaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_204",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lätt",
    "back": "light",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_205",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "neongrön",
    "back": "neon green",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_206",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bagage",
    "back": "luggage",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bagaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bagageen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_207",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bagageband",
    "back": "baggage carousel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bagagebandet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bagagebanden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter7_208",
    "chapter": "Chapter7",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "guld",
    "back": "gold",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "första gången",
    "back": "first time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Storbritannien",
    "back": "the United Kingdom",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kultur",
    "back": "culture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kulturen",
      "form2": "kulturer",
      "form3": "kulturerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väder",
    "back": "weather",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vädret",
      "form2": "väder",
      "form3": "vädren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väderprognos",
    "back": "weather forecast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "väderprognosen",
      "form2": "väderprognoser",
      "form3": "väderprognoserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "växlande väder",
    "back": "changing weather"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regn",
    "back": "rain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "regnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "regnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "packa",
    "back": "pack",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "packar",
      "form2": "packade",
      "form3": "packat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarkläder",
    "back": "summer clothes",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "träningskläder",
    "back": "sportswear",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regnjacka",
    "back": "raincoat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "regnjackan",
      "form2": "regnjackaor",
      "form3": "regnjackaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gummistövel",
    "back": "rubber boot, Wellington boot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gummistöveln",
      "form2": "gummistövelar",
      "form3": "gummistövelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varm tröja",
    "back": "warm sweater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "varm tröjan",
      "form2": "varm tröjaor",
      "form3": "varm tröjaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "myggmedel",
    "back": "mosquito repellent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "myggmedlet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "myggmedlen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förstås",
    "back": "of course",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "juli",
    "back": "July",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hemma hos",
    "back": "at the home of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forum",
    "back": "forum",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forumet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "forumen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mitt i stan",
    "back": "in the middle of the city, downtown",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "staden"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åka (-er, åkte, åkt) runt",
    "back": "travel around",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå på museum",
    "back": "go to a museum"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ABBA-museet",
    "back": "The ABBA Museum",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "promenera (-r, -de, -t) i ...",
    "back": "take a walk in .."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båt",
    "back": "boat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "båten",
      "form2": "båtar",
      "form3": "båtarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båttur",
    "back": "boat tour",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "båtturen",
      "form2": "båtturer",
      "form3": "båtturerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skärgård",
    "back": "archipelago",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skärgården",
      "form2": "skärgårdar",
      "form3": "skärgårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prinsesstårta",
    "back": "Princess cake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prinsesstårtan",
      "form2": "prinsesstårtaor",
      "form3": "prinsesstårtaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "designprylar",
    "back": "design stuff",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Moderna museet",
    "back": "Museum of Modern Art"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Fotografiska",
    "back": "Fotografiska Museum",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dansmusik",
    "back": "dance music",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Djurgården",
    "back": "Djurgården (district in Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köttbulle",
    "back": "meatball",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "köttbullar",
        "köttbullarna"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "potatismos",
    "back": "mashed potatoes",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sylt",
    "back": "jam, preserves",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lingonsylt",
    "back": "lingonberry preserves",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "att göra-lista",
    "back": "to-do list"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "borde",
    "back": "should",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "information",
    "back": "information",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tänk dig att",
    "back": "imagine that"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "besöka",
    "back": "visit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "besökaer",
      "form2": "besökate",
      "form3": "besökat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "presens perfekt",
    "back": "present perfect"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "supinum",
    "back": "supine",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varannan",
    "back": "every other",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "beskriva",
    "back": "describe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "beskrivaer",
      "form2": "beskrev",
      "form3": "beskrivit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bädda",
    "back": "make the bed",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bäddar",
      "form2": "bäddade",
      "form3": "bäddat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släcka",
    "back": "turn off",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släckaer",
      "form2": "släckate",
      "form3": "släckat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "karaoke",
    "back": "karaoke",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "någon gång",
    "back": "some time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "karaokebar",
    "back": "karaoke bar",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "karaokebaren",
      "form2": "karaokebarer",
      "form3": "karaokebarerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Malmö",
    "back": "Malmö",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur var den/det/de?",
    "back": "How was it / were they"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nervös",
    "back": "nervous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "supernervös",
    "back": "super nervous",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låt",
    "back": "song",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "låten",
      "form2": "låtar",
      "form3": "låtarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "främling",
    "back": "stranger",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "främlingen",
      "form2": "främlingar",
      "form3": "främlingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "applåd",
    "back": "applause",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "applåden",
      "form2": "applåder",
      "form3": "applåderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smaka",
    "back": "taste",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smakar",
      "form2": "smakade",
      "form3": "smakat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i somras",
    "back": "last summer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "varför inte",
    "back": "why not"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättekonstig",
    "back": "really strange",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "salt",
    "back": "salty",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hoppa fallskärm",
    "back": "go skydiving"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "för ... år sedan",
    "back": "... years ago"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i present",
    "back": "as a gift"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoppa",
    "back": "jump",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hoppar",
      "form2": "hoppade",
      "form3": "hoppat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rädd",
    "back": "afraid",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "modig",
    "back": "brave",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dansa (-r, -ade, -t) tango",
    "back": "dance tango",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ex",
    "back": "ex (boyfriend, girlfriend)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "exet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "exen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "danskurs",
    "back": "dance course",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "danskursen",
      "form2": "danskurser",
      "form3": "danskurserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Grattis!",
    "back": "Congratulations"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pseudolån",
    "back": "pseudo-loan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pseudolånet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "pseudolånen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uttryck",
    "back": "expression",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "uttrycket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "uttrycken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "finnas",
    "back": "exist, be present",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "finns",
      "form2": "fanns",
      "form3": "funnits"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidpunkt",
    "back": "point in time",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidpunkten",
      "form2": "tidpunkter",
      "form3": "tidpunkterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidsperiod",
    "back": "period",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidsperioden",
      "form2": "tidsperioder",
      "form3": "tidsperioderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "specifik",
    "back": "specific",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "adverb",
    "back": "adverb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "adverbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "adverben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "åka vattenskidor",
    "back": "water skiing"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rida",
    "back": "ride",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ridaer",
      "form2": "red",
      "form3": "ridit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "måla graffiti",
    "back": "paint graffiti"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "springa maraton",
    "back": "run a marathon"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "segla",
    "back": "sail",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "seglar",
      "form2": "seglade",
      "form3": "seglat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helikopter",
    "back": "helicopter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "helikoptern",
      "form2": "helikopterar",
      "form3": "helikopterarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tälta",
    "back": "go camping (in a tent)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tältar",
      "form2": "tältaade",
      "form3": "tältat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vinterbada",
    "back": "ice swimming",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vinterbadar",
      "form2": "vinterbadade",
      "form3": "vinterbadat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hälsning",
    "back": "greeting",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hälsningen",
      "form2": "hälsningar",
      "form3": "hälsningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skina",
    "back": "shine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skinaer",
      "form2": "sken",
      "form3": "skinit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regna",
    "back": "rain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "regnar",
      "form2": "regnade",
      "form3": "regnat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hela dagen",
    "back": "all day"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "augusti",
    "back": "August",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "starta",
    "back": "start",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "startar",
      "form2": "startade",
      "form3": "startat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "destination",
    "back": "destination",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "destinationen",
      "form2": "destinationer",
      "form3": "destinationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "förra veckan",
    "back": "last week"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ordningstal",
    "back": "ordinal numbers",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ordningstalet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "ordningstalen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjätte",
    "back": "sixth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjunde",
    "back": "seventh",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åttonde",
    "back": "eighth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nionde",
    "back": "ninth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tionde",
    "back": "tenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elfte",
    "back": "eleventh",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tolfte",
    "back": "twelfth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trettonde",
    "back": "thirteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjortonde",
    "back": "fourteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "femtonde",
    "back": "fifteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sextonde",
    "back": "sixteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjuttonde",
    "back": "seventeenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "artonde",
    "back": "eighteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nittonde",
    "back": "nineteenth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjugonde",
    "back": "twentieth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjugoförsta",
    "back": "twenty-first",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjugoandra",
    "back": "twenty-second",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trettionde",
    "back": "thirtieth",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trettioförsta",
    "back": "thirty-first",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "januari",
    "back": "January",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "februari",
    "back": "February",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mars",
    "back": "March",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "april",
    "back": "April",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "maj",
    "back": "May",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "juni",
    "back": "June",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "juli",
    "back": "July",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter8_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter8",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "aug",
    "back": "nan",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "transport",
    "back": "transport",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "transporten",
      "form2": "transporter",
      "form3": "transporterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "app",
    "back": "app",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "appen",
      "form2": "appar",
      "form3": "apparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "checka (-r, -de, -t) in",
    "back": "check in",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flyg",
    "back": "flight",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flyget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "flygen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flygplats",
    "back": "airport",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flygplatsen",
      "form2": "flygplatser",
      "form3": "flygplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färja",
    "back": "ferry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färjan",
      "form2": "färjor",
      "form3": "färjorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färjeterminal",
    "back": "ferry terminal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färjeterminalen",
      "form2": "färjeterminaler",
      "form3": "färjeterminalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hållplats",
    "back": "bus stop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hållplatsen",
      "form2": "hållplatser",
      "form3": "hållplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "restaurangvagn",
    "back": "restaurant carriage, dining car",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "restaurangvagnen",
      "form2": "restaurangvagnar",
      "form3": "restaurangvagnarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "säkerhetskontroll",
    "back": "security check",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "säkerhetskontrollen",
      "form2": "säkerhetskontroller",
      "form3": "säkerhetskontrollerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spår",
    "back": "rail",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spåret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "spåren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tåg",
    "back": "train",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tåget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tågen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vagn",
    "back": "carriage",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vagnen",
      "form2": "vagnar",
      "form3": "vagnarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "När går tåget?",
    "back": "When does the train leave? / When is the train scheduled"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Centralen",
    "back": "the Central Station",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "byta buss",
    "back": "change buses, transfer buses"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tvåa buss",
    "back": "number 2 bus"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fyra buss",
    "back": "number 4 bus"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åtta",
    "back": "eight",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ladda (-r, -de, -t) ner",
    "back": "download",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "När går flyget?",
    "back": "When does the flight depart? / When is the flight scheduled"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lämna (-r, -de, -t) in",
    "back": "submit, hand in",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta (-r, tog, tagit) lång tid",
    "back": "take a long time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "koppla (-r, -de, -t) av",
    "back": "relax",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gate",
    "back": "gate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gaten",
      "form2": "gater",
      "form3": "gaterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hemifrån",
    "back": "from home",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidig",
    "back": "early",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tjoho!",
    "back": "Woohoo! / Yay"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Helsingfors",
    "back": "Helsinki",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fot",
    "back": "foot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "foten",
      "form2": "fötter",
      "form3": "fötterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fordon",
    "back": "vehicle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fordonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fordonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidtabell",
    "back": "timetable, schedule",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidtabellen",
      "form2": "tidtabeller",
      "form3": "tidtabellerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rutt",
    "back": "route",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rutten",
      "form2": "rutter",
      "form3": "rutterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "informell",
    "back": "informal",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "det är ganska långt",
    "back": "it’s quite far"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma (-er, kom, kommit) in till/på",
    "back": "arrive at",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "station",
    "back": "station",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stationen",
      "form2": "stationer",
      "form3": "stationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nästa",
    "back": "next",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försenad",
    "back": "delayed",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "anslutningsbuss",
    "back": "connecting bus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "anslutningsbussen",
      "form2": "anslutningsbussar",
      "form3": "anslutningsbussarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vänta",
    "back": "wait",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "väntar",
      "form2": "väntade",
      "form3": "väntat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flygbuss",
    "back": "airport bus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flygbussen",
      "form2": "flygbussar",
      "form3": "flygbussarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Arlanda",
    "back": "Arlanda (international airport near Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framme",
    "back": "arrived",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "terminal",
    "back": "terminal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "terminalen",
      "form2": "terminaler",
      "form3": "terminalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inställd",
    "back": "canceled",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kanal",
    "back": "canal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kanalen",
      "form2": "kanaler",
      "form3": "kanalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klass",
    "back": "class",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klassen",
      "form2": "klasser",
      "form3": "klasserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "våning",
    "back": "floor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "våningen",
      "form2": "våningar",
      "form3": "våningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå i tvåan",
    "back": "be in second grade"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjua",
    "back": "seventh grade",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nia",
    "back": "ninth grade",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hiss",
    "back": "elevator, lift",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hissen",
      "form2": "hissar",
      "form3": "hissarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "torg",
    "back": "square",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "torget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "torgen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "partikelverb",
    "back": "phrasal verb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "partikelverbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "partikelverben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "partikel",
    "back": "particle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "partikeln",
      "form2": "partikellar",
      "form3": "partikellarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "obetonad",
    "back": "unstressed",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betonad",
    "back": "emphasized",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "verbpartikel",
    "back": "verb particle",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma (-er, kom, kommit) ihåg",
    "back": "remember",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Krya på dig!",
    "back": "Get well"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gå (-r, gick, gått) av",
    "back": "get off",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jul",
    "back": "Christmas",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "julen",
      "form2": "jular",
      "form3": "jularna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glass",
    "back": "ice cream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glassen",
      "form2": "glassar",
      "form3": "glassarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunnelbana",
    "back": "subway, metro",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tunnelbanan",
      "form2": "tunnelbanaor",
      "form3": "tunnelbanaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bilresa",
    "back": "car trip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilresan",
      "form2": "bilresaor",
      "form3": "bilresaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hotell",
    "back": "hotel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hotellet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hotellen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "cykla",
    "back": "bike",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "cyklar",
      "form2": "cyklade",
      "form3": "cyklat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pendeltåg",
    "back": "commuter train",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pendeltåget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "pendeltågen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hur kommer vi till ...?",
    "back": "How do we get to ..."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bageri",
    "back": "bakery",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bageriet",
      "form2": "bagerier",
      "form3": "bagerierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skoaffär",
    "back": "shoe store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skoaffären",
      "form2": "skoaffärer",
      "form3": "skoaffärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bokhandel",
    "back": "bookstore",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bokhandeln",
      "form2": "bokhandellar",
      "form3": "bokhandellarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yogastudio",
    "back": "yoga studio",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "yogastudion",
      "form2": "yogastudior",
      "form3": "yogastudiorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sushirestaurang",
    "back": "sushi restaurant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sushirestaurangen",
      "form2": "sushirestauranger",
      "form3": "sushirestaurangerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "optiker",
    "back": "optician",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "optikern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "optikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klädbutik",
    "back": "clothing store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klädbutiken",
      "form2": "klädbutiker",
      "form3": "klädbutikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korvkiosk",
    "back": "hot dog stand",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "korvkiosken",
      "form2": "korvkiosker",
      "form3": "korvkioskerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elektronikaffär",
    "back": "electronics store",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "elektronikaffären",
      "form2": "elektronikaffärer",
      "form3": "elektronikaffärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kiosk",
    "back": "kiosk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kiosken",
      "form2": "kiosker",
      "form3": "kioskerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kyrka",
    "back": "church",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kyrkan",
      "form2": "kyrkaor",
      "form3": "kyrkaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blomsterhandel",
    "back": "flower shop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blomsterhandeln",
      "form2": "blomsterhandellar",
      "form3": "blomsterhandellarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "preposition",
    "back": "preposition",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prepositionen",
      "form2": "prepositioner",
      "form3": "prepositionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korsning",
    "back": "intersection, crossroads",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "korsningen",
      "form2": "korsningar",
      "form3": "korsningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mittemot",
    "back": "opposite",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "mellan ... och",
    "back": "between ... and"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vänster sida",
    "back": "on the left-hand side"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trafikljus",
    "back": "traffic light",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trafikljuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "trafikljusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "längs",
    "back": "along",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "å",
    "back": "river",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ån",
      "form2": "åar",
      "form3": "åarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "övergångsställe",
    "back": "crosswalk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "övergångsstället",
      "form2": "övergångsställen",
      "form3": "övergångsställena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gå (-r, gick, gått) över gatan",
    "back": "cross the street",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rondell",
    "back": "roundabout",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rondellen",
      "form2": "rondeller",
      "form3": "rondellerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "busshållplats",
    "back": "bus stop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "busshållplatsen",
      "form2": "busshållplatser",
      "form3": "busshållplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "resa",
    "back": "trip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "resan",
      "form2": "resaor",
      "form3": "resaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vandra",
    "back": "hike",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vandrar",
      "form2": "vandrade",
      "form3": "vandrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjäll",
    "back": "mountain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fjället",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fjällen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "närmare",
    "back": "closer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kolla (-r, -de, -t) upp",
    "back": "look up",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "västkust",
    "back": "west coast",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strand",
    "back": "beach",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stranden",
      "form2": "stränder",
      "form3": "stränderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Skåne",
    "back": "Skåne (southern Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Siljan",
    "back": "Siljan Lake",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Dalarna",
    "back": "Dalarna (region in central Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "festa",
    "back": "party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "festar",
      "form2": "festade",
      "form3": "festat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Umeå",
    "back": "Umeå",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Göteborg",
    "back": "Gothenburg",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "om 10 dagar",
    "back": "in 10 days"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "en dryg vecka",
    "back": "a little over a week"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i så fall",
    "back": "in that case"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "guide",
    "back": "guide",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "guiden",
      "form2": "guideer",
      "form3": "guideerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyhet",
    "back": "news",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nyheten",
      "form2": "nyheter",
      "form3": "nyheterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontakt",
    "back": "contact",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kontakten",
      "form2": "kontakter",
      "form3": "kontakterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "storstad",
    "back": "big city",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "storstaden",
      "form2": "storstäder",
      "form3": "storstäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjö",
    "back": "lake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjön",
      "form2": "sjöar",
      "form3": "sjöarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta (-r, tog, tagit) ett dopp",
    "back": "take a dip, have a swim",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bad",
    "back": "swimming spot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "badet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "baden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Vänern",
    "back": "Vänern (largest lake in Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Vättern",
    "back": "Vättern (second largest lake in Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Halland",
    "back": "Halland (region in southwestern Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ö",
    "back": "island",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ön",
      "form2": "öar",
      "form3": "öarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Öland",
    "back": "Öland (island in the Baltic Sea)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "norra",
    "back": "northern",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utanför",
    "back": "outside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Luleå",
    "back": "Luleå",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sand",
    "back": "sand",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sanden",
      "form2": "sandar",
      "form3": "sandarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tå",
    "back": "toe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tån",
      "form2": "tår",
      "form3": "tårna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klippa",
    "back": "rock",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klippan",
      "form2": "klippaor",
      "form3": "klippaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Bohuslän",
    "back": "Bohuslän (region in southwestern Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Blekinge",
    "back": "Blekinge (region in southern Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "puls",
    "back": "pulse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pulsen",
      "form2": "pulsar",
      "form3": "pulsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mysig",
    "back": "cozy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "småstad",
    "back": "small town",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "småstaden",
      "form2": "småstäder",
      "form3": "småstäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stadssafari",
    "back": "city safari",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stadssafarin",
      "form2": "stadssafarier",
      "form3": "stadssafarierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kallbadhus",
    "back": "cold bath facility",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kallbadhuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kallbadhusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snabb",
    "back": "quick",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "enkel",
    "back": "simple",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "enkla"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Köpenhamn",
    "back": "Copenhagen",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvudstad",
    "back": "capital city",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudstaden",
      "form2": "huvudstäder",
      "form3": "huvudstäderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färsk",
    "back": "fresh",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "räka",
    "back": "shrimp",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "räkan",
      "form2": "räkaor",
      "form3": "räkaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nöjespark",
    "back": "amusement park",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nöjesparken",
      "form2": "nöjesparker",
      "form3": "nöjesparkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Avenyn",
    "back": "Avenyn (street in Gothenburg)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nattklubb",
    "back": "nightclub",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nattklubben",
      "form2": "nattklubbar",
      "form3": "nattklubbarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Drottninggatan",
    "back": "Drottninggatan (street in Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Stureplan",
    "back": "Stureplan (square in Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Skånegatan",
    "back": "Skånegatan (street in Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Skeppsholmen",
    "back": "Skeppsholmen (island in Stockholm)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ringmur",
    "back": "city wall, ring wall",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ringmuren",
      "form2": "ringmurar",
      "form3": "ringmurarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "medeltid",
    "back": "Middle Ages",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "medeltiden",
      "form2": "medeltider",
      "form3": "medeltiderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kyrkby",
    "back": "church village",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kyrkbyn",
      "form2": "kyrkbyar",
      "form3": "kyrkbyarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utsikt",
    "back": "view",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utsikten",
      "form2": "utsikter",
      "form3": "utsikterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "frisk luft",
    "back": "fresh air"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Lappland",
    "back": "Lapland",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vandringsled",
    "back": "hiking trail",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vandringsleden",
      "form2": "vandringsleder",
      "form3": "vandringslederna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjällstation",
    "back": "mountain station",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fjällstationen",
      "form2": "fjällstationer",
      "form3": "fjällstationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dagstur",
    "back": "day trip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dagsturen",
      "form2": "dagsturer",
      "form3": "dagsturerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nybörjare",
    "back": "beginner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nybörjaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "nybörjarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Höga kusten",
    "back": "High Coast"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunnelbanestation",
    "back": "subway station",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tunnelbanestationen",
      "form2": "tunnelbanestationer",
      "form3": "tunnelbanestationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bildgoogla",
    "back": "image search",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bildgooglar",
      "form2": "bildgooglade",
      "form3": "bildgooglat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på kartan",
    "back": "on the map"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "generell",
    "back": "general",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidspreposition",
    "back": "preposition of time",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidsprepositionen",
      "form2": "tidsprepositioner",
      "form3": "tidsprepositionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rast",
    "back": "break",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rasten",
      "form2": "raster",
      "form3": "rasterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "landskap",
    "back": "landscape",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "landskapet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "landskapen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "region",
    "back": "region",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "regionen",
      "form2": "regioner",
      "form3": "regionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vandrarhem",
    "back": "hostel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vandrarhemmet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "vandrarhemmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stavning",
    "back": "spelling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stavningen",
      "form2": "stavningar",
      "form3": "stavningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forskning",
    "back": "research",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forskningen",
      "form2": "forskningar",
      "form3": "forskningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skinka",
    "back": "ham",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skinkan",
      "form2": "skinkaor",
      "form3": "skinkaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "meddelande",
    "back": "message",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "meddelanden",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "meddelandena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skapa",
    "back": "create",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skapar",
      "form2": "skapade",
      "form3": "skapat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tråd",
    "back": "thread",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tråden",
      "form2": "trådar",
      "form3": "trådarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rundresa",
    "back": "circular trip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rundresan",
      "form2": "rundresaor",
      "form3": "rundresaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "älskling",
    "back": "darling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "älsklingen",
      "form2": "älsklingar",
      "form3": "älsklingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tillbaka",
    "back": "back",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Självklart!",
    "back": "Of course"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kram!",
    "back": "Hugs"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leka",
    "back": "play",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lekaer",
      "form2": "lekate",
      "form3": "lekat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "granne",
    "back": "neighbor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grannen",
      "form2": "grannear",
      "form3": "grannearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "puss",
    "back": "kiss",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pussen",
      "form2": "pussar",
      "form3": "pussarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flyga",
    "back": "fly",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flygaer",
      "form2": "flög",
      "form3": "flugit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vattna (-r, -de, -t) blommor",
    "back": "water the flowers",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "underlag",
    "back": "reference",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "underlaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "underlagen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter9_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter9",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vart",
    "back": "where to",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veta",
    "back": "know",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vet",
      "form2": "visste",
      "form3": "vetat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "platt",
    "back": "flat",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kustlinje",
    "back": "coastline",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kustlinjen",
      "form2": "kustlinjeer",
      "form3": "kustlinjeerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yta",
    "back": "surface",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ytan",
      "form2": "ytaor",
      "form3": "ytaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tätbefolkad",
    "back": "densely populated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ursprungsfolk",
    "back": "indigenous people",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ursprungsfolket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "ursprungsfolken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gräns",
    "back": "border",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gränsen",
      "form2": "gränser",
      "form3": "gränserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordbruk",
    "back": "agriculture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordbruket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "jordbruken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fattig",
    "back": "poor",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetskraft",
    "back": "manpower",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ändra",
    "back": "change",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ändrar",
      "form2": "ändrade",
      "form3": "ändrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flykting",
    "back": "refugee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "flyktingen",
      "form2": "flyktingar",
      "form3": "flyktingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "söka (-er, -te, -t) asyl",
    "back": "apply for asylum",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "asyl",
    "back": "asylum",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "asylen",
      "form2": "asyler",
      "form3": "asylerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "järn",
    "back": "iron",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "järnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "järnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stål",
    "back": "steel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stålet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "stålen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skandinavisk",
    "back": "Scandinavian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "polcirkel",
    "back": "Arctic Circle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "polcirkeln",
      "form2": "polcirklar",
      "form3": "polcirklarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "genom",
    "back": "through",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "södra",
    "back": "southern",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordbruksmark",
    "back": "farmland",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordbruksmarken",
      "form2": "jordbruksmarker",
      "form3": "jordbruksmarkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "procent",
    "back": "percent",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skogsmark",
    "back": "woodland",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skogsmarken",
      "form2": "skogsmarker",
      "form3": "skogsmarkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Östersjön",
    "back": "Baltic Sea",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blandning",
    "back": "mixture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blandningen",
      "form2": "blandningar",
      "form3": "blandningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sötvatten",
    "back": "freshwater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sötvattennet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sötvattennen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "saltvatten",
    "back": "saltwater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "saltvattennet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "saltvattennen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bräckt vatten",
    "back": "brackish water"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "människa",
    "back": "human, person",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "människan",
      "form2": "människor",
      "form3": "människorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kommunal",
    "back": "municipal",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glesbefolkad",
    "back": "sparsely populated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "invånare",
    "back": "resident, population",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "invånaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "invånarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvadratkilometer",
    "back": "square kilometer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvadratkilometern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kvadratkilometrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "same",
    "back": "Sami person",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "samen",
      "form2": "samer",
      "form3": "samerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samiska",
    "back": "Sami / Saami",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "parlament",
    "back": "parliament",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "parlamentet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "parlamenten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Tornedalen",
    "back": "Tornedalen (region along the Swedish–Finnish border)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tornedaling",
    "back": "Tornedalian",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tornedalingen",
      "form2": "tornedalingar",
      "form3": "tornedalingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "meänkieli",
    "back": "Meänkieli (Finnish dialect in northern Sweden)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvudspråk",
    "back": "main language",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudspråket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "huvudspråken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "officiell",
    "back": "official",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "internationell",
    "back": "international",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sammanhang",
    "back": "context",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sammanhanget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sammanhangen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jiddisch",
    "back": "Yiddish",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "romska",
    "back": "Romani",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nationell",
    "back": "national",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minoritetsspråk",
    "back": "minority language",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minoritetsspråket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "minoritetsspråken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "förr i tiden",
    "back": "the olden days"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordbruksland",
    "back": "farmland country",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordbrukslandet",
      "form2": "jordbruksländer",
      "form3": "jordbruksländerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svensk",
    "back": "Swede",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svensken",
      "form2": "svenskar",
      "form3": "svenskarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "emigrera",
    "back": "emigrate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "emigrerar",
      "form2": "emigrerade",
      "form3": "emigrerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mest",
    "back": "mostly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Nordamerika",
    "back": "North America",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "industri",
    "back": "industry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "industrin",
      "form2": "industrier",
      "form3": "industrierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "växa",
    "back": "grow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "växaer",
      "form2": "växate",
      "form3": "växat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "därför",
    "back": "therefore",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nordisk",
    "back": "Nordic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Sydeuropa",
    "back": "Southern Europe",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "1960-talet",
    "back": "the 1960s",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbeta",
    "back": "work",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetar",
      "form2": "arbetade",
      "form3": "arbetat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inom",
    "back": "within",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sämre",
    "back": "worse",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "politik",
    "back": "politics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "invandring",
    "back": "immigration",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samtidig",
    "back": "at the same time",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Latinamerika",
    "back": "Latin America",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Mellanöstern",
    "back": "Middle East",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "forna Jugoslavien",
    "back": "former Yugoslavia"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "EU-medborgare",
    "back": "EU citizen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "EU-medborgaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "EU-medborgarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "femtedel",
    "back": "a fifth",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "femtedelen",
      "form2": "femtedelar",
      "form3": "femtedelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högutbildad",
    "back": "highly educated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "it-specialist",
    "back": "IT specialist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "it-specialisten",
      "form2": "it-specialister",
      "form3": "it-specialisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "säsongsarbetare",
    "back": "seasonal worker",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "säsongsarbetaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "säsongsarbetarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plocka",
    "back": "pick",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "plockar",
      "form2": "plockade",
      "form3": "plockat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "export",
    "back": "export",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "exporten",
      "form2": "exporter",
      "form3": "exporterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "exportera",
    "back": "export",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "exporterar",
      "form2": "exporterade",
      "form3": "exporterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trä",
    "back": "wood",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pappersmassa",
    "back": "wood pulp",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pappersmassan",
      "form2": "pappersmassor",
      "form3": "pappersmassorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "även",
    "back": "even",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lastbil",
    "back": "truck",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lastbilen",
      "form2": "lastbilar",
      "form3": "lastbilarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läkemedel",
    "back": "medicine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läkemedelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "läkemedelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "maskin",
    "back": "machine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "maskinen",
      "form2": "maskiner",
      "form3": "maskinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "produkt",
    "back": "product",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "produkten",
      "form2": "produkter",
      "form3": "produkterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjänst",
    "back": "service",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tjänsten",
      "form2": "tjänster",
      "form3": "tjänsterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "telekom",
    "back": "telecommunications",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mobiltelefoni",
    "back": "mobile technology",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "musikindustri",
    "back": "music industry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "musikindustrin",
      "form2": "musikindustrier",
      "form3": "musikindustrierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "artist",
    "back": "artist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "artisten",
      "form2": "artister",
      "form3": "artisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utomlands",
    "back": "abroad",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låtskrivare",
    "back": "songwriter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "låtskrivaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "låtskrivarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "producent",
    "back": "producer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "producenten",
      "form2": "producenter",
      "form3": "producenterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sektor",
    "back": "sector",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sektorn",
      "form2": "sektorer",
      "form3": "sektorerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "databranschen",
    "back": "the IT industry",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mobilspelbranschen",
    "back": "the mobile gaming industry",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spel",
    "back": "game",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spelet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "spelen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utveckla",
    "back": "develop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utvecklar",
      "form2": "utvecklade",
      "form3": "utvecklat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spelföretag",
    "back": "gaming company",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spelföretaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "spelföretagen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minoritet",
    "back": "minority",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minoriteten",
      "form2": "minoriteter",
      "form3": "minoriteterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sverigefinne",
    "back": "Sweden Finn",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sverigefinnen",
      "form2": "sverigefinnear",
      "form3": "sverigefinnearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jude",
    "back": "Jew",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "juden",
      "form2": "judar",
      "form3": "judarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rom",
    "back": "Roma / Romani",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "romen",
      "form2": "romer",
      "form3": "romerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "finska",
    "back": "Finnish",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helt",
    "back": "completely",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "politiker",
    "back": "politician",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "politikern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "politikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "diplomat",
    "back": "diplomat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "diplomaten",
      "form2": "diplomater",
      "form3": "diplomaterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vetenskapsman",
    "back": "scientist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vetenskapsmannen",
      "form2": "vetenskapsmän",
      "form3": "vetenskapsmännen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regissör",
    "back": "director",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "regissören",
      "form2": "regissörer",
      "form3": "regissörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kokboksförfattare",
    "back": "cookbook author",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kokboksförfattaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kokboksförfattarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helgon",
    "back": "saint",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "helgonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "helgonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "operasångare",
    "back": "opera singer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "operasångaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "operasångarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotbollsspelare",
    "back": "football (soccer) player",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollsspelaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fotbollsspelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "drottning",
    "back": "queen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "drottningen",
      "form2": "drottningar",
      "form3": "drottningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "det mesta",
    "back": "most"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "normal",
    "back": "normal",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studenttidning",
    "back": "student paper",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "studenttidningen",
      "form2": "studenttidningar",
      "form3": "studenttidningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utbytesstudent",
    "back": "exchange student",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utbytesstudenten",
      "form2": "utbytesstudenter",
      "form3": "utbytesstudenterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svar",
    "back": "answer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svaret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "svaren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kebabpizza",
    "back": "kebab pizza",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kebabpizzan",
      "form2": "kebabpizzaor",
      "form3": "kebabpizzaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fläskfilé",
    "back": "pork tenderloin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fläskfilén",
      "form2": "fläskfiléer",
      "form3": "fläskfiléerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "praktisk",
    "back": "practical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tobak",
    "back": "tobacco",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "under",
    "back": "under",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läpp",
    "back": "lip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läppen",
      "form2": "läppar",
      "form3": "läpparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smak",
    "back": "taste, flavor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smaken",
      "form2": "smaker",
      "form3": "smakerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "eukalyptus",
    "back": "eucalyptus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "eukalyptusen",
      "form2": "eukalyptusar",
      "form3": "eukalyptusarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äcklig",
    "back": "disgusting",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Haparanda",
    "back": "Haparanda",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "makaroner",
    "back": "macaroni",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dra (-r, drog, dragit) in luft",
    "back": "inhale, breathe in",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "astma",
    "back": "asthma",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vår",
    "back": "spring",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "våren",
      "form2": "vårar",
      "form3": "vårarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utomhus",
    "back": "outside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ändå",
    "back": "anyway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grilla",
    "back": "barbecue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grillar",
      "form2": "grillade",
      "form3": "grillat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ute",
    "back": "outside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i rad",
    "back": "in a row"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gullig",
    "back": "cute",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snabbfakta",
    "back": "quick facts",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "konstitutionell monarki",
    "back": "constitutional monarchy"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svensk krona",
    "back": "Swedish krona",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "SEK"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Kebnekaise",
    "back": "Kebnekaise (Sweden’s highest peak)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "älv",
    "back": "river",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "älven",
      "form2": "älvar",
      "form3": "älvarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "statskick",
    "back": "system of government",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "statskicket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "statskicken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "befolkning",
    "back": "population",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "befolkningstäthet",
    "back": "population density",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "befolkningstätheten",
      "form2": "befolkningstätheter",
      "form3": "befolkningstätheterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vattendrag",
    "back": "watercourse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vattendraget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "vattendragen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "berg",
    "back": "mountain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "berget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bergen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "valuta",
    "back": "currency",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "valutan",
      "form2": "valutor",
      "form3": "valutorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "landskod",
    "back": "country code",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "landskoden",
      "form2": "landskoder",
      "form3": "landskoderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "landsnummer",
    "back": "country calling code",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "landsnumret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "landsnumren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förnamn",
    "back": "first name, given name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förnamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "förnamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tilltalsnamn",
    "back": "first name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tilltalsnamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tilltalsnamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "separat",
    "back": "separate",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvinnonamn",
    "back": "woman’s name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kvinnonamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kvinnonamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mansnamn",
    "back": "man’s name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mansnamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "mansnamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "10 i topp",
    "back": "Top 10"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "välja",
    "back": "choose",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "väljaer",
      "form2": "valde",
      "form3": "valt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyckelord",
    "back": "keywords",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nyckelordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "nyckelorden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "geografi",
    "back": "geography",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "religion",
    "back": "religion",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "religionen",
      "form2": "religioner",
      "form3": "religionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "östra",
    "back": "eastern",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "västra",
    "back": "western",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "central",
    "back": "central",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gränsa (-r, -de, -t) till",
    "back": "border on",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "öken",
    "back": "desert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "öknen",
      "form2": "öknar",
      "form3": "öknarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "muslim",
    "back": "Muslim",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "muslimen",
      "form2": "muslimer",
      "form3": "muslimerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hindu",
    "back": "Hindu",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hindun",
      "form2": "hinduer",
      "form3": "hinduerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kristen",
    "back": "Christian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "kristna"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "protestant",
    "back": "Protestant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "protestanten",
      "form2": "protestanter",
      "form3": "protestanterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ortodoxt kristna",
    "back": "Orthodox Christians"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "katolik",
    "back": "Catholic",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "katoliken",
      "form2": "katoliker",
      "form3": "katolikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "odla",
    "back": "cultivate, grow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "odlar",
      "form2": "odlade",
      "form3": "odlat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter10_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter10",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "producera",
    "back": "produce",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "producerar",
      "form2": "producerade",
      "form3": "producerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vänskap",
    "back": "friendship",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vänskapen",
      "form2": "vänskaper",
      "form3": "vänskaperna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyfiken",
    "back": "curious",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vuxen",
    "back": "adult",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "vuxet",
        "vuxna"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fritidsaktivitet",
    "back": "leisure activity",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fritidsaktiviteten",
      "form2": "fritidsaktiviteter",
      "form3": "fritidsaktiviteterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lära känna",
    "back": "get to know",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lära kännar",
      "form2": "lära kännade",
      "form3": "lära kännat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "öppen förskola",
    "back": "drop-in preschool"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bebis",
    "back": "baby",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bebisen",
      "form2": "bebisar",
      "form3": "bebisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gratis",
    "back": "for free",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föräldraledig",
    "back": "on parental leave",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spontan",
    "back": "spontaneous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lojal",
    "back": "loyal",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kasse",
    "back": "bag",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kassen",
      "form2": "kassear",
      "form3": "kassearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjälpsam",
    "back": "helpful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-ma"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tålamod",
    "back": "patience",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gnälla",
    "back": "complain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gnällaer",
      "form2": "gnällade",
      "form3": "gnällat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dagens",
    "back": "today’s",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ungdom",
    "back": "youth",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ungdomen",
      "form2": "ungdomar",
      "form3": "ungdomarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skratta",
    "back": "laugh",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skrattar",
      "form2": "skrattade",
      "form3": "skrattat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klok",
    "back": "wise",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mentor",
    "back": "mentor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mentorn",
      "form2": "mentorer",
      "form3": "mentorerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glasställe",
    "back": "ice cream shop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glasstället",
      "form2": "glasställen",
      "form3": "glasställena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samhälle",
    "back": "society",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "samhället",
      "form2": "samhälleen",
      "form3": "samhälleena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejta",
    "back": "skate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtar",
      "form2": "skejtade",
      "form3": "skejtat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejtare",
    "back": "skater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skejtarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejtpark",
    "back": "skatepark",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtparken",
      "form2": "skejtparker",
      "form3": "skejtparkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pirrig",
    "back": "excited",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "duktig",
    "back": "good, capable",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "peppa",
    "back": "encourage, hype up",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "peppar",
      "form2": "peppade",
      "form3": "peppat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skejtklipp",
    "back": "skate clip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skejtklippet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skejtklippen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vegansk",
    "back": "vegan",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grej",
    "back": "thing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grejen",
      "form2": "grejer",
      "form3": "grejerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ovanlig",
    "back": "unusual",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föreslå",
    "back": "suggest",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "föreslår",
      "form2": "förslog",
      "form3": "föreslagit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kör",
    "back": "choir",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kören",
      "form2": "körer",
      "form3": "körerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "golf",
    "back": "golf",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konstutställning",
    "back": "art exhibition",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konstutställningen",
      "form2": "konstutställningar",
      "form3": "konstutställningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "språkkurs",
    "back": "language course",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "språkkursen",
      "form2": "språkkurser",
      "form3": "språkkurserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dejta",
    "back": "date",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dejtar",
      "form2": "dejtade",
      "form3": "dejtat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bjuda",
    "back": "invite",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bjudaer",
      "form2": "bjöd",
      "form3": "bjudit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krog",
    "back": "bar, restaurant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "krogen",
      "form2": "krogar",
      "form3": "krogarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjejkompis",
    "back": "female friend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tjejkompisen",
      "form2": "tjejkompisar",
      "form3": "tjejkompisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inte längre",
    "back": "no longer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hundpromenad",
    "back": "dog walk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hundpromenaden",
      "form2": "hundpromenader",
      "form3": "hundpromenaderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dam",
    "back": "lady",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "damen",
      "form2": "damer",
      "form3": "damerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolflicka",
    "back": "schoolgirl",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolflickan",
      "form2": "skolflickaor",
      "form3": "skolflickaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förskolebarn",
    "back": "preschool child",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förskolebarnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "förskolebarnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snygging",
    "back": "good-looking person",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snyggingen",
      "form2": "snyggingar",
      "form3": "snyggingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tipsa",
    "back": "tip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tipsar",
      "form2": "tipsade",
      "form3": "tipsat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rekommendera",
    "back": "recommend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rekommenderar",
      "form2": "rekommenderade",
      "form3": "rekommenderat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "metod",
    "back": "method",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "metoden",
      "form2": "metoder",
      "form3": "metoderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utställning",
    "back": "exhibition",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utställningen",
      "form2": "utställningar",
      "form3": "utställningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tavla",
    "back": "painting",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tavlan",
      "form2": "tavlaor",
      "form3": "tavlaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pröva",
    "back": "try, test",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prövar",
      "form2": "prövade",
      "form3": "prövat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nätdejting",
    "back": "online dating",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "profil",
    "back": "profile",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "profilen",
      "form2": "profiler",
      "form3": "profilerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dejtingapp",
    "back": "dating app",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dejtingappen",
      "form2": "dejtingappar",
      "form3": "dejtingapparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mess",
    "back": "text message",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "messet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "messen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barnfri",
    "back": "child-free",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sportig",
    "back": "athletic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "löpning",
    "back": "running",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "löpningen",
      "form2": "löpningar",
      "form3": "löpningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motorsport",
    "back": "motorsport",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "motorsporten",
      "form2": "motorsporter",
      "form3": "motorsporterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fet",
    "back": "cool",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motorcykel",
    "back": "motorcycle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "motorcykeln",
      "form2": "motorcykelar",
      "form3": "motorcykelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Rom",
    "back": "Rome",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "radera",
    "back": "delete",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "raderar",
      "form2": "raderade",
      "form3": "raderat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inte heller",
    "back": "neither"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sportbar",
    "back": "sports bar",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sportbaren",
      "form2": "sportbarer",
      "form3": "sportbarerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "mellan jobb",
    "back": "between jobs"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trist",
    "back": "boring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hallå där!",
    "back": "Hello there"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frånskild",
    "back": "divorced",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "städa",
    "back": "clean up",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "städar",
      "form2": "städade",
      "form3": "städat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvätta",
    "back": "do the laundry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tvättar",
      "form2": "tvättade",
      "form3": "tvättat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stryka",
    "back": "iron",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "strykaer",
      "form2": "strök",
      "form3": "strukit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tåla",
    "back": "tolerate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tålar",
      "form2": "tålade",
      "form3": "tålat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nick",
    "back": "nickname",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nicken",
      "form2": "nickar",
      "form3": "nickarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sporthatare",
    "back": "sports hater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sporthataren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sporthataresporthatarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mikro",
    "back": "microwave",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mikron",
      "form2": "mikroer",
      "form3": "mikroerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i närheten",
    "back": "nearby"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gård",
    "back": "farm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gården",
      "form2": "gårdar",
      "form3": "gårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjärtlig",
    "back": "heartfelt",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frys",
    "back": "freezer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frysen",
      "form2": "frysar",
      "form3": "frysarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pirog",
    "back": "pasty",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pirogen",
      "form2": "piroger",
      "form3": "pirogerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "redo",
    "back": "ready",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chans",
    "back": "chance, opportunity",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "chansen",
      "form2": "chanser",
      "form3": "chanserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta chansen",
    "back": "take the chance",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ta chansenr",
      "form2": "tog",
      "form3": "tagit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tjenixen!",
    "back": "Hi there! / Hey"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uteliv",
    "back": "nightlife",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "annars",
    "back": "otherwise",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "körkort",
    "back": "driver’s license",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "körkortet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "körkorten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sitta (-er, satt, suttit) bak",
    "back": "sit in the back",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snart",
    "back": "soon",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "också",
    "back": "also, too",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Mars",
    "back": "Mars",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ljuga",
    "back": "lie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ljugaer",
      "form2": "ljög",
      "form3": "ljugit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ingenting",
    "back": "nothing",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetslös",
    "back": "unemployed",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadslös",
    "back": "homeless",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huslig",
    "back": "domestic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ironisk",
    "back": "ironic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ointressant",
    "back": "uninteresting",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "töntig",
    "back": "dorky, uncool",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äventyrlig",
    "back": "adventurous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "verka",
    "back": "seem",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "verkar",
      "form2": "verkade",
      "form3": "verkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fritid",
    "back": "free time",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "repetera",
    "back": "repeat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "repeterar",
      "form2": "repeterade",
      "form3": "repeterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tabell",
    "back": "table",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tabellen",
      "form2": "tabeller",
      "form3": "tabellerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lukta",
    "back": "smell",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "luktar",
      "form2": "luktade",
      "form3": "luktat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lyssnare",
    "back": "listener",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lyssnaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lyssnarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läsare",
    "back": "reader",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läsaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "läsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "genitiv",
    "back": "genitive",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "genitivet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "genitiven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "digital",
    "back": "digital",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tangentbord",
    "back": "keyboard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tangentbordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tangentborden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "papperskorg",
    "back": "wastepaper basket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "papperskorgen",
      "form2": "papperskorgar",
      "form3": "papperskorgarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sladd",
    "back": "cord",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sladden",
      "form2": "sladdar",
      "form3": "sladdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kabel",
    "back": "cable",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kabeln",
      "form2": "kablar",
      "form3": "kablarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kursiv stil",
    "back": "italics",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kursiv stilen",
      "form2": "kursiv stilar",
      "form3": "kursiv stilarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spara",
    "back": "save",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sparar",
      "form2": "sparade",
      "form3": "sparat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skriva ut",
    "back": "print",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skriva uter",
      "form2": "skrev",
      "form3": "skrivit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snabel-a",
    "back": "@ symbol",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snabel-aet",
      "form2": "snabel-an",
      "form3": "snabel-ana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mapp",
    "back": "folder",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mappen",
      "form2": "mappar",
      "form3": "mapparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fet stil",
    "back": "bold"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bindestreck",
    "back": "hyphen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bindestrecket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bindestrecken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ångra",
    "back": "undo",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ångrar",
      "form2": "ångrade",
      "form3": "ångrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hashtagg / fyrkant",
    "back": "hashtag"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bifoga",
    "back": "attach",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bifogar",
      "form2": "bifogade",
      "form3": "bifogat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mus",
    "back": "mouse",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "webbkamera",
    "back": "webcam",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "webbkameran",
      "form2": "webbkameraor",
      "form3": "webbkameraorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "punkt",
    "back": "period, full stop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "punkten",
      "form2": "punkter",
      "form3": "punkterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "understreck",
    "back": "underline",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "understrecket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "understrecken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skärm",
    "back": "screen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skärmen",
      "form2": "skärmar",
      "form3": "skärmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "öppna",
    "back": "open",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "öppnar",
      "form2": "öppnade",
      "form3": "öppnat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utropstecken",
    "back": "exclamation point",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utropsteckenet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "utropsteckenen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frågetecken",
    "back": "question mark",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frågeteckenet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "frågeteckenen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snedstreck",
    "back": "slash",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snedstrecket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "snedstrecken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "typsnitt",
    "back": "font",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "typsnittet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "typsnitten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "söka",
    "back": "search",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sökar",
      "form2": "sökate",
      "form3": "sökat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klistra in",
    "back": "paste",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klistra inr",
      "form2": "klistra inde",
      "form3": "klistra int"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "länk",
    "back": "link",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "länken",
      "form2": "länkar",
      "form3": "länkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fungera",
    "back": "work",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fungerar",
      "form2": "fungerade",
      "form3": "fungerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fylla på",
    "back": "refill",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fylla påer",
      "form2": "fylla påde",
      "form3": "fylla påt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "godkänna",
    "back": "approve",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "godkännar",
      "form2": "godkännade",
      "form3": "godkännat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hackad",
    "back": "hacked",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klicka",
    "back": "click",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klickar",
      "form2": "klickade",
      "form3": "klickat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ansluta",
    "back": "connect",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "anslutar",
      "form2": "anslutade",
      "form3": "anslutat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "koppla",
    "back": "connect",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kopplar",
      "form2": "kopplade",
      "form3": "kopplat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "logga in",
    "back": "log in",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "logga inr",
      "form2": "logga inde",
      "form3": "logga int"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lösenord",
    "back": "password",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lösenordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lösenorden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "muta",
    "back": "mute",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mutaer",
      "form2": "mutade",
      "form3": "mutat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "starta om",
    "back": "restart",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "starta omr",
      "form2": "starta omde",
      "form3": "starta omt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stoppa in",
    "back": "put in",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stoppa inr",
      "form2": "stoppa inde",
      "form3": "stoppa int"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sätta på",
    "back": "turn on",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sätta påer",
      "form2": "satte",
      "form3": "satt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "funka",
    "back": "work",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "funkar",
      "form2": "funkade",
      "form3": "funkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "titta",
    "back": "look",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tittar",
      "form2": "tittade",
      "form3": "tittat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Nu går det.",
    "back": "Now it’s working"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ikon",
    "back": "icon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ikonen",
      "form2": "ikoner",
      "form3": "ikonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trasig",
    "back": "broken",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hända",
    "back": "happen",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "händaer",
      "form2": "händade",
      "form3": "händat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Pang!",
    "back": "Bang"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det sa bara pang!",
    "back": "It just went bang"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "usb-ingång",
    "back": "USB port",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "usb-ingången",
      "form2": "usb-ingångar",
      "form3": "usb-ingångarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dokument",
    "back": "document",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dokumentet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "dokumenten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrivare",
    "back": "printer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skrivaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skrivarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glömma",
    "back": "forget",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glömmer",
      "form2": "glömde",
      "form3": "glömt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inbjudan",
    "back": "invitation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inbjudanen",
      "form2": "inbjudanor",
      "form3": "inbjudanorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mikrofon",
    "back": "microphone",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mikrofonen",
      "form2": "mikrofoner",
      "form3": "mikrofonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stänga av",
    "back": "turn off",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stänga aver",
      "form2": "stänga avde",
      "form3": "stänga avt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "e-postadress",
    "back": "email address",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "e-postadressen",
      "form2": "e-postadresser",
      "form3": "e-postadresserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ordbetoning",
    "back": "word stress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ordbetoningen",
      "form2": "ordbetoningar",
      "form3": "ordbetoningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stavelse",
    "back": "syllable",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stavelsen",
      "form2": "stavelseer",
      "form3": "stavelserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matematik",
    "back": "mathematics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "profiltext",
    "back": "bio",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "profiltexten",
      "form2": "profiltexter",
      "form3": "profiltexterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dejtingsida",
    "back": "dating site",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dejtingsidan",
      "form2": "dejtingsidaor",
      "form3": "dejtingsidaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "seriös",
    "back": "serious",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter11_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter11",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ambitiös",
    "back": "ambitious",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "favoritmat",
    "back": "favorite food",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "favoritmaten",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "favoritmaten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "maträtt",
    "back": "dish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "maträtten",
      "form2": "maträtter",
      "form3": "maträtterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordgubbskräm",
    "back": "strawberry purée",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordgubbskrämen",
      "form2": "jordgubbskrämer",
      "form3": "jordgubbskrämerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kåldolme",
    "back": "cabbage roll",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kåldolmen",
      "form2": "kåldolmar",
      "form3": "kåldolmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pyttipanna",
    "back": "Swedish hash",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "stekt ägg",
    "back": "fried egg"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rödbeta",
    "back": "beetroot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rödbetan",
      "form2": "rödbetaor",
      "form3": "rödbetaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "raggmunk",
    "back": "potato pancake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "raggmunken",
      "form2": "raggmunkar",
      "form3": "raggmunkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fläsk",
    "back": "pork",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fläsket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fläsken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ripa",
    "back": "grouse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ripan",
      "form2": "ripaor",
      "form3": "ripaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gräddsås",
    "back": "gravy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gräddsåsen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "gräddsåser"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rönnbärsgelé",
    "back": "rowanberry jelly",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rönnbärsgelén",
      "form2": "rönnbärsgeléer",
      "form3": "rönnbärsgeléerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spagetti",
    "back": "spaghetti",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varmkorv",
    "back": "hot dog",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "varmkorven",
      "form2": "varmkorvar",
      "form3": "varmkorvarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "älgstek",
    "back": "moose steak",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "älgsteken",
      "form2": "älgstekar",
      "form3": "älgstekarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klyftpotatis",
    "back": "potato wedges",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klyftpotatisen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "klyftpotatisen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svartvinbärsgelé",
    "back": "blackcurrant jelly",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svartvinbärsgelén",
      "form2": "svartvinbärsgeléer",
      "form3": "svartvinbärsgeléerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "förtjust i",
    "back": "fond of, keen on"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "biff med lök",
    "back": "steak with onions"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ris",
    "back": "rice",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "småkakor",
    "back": "small cookies, biscuits",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "husmanskost",
    "back": "traditional Swedish home cooking",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "traditionell",
    "back": "traditional",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "titta efter",
    "back": "look for",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "titta efterr",
      "form2": "titta efterde",
      "form3": "titta eftert"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rättvisemärkt",
    "back": "fair trade",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bondgård",
    "back": "farm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bondgården",
      "form2": "bondgårdar",
      "form3": "bondgårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "närproducerad",
    "back": "locally produced",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blad",
    "back": "leaf",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bladet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bladen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "urdålig",
    "back": "really bad, terrible",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matlagning",
    "back": "cooking",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hämtmat",
    "back": "takeout food",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "thai",
    "back": "thai",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sushi",
    "back": "sushi",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "falafel",
    "back": "falafel",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klimatsmart",
    "back": "environmentally friendly",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sparris",
    "back": "asparagus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sparrisen",
      "form2": "sparrisar",
      "form3": "sparrisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tofu",
    "back": "tofu",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korv",
    "back": "sausage, hot dog",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "korven",
      "form2": "korvar",
      "form3": "korvarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mjölkprodukt",
    "back": "dairy product",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mjölkprodukten",
      "form2": "mjölkprodukter",
      "form3": "mjölkprodukterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "laktosintolerant",
    "back": "lactose intolerant",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vete",
    "back": "wheat",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glutenallergi",
    "back": "gluten allergy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glutenallergin",
      "form2": "glutenallergier",
      "form3": "glutenallergierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svamp",
    "back": "mushroom",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svampen",
      "form2": "svampar",
      "form3": "svamparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "torka",
    "back": "dry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "torkar",
      "form2": "torkade",
      "form3": "torkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "koka",
    "back": "boil",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kokar",
      "form2": "kokade",
      "form3": "kokat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färdigrätt",
    "back": "ready-made meal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färdigrätten",
      "form2": "färdigrätter",
      "form3": "färdigrätterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pulvermos",
    "back": "instant mashed potatoes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pulvermoset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "pulvermosen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "stor stark",
    "back": "large draft beer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bisats",
    "back": "subordinate clause",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bisatsen",
      "form2": "bisatser",
      "form3": "bisatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "subjunktion",
    "back": "subordinating conjunction",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "subjunktionen",
      "form2": "subjunktioner",
      "form3": "subjunktionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordgubbstårta",
    "back": "strawberry cake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jordgubbstårtan",
      "form2": "jordgubbstårtaor",
      "form3": "jordgubbstårtaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "indisk",
    "back": "Indian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "norsk",
    "back": "Norwegian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "colombiansk",
    "back": "Colombian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "algerisk",
    "back": "Algerian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nationalitet",
    "back": "nationality",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nationaliteten",
      "form2": "nationaliteter",
      "form3": "nationaliteterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "afghansk",
    "back": "Afghan",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "australiensisk",
    "back": "Australian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brasiliansk",
    "back": "Brazilian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brittisk",
    "back": "British",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "eritreansk",
    "back": "Eritrean",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "etiopisk",
    "back": "Ethiopian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "finsk",
    "back": "Finnish",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fransk",
    "back": "French",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grekisk",
    "back": "Greek",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "indonesisk",
    "back": "Indonesian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "irakisk",
    "back": "Iraqi",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "iransk/persisk",
    "back": "Iranian, Persian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "italiensk",
    "back": "Italian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "japansk",
    "back": "Japanese",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kenyansk",
    "back": "Kenyan",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kinesisk",
    "back": "Chinese",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "koreansk",
    "back": "Korean",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kubansk",
    "back": "Cuban",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "libanesisk",
    "back": "Lebanese",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "marockansk",
    "back": "Moroccan",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mexikansk",
    "back": "Mexican",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyzeeländsk",
    "back": "New Zealander",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pakistansk",
    "back": "Pakistani",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "polsk",
    "back": "Polish",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rysk",
    "back": "Russian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sydafrikansk",
    "back": "South African",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "syrisk",
    "back": "Syrian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "thailändsk",
    "back": "Thai",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunisisk",
    "back": "Tunisian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "turkisk",
    "back": "Turkish",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tysk",
    "back": "German",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ukrainsk",
    "back": "Ukrainian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ungersk",
    "back": "Hungarian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "österrikisk",
    "back": "Austrian",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "anteckna",
    "back": "make notes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "antecknar",
      "form2": "antecknade",
      "form3": "antecknat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blodpudding",
    "back": "blood pudding",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "råvara",
    "back": "raw ingredient",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "råvaran",
      "form2": "råvaraor",
      "form3": "råvaraorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rotfrukt",
    "back": "root vegetable",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rotfrukten",
      "form2": "rotfrukter",
      "form3": "rotfrukterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "växt",
    "back": "plant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "växten",
      "form2": "växter",
      "form3": "växterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "midsommar",
    "back": "midsummer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "midsommaren",
      "form2": "midsomrar",
      "form3": "midsomrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sädesslag",
    "back": "cereal grain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sädesslaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sädesslagen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "invandrare",
    "back": "immigrant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "invandraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "invandrarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "introducera",
    "back": "introduce",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "introducerar",
      "form2": "introducerade",
      "form3": "introducerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pizzasallad",
    "back": "pizza salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pizzasalladen",
      "form2": "pizzasallader",
      "form3": "pizzasalladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kålsallad",
    "back": "cabbage salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kålsalladen",
      "form2": "kålsallader",
      "form3": "kålsalladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Kroatien",
    "back": "Croatia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nordöstra",
    "back": "northeastern",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kebab",
    "back": "kebab",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kebaben",
      "form2": "kebaber",
      "form3": "kebaberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vardagsmat",
    "back": "everyday food",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ostkust",
    "back": "east coast",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inlagd",
    "back": "pickled",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "inlagt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ättika",
    "back": "Swedish vinegar",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kryddning",
    "back": "seasoning",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kryddningen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kryddningar"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "senapssill",
    "back": "herring in mustard sauce",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "löksill",
    "back": "onion-marinated herring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "exempelvis",
    "back": "for example",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "wasabisill",
    "back": "wasabi-marinated herring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "baconsill",
    "back": "bacon-flavored herring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strömming",
    "back": "Baltic herring",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "strömmingen",
      "form2": "strömmingar",
      "form3": "strömmingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "surströmming",
    "back": "fermented Baltic herring",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "surströmmingen",
      "form2": "surströmmingar",
      "form3": "surströmmingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "syrad",
    "back": "fermented",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fermenterad",
    "back": "fermented",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "fermenterat",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stark",
    "back": "strong",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förrän",
    "back": "until",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brännvin",
    "back": "vodka, aquavit",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bas",
    "back": "staple",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "basen",
      "form2": "baser",
      "form3": "baserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "dubbelt så mycket",
    "back": "twice as much"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färskpotatis",
    "back": "new potatoes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färskpotatisen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "färskpotatisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nykokt",
    "back": "freshly boiled",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dill",
    "back": "dill",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "råg",
    "back": "rye",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klimat",
    "back": "climate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klimatet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "klimaten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blanda",
    "back": "mix",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blandar",
      "form2": "blandade",
      "form3": "blandat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rågmjöl",
    "back": "rye flour",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunn",
    "back": "thin",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skafferi",
    "back": "pantry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skafferit",
      "form2": "skafferir",
      "form3": "skafferirna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunnbröd",
    "back": "flatbread",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korn",
    "back": "barley",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "meter",
    "back": "meter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "metern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "meterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väga",
    "back": "weigh",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vägaer",
      "form2": "vägade",
      "form3": "vägat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ton",
    "back": "pitch",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tonen",
      "form2": "toner",
      "form3": "tonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ha tur",
    "back": "be lucky",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ha turr",
      "form2": "hade",
      "form3": "haft"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "älgkött",
    "back": "moose meat",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nötkött",
    "back": "beef",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lingon",
    "back": "lingonberry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lingonet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lingonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vild",
    "back": "wild",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "vilt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "saft",
    "back": "juice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "saften",
      "form2": "safter",
      "form3": "safterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "rårörda lingon",
    "back": "raw-stirred lingonberries"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kroppkakor",
    "back": "potato dumplings",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fläskpannkaka",
    "back": "pork pancake",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jordgubbsfeber",
    "back": "strawberry fever",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mogen",
    "back": "ripe",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et",
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "importerad",
    "back": "imported",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "midsommarhelg",
    "back": "Midsummer weekend",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "midsommarhelgen",
      "form2": "midsommarhelger",
      "form3": "midsommarhelgerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "självplock",
    "back": "pick-your-own",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kräm",
    "back": "fruit purée",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "krämen",
      "form2": "krämer",
      "form3": "krämerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lägga",
    "back": "put",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läggaer",
      "form2": "lade",
      "form3": "lagt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gräddtårta",
    "back": "whipped cream cake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gräddtårtan",
      "form2": "gräddtårtaor",
      "form3": "gräddtårtaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "naturell",
    "back": "plain, natural",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fett",
    "back": "fat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fetten",
      "form2": "fetter",
      "form3": "fetterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rad",
    "back": "line",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "raden",
      "form2": "rader",
      "form3": "raderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "få",
    "back": "few",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pannkaka",
    "back": "pancake",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pannkakan",
      "form2": "pannkakaor",
      "form3": "pannkakaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "buffé",
    "back": "buffet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "buffén",
      "form2": "bufféer",
      "form3": "bufféerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lax",
    "back": "salmon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "laxen",
      "form2": "laxar",
      "form3": "laxarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minipizza",
    "back": "mini pizza",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minipizzan",
      "form2": "minipizzaor",
      "form3": "minipizzaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mätt",
    "back": "full",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pralin",
    "back": "praline",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pralinen",
      "form2": "praliner",
      "form3": "pralinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gäst",
    "back": "guest",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gästen",
      "form2": "gäster",
      "form3": "gästerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvärtom",
    "back": "the opposite",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "annorlunda",
    "back": "different",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "haj",
    "back": "shark",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hajen",
      "form2": "hajar",
      "form3": "hajarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "säker",
    "back": "certain",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "säkra"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åsikt",
    "back": "opinion",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "åsikten",
      "form2": "åsikter",
      "form3": "åsikterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "värdering",
    "back": "value",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "värderingen",
      "form2": "värderingar",
      "form3": "värderingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i vinter",
    "back": "this winter"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mörk choklad",
    "back": "dark chocolate",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mjölkchoklad",
    "back": "milk chocolate",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stänga",
    "back": "close",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stängaer",
      "form2": "stängade",
      "form3": "stängat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på väg",
    "back": "on the way"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "så länge",
    "back": "for now"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "alkoholfri",
    "back": "non-alcoholic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ett glas rött",
    "back": "a glass of red wine"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sorter",
    "back": "types, kinds",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hemlagad",
    "back": "homemade",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tacka",
    "back": "thank",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tackar",
      "form2": "tackade",
      "form3": "tackat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dessert",
    "back": "dessert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "desserten",
      "form2": "desserter",
      "form3": "desserterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "avec",
    "back": "after-dinner drink",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "avecen",
      "form2": "avecer",
      "form3": "avecerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "efterrätt",
    "back": "dessert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "efterrätten",
      "form2": "efterrätter",
      "form3": "efterrätterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Kan vi få notan?",
    "back": "May we have the bill"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_187",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chokladbit",
    "back": "piece of chocolate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "chokladbiten",
      "form2": "chokladbitar",
      "form3": "chokladbitarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_188",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ska vi dela rakt av?",
    "back": "Should we split it evenly"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_189",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dricksa",
    "back": "tip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dricksar",
      "form2": "dricksade",
      "form3": "dricksat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_190",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hundring",
    "back": "a hundred (SEK)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hundringen",
      "form2": "hundringar",
      "form3": "hundringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_191",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vrålhungrig",
    "back": "starving",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_192",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tillbehör",
    "back": "side dish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tillbehöret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tillbehören"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_193",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Mums.",
    "back": "Yum"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_194",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "torka av",
    "back": "wipe off",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "torka avr",
      "form2": "torka avde",
      "form3": "torka avt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_195",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smula",
    "back": "crumb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smulan",
      "form2": "smulaor",
      "form3": "smulaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_196",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "visst",
    "back": "sure, of course",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_197",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "herregud",
    "back": "oh my god",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_198",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvudrätt",
    "back": "main course",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudrätten",
      "form2": "huvudrätter",
      "form3": "huvudrätterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_199",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grönsallad",
    "back": "green salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grönsalladen",
      "form2": "grönsallader",
      "form3": "grönsalladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_200",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jättesugen",
    "back": "really craving",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et",
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_201",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lägga dricks",
    "back": "leave a tip",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lägga drickser",
      "form2": "lade",
      "form3": "lagt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_202",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "swisha",
    "back": "pay with Swish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "swishar",
      "form2": "swishade",
      "form3": "swishat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_203",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tendens",
    "back": "tendency",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tendensen",
      "form2": "tendenser",
      "form3": "tendenserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_204",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "till vardags",
    "back": "in everyday life"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter12_205",
    "chapter": "Chapter12",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "satsdel",
    "back": "part of a sentence",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "satsdelen",
      "form2": "satsdelar",
      "form3": "satsdelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolklass",
    "back": "class",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolklassen",
      "form2": "skolklasser",
      "form3": "skolklasserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "planet",
    "back": "planet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "planeten",
      "form2": "planeter",
      "form3": "planeterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "astronaut",
    "back": "astronaut",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "astronauten",
      "form2": "astronauter",
      "form3": "astronauterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "månen",
    "back": "the moon",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "därifrån",
    "back": "from there",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rymden",
    "back": "space",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rymdraket",
    "back": "space rocket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rymdraketen",
      "form2": "rymdraketer",
      "form3": "rymdraketerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trädgårdsmästare",
    "back": "gardener",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trädgårdsmästaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "trädgårdsmästarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontor",
    "back": "office",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kontoret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "kontoren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stirra",
    "back": "stare",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stirrar",
      "form2": "stirrade",
      "form3": "stirrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotbollsproffs",
    "back": "football/soccer player",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollsproffset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fotbollsproffsen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rappare",
    "back": "rapper",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rapparen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "rapparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "polisbil",
    "back": "police car",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "polisbilen",
      "form2": "polisbilar",
      "form3": "polisbilarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veterinär",
    "back": "veterinarian",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "veterinären",
      "form2": "veterinärer",
      "form3": "veterinärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tandhygienist",
    "back": "dental hygienist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tandhygienisten",
      "form2": "tandhygienister",
      "form3": "tandhygienisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det stämmer.",
    "back": "That’s right"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inne",
    "back": "inside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ute",
    "back": "outside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uppe",
    "back": "up there, above",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nere",
    "back": "down there, below",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framme",
    "back": "in an easily noticeable spot",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "borta",
    "back": "away",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vart",
    "back": "where to",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dit",
    "back": "there",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hit",
    "back": "here",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bort",
    "back": "away",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "därifrån",
    "back": "from there",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "härifrån",
    "back": "from here",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inifrån",
    "back": "from inside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utifrån",
    "back": "from outside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uppifrån",
    "back": "from above",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nerifrån",
    "back": "from below",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framifrån",
    "back": "from in front",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bortifrån",
    "back": "from over there",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rymdfysiker",
    "back": "space physicist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rymdfysikern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "rymdfysikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "institut",
    "back": "institute",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "institutet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "instituten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rymdfysik",
    "back": "space physics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "doktorera",
    "back": "get a PhD",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "doktorerar",
      "form2": "doktorerade",
      "form3": "doktorerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "norrsken",
    "back": "northern lights / aurora borealis",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "norrskenet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "norrskenen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forskningsprojekt",
    "back": "research project",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "forskningsprojektet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "forskningsprojekten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skräckroman",
    "back": "horror novel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skräckromanen",
      "form2": "skräckromaner",
      "form3": "skräckromanerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jobba (-r, -de, -t) över",
    "back": "work overtime",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hushållsarbete",
    "back": "household chores",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hushållsarbetet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hushållsarbeten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skoter",
    "back": "snowmobile",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skotern",
      "form2": "skoterrar",
      "form3": "skoterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "intensiv",
    "back": "intense",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stressig",
    "back": "stressful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försova (-er, försov, försovit) sig",
    "back": "oversleep",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ostfrall",
    "back": "cheese sandwich",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ostfralln",
      "form2": "ostfrallor",
      "form3": "ostfrallorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "presentera",
    "back": "present",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "presenterar",
      "form2": "presenterade",
      "form3": "presenterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "resultat",
    "back": "result",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "resultatet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "resultaten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uppsats",
    "back": "essay, thesis",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "uppsatsen",
      "form2": "uppsatser",
      "form3": "uppsatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rymdbas",
    "back": "space base",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rymdbasen",
      "form2": "rymdbaser",
      "form3": "rymdbaserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "amerikan",
    "back": "American",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "amerikanen",
      "form2": "amerikaner",
      "form3": "amerikanerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skynda (-r, -de, -t) sig",
    "back": "hurry",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "duka",
    "back": "set the table",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dukar",
      "form2": "dukade",
      "form3": "dukat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "norrländsk",
    "back": "from Norrland, Northern Swedish",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vargtass",
    "back": "vargtass (traditional Swedish drink with lingonberry juice and vodka)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "välkomstdrink",
    "back": "welcome drink",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "välkomstdrinken",
      "form2": "välkomstdrinkar",
      "form3": "välkomstdrinkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjällröding",
    "back": "Arctic char",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fjällrödingen",
      "form2": "fjällrödingar",
      "form3": "fjällrödingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mandelpotatis",
    "back": "almond potato",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mandelpotatisen",
      "form2": "mandelpotatisar",
      "form3": "mandelpotatisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjortronglass",
    "back": "cloudberry ice cream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjortronglassen",
      "form2": "hjortronglassar",
      "form3": "hjortronglassarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lingonsaft",
    "back": "lingonberry juice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lingonsaften",
      "form2": "lingonsafter",
      "form3": "lingonsafterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fönster",
    "back": "window",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fönstret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fönstren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "magisk",
    "back": "magical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förskollärare",
    "back": "preschool teacher",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förskolläraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "förskollärarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "larm",
    "back": "alarm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "larmet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "larmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "golv",
    "back": "floor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "golvet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "golven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "saga",
    "back": "fairy tale",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sagan",
      "form2": "sagaor",
      "form3": "sagaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bråka",
    "back": "fight, argue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bråkar",
      "form2": "bråkade",
      "form3": "bråkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lekpark",
    "back": "playground",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lekparken",
      "form2": "lekparker",
      "form3": "lekparkerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sandlåda",
    "back": "sandbox",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sandlådan",
      "form2": "sandlådaor",
      "form3": "sandlådaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gunga",
    "back": "swing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gungan",
      "form2": "gungaor",
      "form3": "gungaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konferens",
    "back": "conference",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konferensen",
      "form2": "konferenser",
      "form3": "konferenserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i förrgår",
    "back": "the day before yesterday"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "aktuell",
    "back": "relevant",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Chile",
    "back": "Chile",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grammatikprov",
    "back": "grammar test",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grammatikprovet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "grammatikproven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snickare",
    "back": "carpenter",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snickaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "snickarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "butikssäljare",
    "back": "store clerk, shop assistant",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läxhjälpare",
    "back": "homework helper, tutor",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "simlärare",
    "back": "swimming instructor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "simläraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "simlärarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "receptionist",
    "back": "receptionist",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "receptionisten",
      "form2": "receptionister",
      "form3": "receptionisterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "grafisk formgivare",
    "back": "graphic designer"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bilmekaniker",
    "back": "car mechanic",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilmekanikern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bilmekanikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bartender",
    "back": "bartender",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bartendern",
      "form2": "bartendertendrar",
      "form3": "bartenderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "händig",
    "back": "dexterous, skillful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "noggrann",
    "back": "careful, meticulous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pedagogisk",
    "back": "pedagogical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kreativ",
    "back": "creative",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "social",
    "back": "social",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "serviceinriktad",
    "back": "service-minded",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bra med barn",
    "back": "good with children"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "teknisk",
    "back": "technical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "omtänksam",
    "back": "caring",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-ma"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konsthistoria",
    "back": "art history",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "maskiningenjör",
    "back": "mechanical engineer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "maskiningenjören",
      "form2": "maskiningenjörer",
      "form3": "maskiningenjörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "KTH = Kungliga Tekniska Högskolan",
    "back": "Royal Institute of Technology"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "extrajobb",
    "back": "extra work, part-time job",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "extrajobbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "extrajobben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "idrottslärare",
    "back": "physical education teacher",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "idrottsläraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "idrottslärarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högstadiet",
    "back": "lower secondary school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "högstadietet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "högstadieten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "miljövetenskap",
    "back": "environmental science",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sabbatsår",
    "back": "gap year",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sabbatsåret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sabbatsåren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pyssla",
    "back": "do crafts",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pysslar",
      "form2": "pysslade",
      "form3": "pysslat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dammsuga",
    "back": "vacuum clean",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dammsugaer",
      "form2": "dammsög",
      "form3": "dammsugit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "saffransrisotto",
    "back": "saffron risotto",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsdag",
    "back": "workday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetsdagen",
      "form2": "arbetsdagar",
      "form3": "arbetsdagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsuppgift",
    "back": "task",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetsuppgiften",
      "form2": "arbetsuppgifter",
      "form3": "arbetsuppgifterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "diska",
    "back": "wash the dishes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "diskar",
      "form2": "diskade",
      "form3": "diskat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vattengympa",
    "back": "water aerobics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hotellfrukost",
    "back": "hotel breakfast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hotellfrukosten",
      "form2": "hotellfrukostar",
      "form3": "hotellfrukostarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vara (-r, var, varit) ledig",
    "back": "be off work, have free time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "organisation",
    "back": "organization",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "organisationen",
      "form2": "organisationer",
      "form3": "organisationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "personal",
    "back": "staff",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spontanansökan",
    "back": "unsolicited application",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spontanansökanen",
      "form2": "spontanansökanningar",
      "form3": "spontanansökanningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "UX-designer",
    "back": "UX designer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "UX-designern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "UX-designerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bransch",
    "back": "industry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "branschen",
      "form2": "branscher",
      "form3": "branscherna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "byrå",
    "back": "agency",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byrån",
      "form2": "byråer",
      "form3": "byråerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kund",
    "back": "customer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kunden",
      "form2": "kunder",
      "form3": "kunderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "undra",
    "back": "wonder",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "undrar",
      "form2": "undrade",
      "form3": "undrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "medarbetare",
    "back": "employee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "medarbetaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "medarbetarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "projekt",
    "back": "project",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "projektet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "projekten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter13_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter13",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vänliga hälsningar",
    "back": "best regards"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fast jobb",
    "back": "permanent position"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "betald semester",
    "back": "paid vacation"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försäkringsbolag",
    "back": "insurance company",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "försäkringsbolaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "försäkringsbolagen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "följande",
    "back": "the following",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båtsemester",
    "back": "boating holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "båtsemestern",
      "form2": "båtsemesterrar",
      "form3": "båtsemesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "campingsemester",
    "back": "camping holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "campingsemestern",
      "form2": "campingsemesterrar",
      "form3": "campingsemesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "cykelsemester",
    "back": "cycling holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "cykelsemestern",
      "form2": "cykelsemesterrar",
      "form3": "cykelsemesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vandringssemester",
    "back": "hiking holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vandringssemestern",
      "form2": "vandringssemesterrar",
      "form3": "vandringssemesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motorcykelsemester",
    "back": "motorcycling holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "motorcykelsemestern",
      "form2": "motorcykelsemesterrar",
      "form3": "motorcykelsemesterrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarstuga",
    "back": "summer cottage, holiday home",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sommarstugan",
      "form2": "sommarstugaor",
      "form3": "sommarstugaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hyra",
    "back": "rent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hyran",
      "form2": "hyraor",
      "form3": "hyraorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stuga",
    "back": "cottage",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stugan",
      "form2": "stugor",
      "form3": "stugorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "statistik",
    "back": "statistics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "längst ner",
    "back": "at the bottom"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gissa",
    "back": "guess",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gissar",
      "form2": "gissade",
      "form3": "gissat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förvånad",
    "back": "surprised",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "något helt annat",
    "back": "something completely different"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fritidshus",
    "back": "holiday home",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fritidshuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fritidshusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hav",
    "back": "sea",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "havet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "haven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "semesterdröm",
    "back": "holiday dream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "semesterdrömmen",
      "form2": "semesterdrömmar",
      "form3": "semesterdrömmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "åka (-er, -te, -t) båt",
    "back": "go boating",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barfota",
    "back": "barefoot",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gräs",
    "back": "grass",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frihet",
    "back": "freedom",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "än",
    "back": "than",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spela (-r, -de, -t) kort",
    "back": "play cards",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lycklig",
    "back": "happy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dröm",
    "back": "dream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "drömmen",
      "form2": "drömmar",
      "form3": "drömmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "måla",
    "back": "paint",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "målar",
      "form2": "målade",
      "form3": "målat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "renovera",
    "back": "renovate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "renoverar",
      "form2": "renoverade",
      "form3": "renoverat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klippa (-er, -te, -t) gräs",
    "back": "cut the grass, mow the lawn",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hugga",
    "back": "chop",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huggaer",
      "form2": "högg",
      "form3": "huggit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ved",
    "back": "wood",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sola",
    "back": "sunbathe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "solar",
      "form2": "solade",
      "form3": "solat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "möjlighet",
    "back": "possibility",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "möjligheten",
      "form2": "möjligheter",
      "form3": "möjligheterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lantställe",
    "back": "country house",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lantstället",
      "form2": "lantställen",
      "form3": "lantställena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "landställe",
    "back": "country house",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "landstället",
      "form2": "landställen",
      "form3": "landställena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarhus",
    "back": "summer house",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sommarhuset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "sommarhusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "torp",
    "back": "croft",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "torpet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "torpen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "shout",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ropar",
      "form2": "ropade",
      "form3": "ropat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lakan",
    "back": "bedsheets",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lakanet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lakanen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "direkt tal",
    "back": "direct speech"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "indirekt tal",
    "back": "indirect speech"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sats",
    "back": "clause",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "satsen",
      "form2": "satser",
      "form3": "satserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bisatsinledare",
    "back": "subordinate conjunction",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bisatsinledaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bisatsinledarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ifall",
    "back": "in case, if",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjortron",
    "back": "cloudberry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjortronet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hjortronen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frågeordsfråga",
    "back": "wh-question",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frågeordsfrågan",
      "form2": "frågeordsfrågaor",
      "form3": "frågeordsfrågaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bilfärja",
    "back": "car ferry",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bilfärjan",
      "form2": "bilfärjaor",
      "form3": "bilfärjaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mås",
    "back": "seagull",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "måsen",
      "form2": "måsar",
      "form3": "måsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrika",
    "back": "scream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skrikaer",
      "form2": "skrek",
      "form3": "skrikit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färjeläge",
    "back": "ferry landing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färjeläget",
      "form2": "färjelägen",
      "form3": "färjelägena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grusväg",
    "back": "gravel road",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grusvägen",
      "form2": "grusvägar",
      "form3": "grusvägarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "träd",
    "back": "tree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trädet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "träden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glittra",
    "back": "glitter, shine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glittrar",
      "form2": "glittrade",
      "form3": "glittrat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "parkera",
    "back": "park",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "parkerar",
      "form2": "parkerade",
      "form3": "parkerat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kliva (-er, klev, klivit) ur",
    "back": "step out",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dass",
    "back": "outhouse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dasset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "dassen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "toalett",
    "back": "toilet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "toaletten",
      "form2": "toaletter",
      "form3": "toaletterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjärta",
    "back": "heart",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjärtat",
      "form2": "hjärtan",
      "form3": "hjärtana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvätta (-r, -de, -t) sig",
    "back": "wash oneself",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skicka",
    "back": "send",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skickar",
      "form2": "skickade",
      "form3": "skickat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nubbe",
    "back": "snaps, flavored vodka",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nubben",
      "form2": "nubbear",
      "form3": "nubbearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vodka",
    "back": "vodka",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "helan",
    "back": "the whole",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halvan",
    "back": "the half",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Skål!",
    "back": "Cheers"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snöre",
    "back": "string",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snöret",
      "form2": "snören",
      "form3": "snörena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snapsvisa",
    "back": "drinking song",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snapsvisan",
      "form2": "snapsvisaor",
      "form3": "snapsvisaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snaps",
    "back": "schnapps",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "snapsen",
      "form2": "snapsar",
      "form3": "snapsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "visa",
    "back": "song",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "visan",
      "form2": "visaor",
      "form3": "visaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "melodi",
    "back": "melody",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "melodin",
      "form2": "melodier",
      "form3": "melodierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Spritmuseum",
    "back": "The Museum of Spirits",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mästerskap",
    "back": "championship",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mästerskapet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "mästerskapen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ont i ryggen",
    "back": "have a backache"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "medan",
    "back": "while",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vaniljbulle",
    "back": "vanilla bun",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vaniljbullen",
      "form2": "vaniljbullear",
      "form3": "vaniljbullearna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kantarell",
    "back": "chanterelles",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kantarellen",
      "form2": "kantareller",
      "form3": "kantarellerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sur",
    "back": "annoyed",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blåbärspaj",
    "back": "blueberry pie",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blåbärspajen",
      "form2": "blåbärspajer",
      "form3": "blåbärspajerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skjuta",
    "back": "shoot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skjutaer",
      "form2": "sköt",
      "form3": "skjutit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vaniljsås",
    "back": "custard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vaniljsåsen",
      "form2": "vaniljsåser",
      "form3": "vaniljsåserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frysa",
    "back": "freeze, be cold",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fryser",
      "form2": "frös",
      "form3": "frusit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bastu",
    "back": "sauna",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bastun",
      "form2": "bastur",
      "form3": "basturna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "naken",
    "back": "naked",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "naket",
        "nakna"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoppa (-r, -de, -t) ner",
    "back": "jump down",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "relativa bisatser",
    "back": "relative clause"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "referera",
    "back": "refer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "refererar",
      "form2": "refererade",
      "form3": "refererat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Toscana",
    "back": "Tuscany",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bottenvåning",
    "back": "ground floor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bottenvåningen",
      "form2": "bottenvåningar",
      "form3": "bottenvåningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trots",
    "back": "although",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidssubjunktion",
    "back": "temporal conjunction",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidssubjunktionen",
      "form2": "tidssubjunktioner",
      "form3": "tidssubjunktionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontrast",
    "back": "contrast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kontrasten",
      "form2": "kontraster",
      "form3": "kontrasterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyansskillnad",
    "back": "nuance",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nyansskillnaden",
      "form2": "nyansskillnader",
      "form3": "nyansskillnaderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spekulation",
    "back": "speculation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spekulationen",
      "form2": "spekulationer",
      "form3": "spekulationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vana",
    "back": "habit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vanan",
      "form2": "vanaor",
      "form3": "vanaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "avsikt",
    "back": "intention",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "avsikten",
      "form2": "avsikter",
      "form3": "avsikterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mål",
    "back": "goal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "målet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "målen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Berlin",
    "back": "Berlin",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lektion",
    "back": "lesson",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lektionen",
      "form2": "lektioner",
      "form3": "lektionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bilradio",
    "back": "car radio",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "replik",
    "back": "reply",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "repliken",
      "form2": "repliker",
      "form3": "replikerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tack för ikväll!",
    "back": "Thank you for a nice evening"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Välkomna till bords!",
    "back": "Welcome to the table"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Ta för er!",
    "back": "Help yourselves"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Det är bra för mig.",
    "back": "I'm good"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "recept",
    "back": "recipe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "receptet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "recepten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skåla",
    "back": "toast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skålar",
      "form2": "skålade",
      "form3": "skålat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rooibos",
    "back": "rooibos",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dra (-r, drog, dragit) sig hemåt",
    "back": "go home",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utrop",
    "back": "exclamation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utropet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "utropen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glasögon",
    "back": "glasses",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komplimang",
    "back": "compliment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "komplimangen",
      "form2": "komplimanger",
      "form3": "komplimangerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "keps",
    "back": "cap",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kepsen",
      "form2": "kepsar",
      "form3": "kepsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blus",
    "back": "blouse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blusen",
      "form2": "blusar",
      "form3": "blusarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nagellack",
    "back": "nail polish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nagellacket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "nagellacken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "armband",
    "back": "bracelet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "armbandet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "armbanden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skärp",
    "back": "belt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skärpet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "skärpen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "örhänge",
    "back": "earring",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "örhänget",
      "form2": "örhängen",
      "form3": "örhängena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vett och etikett",
    "back": "common sense and etiquette"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "expert",
    "back": "expert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "experten",
      "form2": "experter",
      "form3": "experterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kolumn",
    "back": "column",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kolumnen",
      "form2": "kolumner",
      "form3": "kolumnerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma (-er, kom, kommit) i tid",
    "back": "arrive on time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lagom",
    "back": "just enough, the perfect amount",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yttersko",
    "back": "outdoor shoe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ytterskon",
      "form2": "ytterskor",
      "form3": "ytterskorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "värd",
    "back": "host",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "värden",
      "form2": "värdar",
      "form3": "värdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "innesko",
    "back": "indoor shoe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inneskon",
      "form2": "inneskor",
      "form3": "inneskorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "present",
    "back": "gift",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "presenten",
      "form2": "presenter",
      "form3": "presenterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chokladask",
    "back": "box of chocolates",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "chokladasken",
      "form2": "chokladaskar",
      "form3": "chokladaskarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta i hand",
    "back": "shake hands"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "värdinna",
    "back": "hostess",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "värdinnan",
      "form2": "värdinnaor",
      "form3": "värdinnaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "liknande",
    "back": "similar",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "öga",
    "back": "eye",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ögat",
      "form2": "ögaon",
      "form3": "ögaonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tack för maten!",
    "back": "Thank you for the meal"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klar",
    "back": "ready, finished",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "räcka",
    "back": "be enough",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "räckaer",
      "form2": "räckate",
      "form3": "räckat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Tack för senast!",
    "back": "Thank you for a nice evening/dinner/party"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "etikettsregel",
    "back": "rule of etiquette",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "etikettsregeln",
      "form2": "etikettsregler",
      "form3": "etikettsreglerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "dags för",
    "back": "time for"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bli (-r, blev, blivit) över",
    "back": "be left over",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "50-årsfest",
    "back": "50th birthday party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "50-årsfesten",
      "form2": "50-årsfester",
      "form3": "50-årsfesterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inflyttningsfest",
    "back": "housewarming party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inflyttningsfesten",
      "form2": "inflyttningsfester",
      "form3": "inflyttningsfesterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kickoff",
    "back": "launch event",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kickoffen",
      "form2": "kickoffer",
      "form3": "kickofferna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klassfest",
    "back": "class party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klassfesten",
      "form2": "klassfester",
      "form3": "klassfesterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "knytis",
    "back": "potluck",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "knytkalas"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barnkalas",
    "back": "children’s party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "barnkalaset",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "barnkalasen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bröllop",
    "back": "wedding",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bröllopet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bröllopen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "årets",
    "back": "this year's",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tända",
    "back": "light",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tändaer",
      "form2": "tändade",
      "form3": "tändat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grill",
    "back": "grill",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grillen",
      "form2": "grillar",
      "form3": "grillarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äntligen",
    "back": "finally",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotbollsfest",
    "back": "soccer party",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollsfesten",
      "form2": "fotbollsfester",
      "form3": "fotbollsfesterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mot",
    "back": "against",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotbollsplan",
    "back": "soccer/football field",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollsplanen",
      "form2": "fotbollsplaner",
      "form3": "fotbollsplanerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "picknick",
    "back": "picnic",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "picknicken",
      "form2": "picknickar",
      "form3": "picknickarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gymnastiksal",
    "back": "gym hall",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gymnastiksalen",
      "form2": "gymnastiksalar",
      "form3": "gymnastiksalarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spökboll",
    "back": "dodgeball",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vigsel",
    "back": "wedding ceremony",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vigseln",
      "form2": "vigslar",
      "form3": "vigslarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äga (-er, -de, -t) rum",
    "back": "take place",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klädsel",
    "back": "dress code",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klädseln",
      "form2": "klädselar",
      "form3": "klädselarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halvvägs",
    "back": "halfway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "danssko",
    "back": "dance shoe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dansskon",
      "form2": "dansskor",
      "form3": "dansskorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fira",
    "back": "celebrate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "firar",
      "form2": "firade",
      "form3": "firat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "valfri klädsel",
    "back": "no dress code"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Obs!",
    "back": "Note"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "peng",
    "back": "money",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "vard"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "välgörenhet",
    "back": "charity",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "toppendag",
    "back": "great day",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "toppendagen",
      "form2": "toppendagar",
      "form3": "toppendagarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kära",
    "back": "dear",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyfödd",
    "back": "newborn",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "nyfött",
        "nyfödda"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Hoppas det går bra.",
    "back": "Hope it is ok"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klockslag",
    "back": "time (specific time of day)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klockslaget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "klockslagen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sammansättning",
    "back": "compound formation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sammansättningen",
      "form2": "sammansättningar",
      "form3": "sammansättningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vardagligt tal",
    "back": "everyday speech"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "asterisk",
    "back": "asterisk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "asterisken",
      "form2": "asterisker",
      "form3": "asteriskerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fotbollsturnering",
    "back": "soccer/football tournament",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fotbollsturneringen",
      "form2": "fotbollsturneringar",
      "form3": "fotbollsturneringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter14_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter14",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bör",
    "back": "should, must",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "generalisera",
    "back": "generalize",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "generaliserar",
      "form2": "generaliserade",
      "form3": "generaliserat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tyst",
    "back": "silent",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "långt ifrån",
    "back": "far away"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veckonummer",
    "back": "number of the week",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "veckonumret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "veckonumren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "egentid",
    "back": "personal time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Thailand",
    "back": "Thailand",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spårvagn",
    "back": "tram",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spårvagnen",
      "form2": "spårvagnar",
      "form3": "spårvagnarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bubbla",
    "back": "bubble",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bubblan",
      "form2": "bubblaor",
      "form3": "bubblaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klaga",
    "back": "complain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klagar",
      "form2": "klagade",
      "form3": "klagat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nicka",
    "back": "nod",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nickar",
      "form2": "nickade",
      "form3": "nickat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ljus",
    "back": "light",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mörker",
    "back": "darkness",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "mörkret"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sucka",
    "back": "sigh",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "suckar",
      "form2": "suckade",
      "form3": "suckat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "deppig",
    "back": "depressed",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "by",
    "back": "village",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byn",
      "form2": "byar",
      "form3": "byarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nöjd",
    "back": "satisfied",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "nöjt",
        "nöjda"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sten",
    "back": "stone, rock",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stenen",
      "form2": "stenar",
      "form3": "stenarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hotellrum",
    "back": "hotel room",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hotellrummet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "hotellrummen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "exakt",
    "back": "exact",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "personnummer",
    "back": "social security number, identification number",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "personnumret",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "personnumren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "okänd",
    "back": "unknown",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "badplats",
    "back": "beach, bathing spot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "badplatsen",
      "form2": "badplatser",
      "form3": "badplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fatta",
    "back": "understand, grasp",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fattar",
      "form2": "fattade",
      "form3": "fattat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "självständiga pronomen",
    "back": "independent pronouns"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "abstrakt",
    "back": "abstract",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "magsjuk",
    "back": "stomach sick, nauseous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på grund av",
    "back": "because of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smeknamn",
    "back": "nickname",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smeknamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "smeknamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "genomsnittlig",
    "back": "average",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "andranamn",
    "back": "middle name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "andranamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "andranamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trendig",
    "back": "trendy",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "period",
    "back": "period",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "perioden",
      "form2": "perioder",
      "form3": "perioderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "generation",
    "back": "generation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "generationen",
      "form2": "generationer",
      "form3": "generationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kungafamilj",
    "back": "royal family",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kungafamiljen",
      "form2": "kungafamiljer",
      "form3": "kungafamiljerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "idrottare",
    "back": "athlete",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "idrottaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "idrottarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nuförtiden",
    "back": "nowadays",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "unik",
    "back": "unique",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "enorm",
    "back": "enormous",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "djurägare",
    "back": "pet owner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "djurägaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "djurägarena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "döpa",
    "back": "name (a child, for example)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "döpaer",
      "form2": "döpate",
      "form3": "döpat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "släktnamn",
    "back": "surname",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "släktnamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "släktnamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försvinna",
    "back": "disappear",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "försvinnaer",
      "form2": "försvann",
      "form3": "försvunnit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "väderstreck",
    "back": "cardinal directions",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "väderstrecket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "väderstrecken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stödord",
    "back": "key word",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stödordet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "stödorden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "återberätta",
    "back": "retell",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "återberättar",
      "form2": "återberättade",
      "form3": "återberättat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förbjuden",
    "back": "forbidden",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et",
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "enligt lagen",
    "back": "according to the law"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "obehaglig",
    "back": "unpleasant",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "olämplig",
    "back": "inappropriate",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Skatteverket",
    "back": "the Swedish Tax Agency",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "runsten",
    "back": "runestone",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "runstenen",
      "form2": "runstenar",
      "form3": "runstenarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vikingagud",
    "back": "Viking god",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vikingaguden",
      "form2": "vikingagudar",
      "form3": "vikingagudarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krigisk",
    "back": "warlike",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betydelse",
    "back": "meaning",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "betydelsen",
      "form2": "betydelser",
      "form3": "betydelserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spjut",
    "back": "spear",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spjutet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "spjuten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strid",
    "back": "battle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "striden",
      "form2": "strider",
      "form3": "striderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Bibel",
    "back": "Bible",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "reflexiva possessiva pronomen",
    "back": "reflexive possessive pronouns"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "objekt",
    "back": "object",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "objektet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "objekten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "papegoja",
    "back": "parrot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "papegojan",
      "form2": "papegojaor",
      "form3": "papegojaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hamster",
    "back": "hamster",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hamstern",
      "form2": "hamstrar",
      "form3": "hamstrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äppelträd",
    "back": "apple tree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "äppelträdet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "äppelträden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyckel",
    "back": "key",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nyckeln",
      "form2": "nycklar",
      "form3": "nycklarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbelbokad",
    "back": "double booked",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Försäkringskassan",
    "back": "Swedish Social Insurance Agency",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föräldrapenning",
    "back": "parental benefits",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbel",
    "back": "double",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "dubbla"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbla",
    "back": "double",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dubblar",
      "form2": "dubblade",
      "form3": "dubblaat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lamm",
    "back": "lamb",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "lammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "damm",
    "back": "dust",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mata",
    "back": "feed",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "matar",
      "form2": "matade",
      "form3": "matat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matta",
    "back": "carpet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mattan",
      "form2": "mattaor",
      "form3": "mattaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gran",
    "back": "fir tree",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "granen",
      "form2": "granar",
      "form3": "granarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "parkering",
    "back": "parking",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "parkeringen",
      "form2": "parkeringar",
      "form3": "parkeringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvinnlig",
    "back": "female",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbelnamn",
    "back": "double name, hyphenated name",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dubbelnamnet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "dubbelnamnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "manlig",
    "back": "male",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "situation",
    "back": "situation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "situationen",
      "form2": "situationer",
      "form3": "situationerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "egentligen",
    "back": "actually",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bero (-r, -dde, -t) på",
    "back": "be due to",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter15_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter15",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kalla",
    "back": "call",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kallar",
      "form2": "kallade",
      "form3": "kallat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utbildning",
    "back": "education",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utbildningen",
      "form2": "utbildningar",
      "form3": "utbildningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "prov",
    "back": "test",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "provet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "proven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lov",
    "back": "holiday, break",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lovet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "loven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ämne",
    "back": "subject",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ämnet",
      "form2": "ämnen",
      "form3": "ämnena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sträng",
    "back": "strict",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betyg",
    "back": "grade",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "betyget",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "betygen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stressa",
    "back": "stress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stressar",
      "form2": "stressade",
      "form3": "stressat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trumma",
    "back": "drum",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trumman",
      "form2": "trummaor",
      "form3": "trummaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "band",
    "back": "band",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bandet",
      "form2": "banden",
      "form3": "bandena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "storasyster",
    "back": "older sister",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "etta",
    "back": "first grade",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ettan",
      "form2": "ettaor",
      "form3": "ettaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "peppad",
    "back": "excited, motivated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "respekt",
    "back": "respect",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motivera",
    "back": "motivate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "motiverar",
      "form2": "motiverade",
      "form3": "motiverat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "genom att",
    "back": "by, through"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "inte alls",
    "back": "not at all"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utbildningssystem",
    "back": "education system",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utbildningssystemet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "utbildningssystemen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frivillig",
    "back": "voluntary",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "obligatorisk",
    "back": "obligatory",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "termin",
    "back": "term, semester",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "terminen",
      "form2": "terminer",
      "form3": "terminerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grundskola",
    "back": "grade school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grundskolan",
      "form2": "grundskolaor",
      "form3": "grundskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gymnasium",
    "back": "high school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gymnasiet",
      "form2": "gymnasier",
      "form3": "gymnasierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komvux",
    "back": "secondary education for adults",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föreläsning",
    "back": "lecture",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "föreläsningen",
      "form2": "föreläsningar",
      "form3": "föreläsningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "seminarium",
    "back": "seminar",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "seminariet",
      "form2": "seminarier",
      "form3": "seminarierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förskoleklass",
    "back": "preschool class",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förskoleklassen",
      "form2": "förskoleklasser",
      "form3": "förskoleklasserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "årskurs",
    "back": "year, grade",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "årskursen",
      "form2": "årskurser",
      "form3": "årskurserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "biologi",
    "back": "biology",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bedömning",
    "back": "assessment",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bedömningen",
      "form2": "bedömningar",
      "form3": "bedömningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "diskussion",
    "back": "discussion",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "diskussionen",
      "form2": "diskussioner",
      "form3": "diskussionerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "särskild",
    "back": "particular",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "innehålla",
    "back": "contain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "innehållaer",
      "form2": "innehållahöll",
      "form3": "innehållahållit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fritidshem",
    "back": "after-school care",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skoltid",
    "back": "schooling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skoltiden",
      "form2": "skoltider",
      "form3": "skoltiderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kommunal",
    "back": "municipal",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "friskola",
    "back": "independent school, charter school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "friskolan",
      "form2": "friskolaor",
      "form3": "friskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hösttermin",
    "back": "fall semester, autumn term",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "höstterminen",
      "form2": "höstterminer",
      "form3": "höstterminerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vårtermin",
    "back": "spring semester, spring term",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vårterminen",
      "form2": "vårterminer",
      "form3": "vårterminerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jullov",
    "back": "Christmas holiday, Christmas break",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarlov",
    "back": "summer vacation",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höstlov",
    "back": "autumn break",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sportlov",
    "back": "February break",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "påsklov",
    "back": "Easter break",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "påsk",
    "back": "Easter",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lagen säger",
    "back": "the law says"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "icke godkänt",
    "back": "fail"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gymnasieskola",
    "back": "upper secondary school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gymnasieskolan",
      "form2": "gymnasieskolaor",
      "form3": "gymnasieskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hög",
    "back": "high",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma (-er, kom, kommit) in",
    "back": "get admitted to",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "de flesta",
    "back": "most people"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "teoretisk",
    "back": "theoretical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högskoleförberedande",
    "back": "university preparatory",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "naturvetenskapsprogram",
    "back": "science program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "naturvetenskapsprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "naturvetenskapsprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekonomiprogram",
    "back": "business program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ekonomiprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "ekonomiprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yrkesprogram",
    "back": "vocational program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "yrkesprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "yrkesprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fordons- och transportprogram",
    "back": "vehicle and transport program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fordons- och transportprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "fordons- och transportprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "barn- och fritidsprogram",
    "back": "child and leisure program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "barn- och fritidsprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "barn- och fritidsprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gymnasieprogram",
    "back": "upper secondary school program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gymnasieprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "gymnasieprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bland annat",
    "back": "among other things"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samhällskunskap",
    "back": "social studies, civics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "på så sätt",
    "back": "in this way"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läsa (-er, -te, -t) vidare",
    "back": "continue studying",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vuxenutbildning",
    "back": "adult education",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vuxenutbildningen",
      "form2": "vuxenutbildningar",
      "form3": "vuxenutbildningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "folkhögskola",
    "back": "folk high school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "folkhögskolan",
      "form2": "folkhögskolaor",
      "form3": "folkhögskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komplettera",
    "back": "complete",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kompletterar",
      "form2": "kompletterade",
      "form3": "kompletterat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tredjedel",
    "back": "a third",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tredjedelen",
      "form2": "tredjedelar",
      "form3": "tredjedelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studenten",
    "back": "graduation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "studentenen",
      "form2": "studentener",
      "form3": "studentenerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Så här kan det gå till.",
    "back": "Here's how it works"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utspring",
    "back": "graduation ceremony",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utspringet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "utspringen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolgård",
    "back": "schoolyard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolgården",
      "form2": "skolgårdar",
      "form3": "skolgårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lastbil",
    "back": "truck",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lastbilen",
      "form2": "lastbilar",
      "form3": "lastbilarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mottagning",
    "back": "reception",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mottagningen",
      "form2": "mottagningar",
      "form3": "mottagningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "universitetsstudier",
    "back": "university studies",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jurist",
    "back": "lawyer, legal expert",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "juristen",
      "form2": "jurister",
      "form3": "juristerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nivå",
    "back": "level",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nivån",
      "form2": "nivåer",
      "form3": "nivåerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grundnivå",
    "back": "basic level",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kandidatexamen",
    "back": "bachelor's degree",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "avancerad nivå",
    "back": "advanced level"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "masterexamen",
    "back": "master's degree",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "forskarnivå",
    "back": "research level",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "doktorsexamen",
    "back": "doctoral degree, PhD",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yrkeshögskola/YH-utbildning",
    "back": "higher vocational education",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matcha",
    "back": "match",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "matchar",
      "form2": "matchade",
      "form3": "matchat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "behov",
    "back": "need",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "behovet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "behoven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsmarknad",
    "back": "job market",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetsmarknaden",
      "form2": "arbetsmarknader",
      "form3": "arbetsmarknaderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "teori",
    "back": "theory",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "teorin",
      "form2": "teorier",
      "form3": "teorierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "praktik",
    "back": "internship",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsplats",
    "back": "workplace",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "arbetsplatsen",
      "form2": "arbetsplatser",
      "form3": "arbetsplatserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kostnadsfri",
    "back": "free of charge",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-tt",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hyra",
    "back": "rent",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hyran",
      "form2": "hyraor",
      "form3": "hyraorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "finansiera",
    "back": "finance",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "finansierar",
      "form2": "finansierade",
      "form3": "finansierat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studielån",
    "back": "student loan",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "studielånet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "studielånen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stat",
    "back": "state",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "staten",
      "form2": "stater",
      "form3": "staterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "låna (-r, -de, -t) ut",
    "back": "lend",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolgång",
    "back": "schooling",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsliv",
    "back": "working life",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "storebror",
    "back": "older brother",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "storebrorbrodern",
      "form2": "storebrorbröder",
      "form3": "storebrorbröderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fokusera",
    "back": "focus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fokuserar",
      "form2": "fokuserade",
      "form3": "fokuserat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "extraövning",
    "back": "extra exercises",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "extraövningen",
      "form2": "extraövningar",
      "form3": "extraövningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "idrott och hälsa",
    "back": "physical education"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plugghäst",
    "back": "nerd, someone who studies hard",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "plugghästen",
      "form2": "plugghästar",
      "form3": "plugghästarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mattelärare",
    "back": "mathematics teacher",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "historielärare",
    "back": "history teacher",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "historieläraren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "historielärarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "orättvis",
    "back": "unfair",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rädd",
    "back": "afraid",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kassa",
    "back": "cash register",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kassan",
      "form2": "kassaor",
      "form3": "kassaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "garderob",
    "back": "wardrobe",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "garderoben",
      "form2": "garderober",
      "form3": "garderoberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "halvår",
    "back": "half a year",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sugen",
    "back": "eager",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-et",
        "-na"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Chalmers tekniska högskola",
    "back": "Chalmers University of Technology"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tuff",
    "back": "tough",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färdig",
    "back": "finished",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nanoteknik",
    "back": "nanotechnology",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hållbarhet",
    "back": "sustainability",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "taggad",
    "back": "excited, pumped",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-de"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lek",
    "back": "play",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "leken",
      "form2": "lekar",
      "form3": "lekarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sitta (-er, satt, suttit) stilla",
    "back": "sit still",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tonåring",
    "back": "teenager",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tonåringen",
      "form2": "tonåringar",
      "form3": "tonåringarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skoltrött",
    "back": "tired of school, lost motivation",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spela (-r, -de, -t) gitarr",
    "back": "play guitar",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolka",
    "back": "skip school",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolkar",
      "form2": "skolkade",
      "form3": "skolkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gå (-r, gick, gått) ut",
    "back": "go out",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoppa (-r, -de, -t) av",
    "back": "drop out",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "juristprogram",
    "back": "law program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "juristprogrammet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "juristprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "advokatbyrå",
    "back": "law firm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "advokatbyrån",
      "form2": "advokatbyråer",
      "form3": "advokatbyråerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motiverad",
    "back": "motivated",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-e"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "andra chans",
    "back": "second chance"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slacker/slöfock",
    "back": "slacker",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "slacker/slöfocken",
      "form2": "slacker/slöfockar",
      "form3": "slacker/slöfockarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "svenska som andraspråk",
    "back": "Swedish as a second language"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hem- och konsumentkunskap",
    "back": "home economics",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "hemkunskap) (-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "moderna språk",
    "back": "modern languages"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "religionskunskap",
    "back": "religious studies",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "psykologi",
    "back": "psychology",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-n"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "teknik",
    "back": "technology",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bild",
    "back": "art class",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "slöjd",
    "back": "shop class, woodwork",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-en"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "omelett",
    "back": "omelet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "omeletten",
      "form2": "omeletter",
      "form3": "omeletterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utländsk",
    "back": "foreign",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Litauen",
    "back": "Lithuania",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Vilnius",
    "back": "Vilnius",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "byggnadsingenjör",
    "back": "structural engineer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byggnadsingenjören",
      "form2": "byggnadsingenjörer",
      "form3": "byggnadsingenjörerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Warszawa",
    "back": "Warsaw",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Japan",
    "back": "Japan",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högskola",
    "back": "university",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "högskolan",
      "form2": "högskolaor",
      "form3": "högskolaorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frilansa",
    "back": "freelance",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frilansar",
      "form2": "frilansade",
      "form3": "frilansat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "översättare",
    "back": "translator",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "översättaren",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "översättarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvar",
    "back": "remaining",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "managementkonsult",
    "back": "management consultant",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "managementkonsulten",
      "form2": "managementkonsulter",
      "form3": "managementkonsulterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framtidsuttryck",
    "back": "future expressions",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "framtidsuttrycket",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "framtidsuttrycken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "naturlig",
    "back": "natural",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "process",
    "back": "process",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "processen",
      "form2": "processer",
      "form3": "processerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "logisk",
    "back": "logical",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "-t",
        "-a"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "konsekvens",
    "back": "consequence",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konsekvensen",
      "form2": "konsekvenser",
      "form3": "konsekvenserna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "neurokirurg",
    "back": "neurosurgeon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "neurokirurgen",
      "form2": "neurokirurger",
      "form3": "neurokirurgerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tidsadverb",
    "back": "adverbs of time",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tidsadverbet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "tidsadverben"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stadsbyggnad",
    "back": "urban planning",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stadsbyggnaden",
      "form2": "stadsbyggnader",
      "form3": "stadsbyggnaderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter16_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter16",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framtidsplan",
    "back": "plan for the future",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "framtidsplanen",
      "form2": "framtidsplaner",
      "form3": "framtidsplanerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "boende",
    "back": "housing, residence",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvåa",
    "back": "two-room apartment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trappa",
    "back": "stairs",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "balkong",
    "back": "balcony",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kvällssol",
    "back": "evening sun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morgonsol",
    "back": "morning sun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "morgonkaffe",
    "back": "morning coffee",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kollektiv",
    "back": "collective",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "möbel",
    "back": "piece of furniture",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "husbil",
    "back": "motorhome",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leva",
    "back": "live",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "dag för dag",
    "back": "day by day"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förort",
    "back": "suburb",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadsrätt",
    "back": "co-op apartment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hyresrätt",
    "back": "rental apartment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvättstuga",
    "back": "laundry room",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kakelugn",
    "back": "tile stove",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "öppen spis",
    "back": "fireplace"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tomt",
    "back": "garden, yard",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pendla",
    "back": "commute",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skick",
    "back": "condition",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvättmaskin",
    "back": "washing machine",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elda",
    "back": "make a fire",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hyreslägenhet",
    "back": "rental apartment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förstahandskontrakt",
    "back": "primary lease",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadskö",
    "back": "housing queue",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i andra hand",
    "back": "sublet"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inneboende",
    "back": "lodger",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lån",
    "back": "loan",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ägare",
    "back": "owner",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "månadsavgift",
    "back": "monthly fee",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "typ",
    "back": "type",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nyrenoverad",
    "back": "newly renovated",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "renoveringsobjekt",
    "back": "an object for renovation, a run-down place",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uteplats",
    "back": "patio",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "högt i tak",
    "back": "high ceiling"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lågt i tak",
    "back": "low ceiling"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kokvrå",
    "back": "kitchenette",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "badrum",
    "back": "bathroom",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "viss",
    "back": "certain",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "wc",
    "back": "water closet, toilet",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förråd",
    "back": "storage",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "källare",
    "back": "basement",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vind",
    "back": "attic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flerfamiljshus",
    "back": "multi-family house",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gemensam",
    "back": "communal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studentrum",
    "back": "student room, dorm room",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "radhus",
    "back": "semi-detached",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "parhus",
    "back": "semi-detached, two-family house",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "husbåt",
    "back": "houseboat",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "boyta",
    "back": "living space",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ensamstående",
    "back": "single",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "småhus",
    "back": "small house",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "andrahandslägenhet",
    "back": "sublet apartment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pendlingsavstånd",
    "back": "commuting distance",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leta",
    "back": "look for, search",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plus",
    "back": "plus",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "uppvärmning",
    "back": "heating",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sophämtning",
    "back": "garbage removal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sopor",
    "back": "garbage",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "solpanel",
    "back": "solar panel",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kompost",
    "back": "compost",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadsrättförening",
    "back": "condominium association",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förening",
    "back": "co-op",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "avgift",
    "back": "fee",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ränta",
    "back": "interest rate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "amortering",
    "back": "amortization",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regel",
    "back": "rule",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stadgar",
    "back": "bylaws",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "följa",
    "back": "follow",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tågstation",
    "back": "train station",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "solsemester",
    "back": "sun holiday",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skidsemester",
    "back": "skiing holiday",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jämförelse",
    "back": "comparison",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "status",
    "back": "status",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lika",
    "back": "equal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "affisch",
    "back": "poster",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elcykel",
    "back": "electric bicycle",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "moped",
    "back": "moped",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fördel",
    "back": "advantage, pro",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nackdel",
    "back": "disadvantage, con",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förbereda",
    "back": "prepare",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadsannons",
    "back": "housing ad, house listings",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "objekt",
    "back": "property",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spa",
    "back": "spa",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pizzaugn",
    "back": "pizza oven",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "charmig",
    "back": "charming",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tvåplansvilla",
    "back": "two-story villa",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jacuzzi",
    "back": "jacuzzi",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trädäck",
    "back": "wooden deck",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "murad",
    "back": "brick-built",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gångavstånd",
    "back": "walking distance",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "visning",
    "back": "viewing",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "boarea",
    "back": "living area",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "driftkostnad",
    "back": "operating cost",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högstbjudande",
    "back": "highest bidder",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "planritning",
    "back": "floor plan",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "välplanerad",
    "back": "well planned",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lyxig",
    "back": "luxurious",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "marmor",
    "back": "marble",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "exklusiv",
    "back": "exclusive",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "parkettgolv",
    "back": "parquet flooring",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "norrläge",
    "back": "northern exposure",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sittgrupp",
    "back": "seating area",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "renoveringschans",
    "back": "opportunity for renovation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "drömboende",
    "back": "dream home",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "runt hörnet",
    "back": "around the corner"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "öppen planlösning",
    "back": "open floor plan"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "middagsgäst",
    "back": "dinner guest",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "retro",
    "back": "retro",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fungerande",
    "back": "functional",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "originalkök",
    "back": "original kitchen",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "drömkök",
    "back": "dream kitchen",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plastmatta",
    "back": "vinyl flooring",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trägolv",
    "back": "wood floors",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "acceptpris",
    "back": "reserve price",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matbord",
    "back": "dining table",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skåp",
    "back": "cupboard",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fåtölj",
    "back": "armchair",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stol",
    "back": "chair",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrivbord",
    "back": "desk",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "soffbord",
    "back": "coffee table",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "taklampa",
    "back": "ceiling lamp",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bokhylla",
    "back": "bookshelf",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "golvlampa",
    "back": "floorlamp",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrivbordslampa",
    "back": "desk lamp",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krukväxt",
    "back": "potted plant",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utemöbel",
    "back": "outdoor furniture",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "badkar",
    "back": "bathtub",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inredningsdetalj",
    "back": "interior detail",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta reda på",
    "back": "find out"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sovrum",
    "back": "bedroom",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsrum",
    "back": "office",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hall",
    "back": "entrance hallway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "veranda",
    "back": "veranda",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mäklare",
    "back": "broker",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sympatisk",
    "back": "sympathetic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "besiktigat",
    "back": "inspected",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "dra om elen",
    "back": "rewire the electrical system"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_140",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stajlad",
    "back": "styled",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_141",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fräsch",
    "back": "fresh",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_142",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hänga",
    "back": "hang",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_143",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kristallkrona",
    "back": "crystal chandelier",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_144",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gigantisk",
    "back": "gigantic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_145",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gråbeige",
    "back": "gray-beige",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_146",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hörnsoffa",
    "back": "corner sofa",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_147",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hörn",
    "back": "corner",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_148",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "designlampa",
    "back": "designer lamp",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_149",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vägg",
    "back": "wall",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_150",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ordna efter färg",
    "back": "arrange by color"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_151",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spis",
    "back": "stove",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_152",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kylskåp",
    "back": "fridge",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_153",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köksskåp",
    "back": "fridge",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_154",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kakel",
    "back": "tiles",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_155",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pytteliten",
    "back": "tiny",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_156",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gräsklippare",
    "back": "lawnmower",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_157",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "färgburk",
    "back": "paint can",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_158",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fuktig",
    "back": "damp",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_159",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "illa",
    "back": "bad",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_160",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rabatt",
    "back": "flowerbed",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_161",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lägga ett bud",
    "back": "make a bid"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_162",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skriva",
    "back": "sign up",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_163",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "studsmatta",
    "back": "trampoline",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_164",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skälla",
    "back": "bark",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_165",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "se ... ut",
    "back": "look .."
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_166",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "böja",
    "back": "conjugate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_167",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pigg",
    "back": "lively, alert",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_168",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ovanför",
    "back": "above",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_169",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "till höger om",
    "back": "to the right of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_170",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "till vänster om",
    "back": "to the left of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_171",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaffekopp",
    "back": "coffee cup",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_172",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "presentering",
    "back": "presentation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_173",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vertikal",
    "back": "vertical",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_174",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "horisontell",
    "back": "horizontal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_175",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fast",
    "back": "fixed",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_176",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fixerad",
    "back": "fixed, attached",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_177",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "högtalare",
    "back": "speaker",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_178",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "komma överens",
    "back": "agree"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_179",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lånelöfte",
    "back": "mortgage pre-approval",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_180",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leasa",
    "back": "lease",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_181",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "elbil",
    "back": "electric car",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_182",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "besiktningsman",
    "back": "inspector",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_183",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "budget",
    "back": "budget",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_184",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "laddstolpe",
    "back": "charging station",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_185",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "infartsparkering",
    "back": "driveway parking",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_186",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sova på saken",
    "back": "sleep on it"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_187",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kostnad",
    "back": "cost",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_188",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "besiktning",
    "back": "inspection",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_189",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "buda",
    "back": "bid",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_190",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köpare",
    "back": "buyer, customer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_191",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ordna",
    "back": "arrange",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_192",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontant",
    "back": "cash",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_193",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spekulant",
    "back": "prospective buyer, speculator",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_194",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "budgivning",
    "back": "bidding",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_195",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bindande",
    "back": "binding",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_196",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "dra tillbaka",
    "back": "withdraw"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_197",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köpekontrakt",
    "back": "purchase agreement",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_198",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ändra sig",
    "back": "change one's mind"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_199",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ritning",
    "back": "floorplan",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter17_200",
    "chapter": "Chapter17",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kategori",
    "back": "category",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lön",
    "back": "salary",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "omskola",
    "back": "retrain",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "deltid",
    "back": "part-time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flextid",
    "back": "flexible hours",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förmån",
    "back": "benefit",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fortbildning",
    "back": "continuing education",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vabba",
    "back": "(vard) = ta ledigt för vård av sjukt barn, stay home from work to care for a sick child",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "anställd",
    "back": "employee",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjukskriven",
    "back": "on sick leave",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vd",
    "back": "verkställande direktör, CEO",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förkortning",
    "back": "abbreviation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "anställningstrygghet",
    "back": "job security",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "semesterdag",
    "back": "vacation day",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "friskvårdstimme",
    "back": "wellness hour",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pension",
    "back": "pension",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "heltid",
    "back": "full-time",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chef",
    "back": "boss",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förlora",
    "back": "lose",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsgivare",
    "back": "employer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "opinionsinstitut",
    "back": "opinion institute",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "balans",
    "back": "balance",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "flexibla arbetstider",
    "back": "flexible working hours"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bråk",
    "back": "argument, fight",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "majoritet",
    "back": "majority",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tanke",
    "back": "thought",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "karriär",
    "back": "career",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utvecklare",
    "back": "developer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lämna",
    "back": "leave",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hämta",
    "back": "pick up",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trygg",
    "back": "secure, safe",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "statlig",
    "back": "governmental, state",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "myndighet",
    "back": "authority",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "strukturerad",
    "back": "structured",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "protokoll",
    "back": "protocol",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "oinspirerande",
    "back": "uninspiring",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kundtjänst",
    "back": "customer service",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "service",
    "back": "service",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "helt och hållet",
    "back": "entirely, completely"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsnarkoman",
    "back": "workaholic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jämt",
    "back": "consistently",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mellanchef",
    "back": "middle manager",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fikapaus",
    "back": "(= kaffepaus) coffee break",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta paus",
    "back": "take a break"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "slå upp",
    "back": "look up"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaffeapparat",
    "back": "coffee maker",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "kratta löv",
    "back": "rake leaves"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta upp båten",
    "back": "bring in the boat"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "apropå",
    "back": "speaking of",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "agent",
    "back": "agent",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fel",
    "back": "wrong",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hoppsan",
    "back": "oops",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trevlig",
    "back": "nice, friendly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hålla igång",
    "back": "keep going"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samtal",
    "back": "conversation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förresten",
    "back": "incidentally",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "avsluta",
    "back": "finish, end",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pryl",
    "back": "gadget, thing",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "apparat",
    "back": "device",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kopieringsmaskin",
    "back": "copier, copy machine",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kortläsare",
    "back": "card reader",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "projektor",
    "back": "projector",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaffebryggare",
    "back": "coffee maker",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "diskmaskin",
    "back": "dishwasher",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kanna",
    "back": "pot",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hälla",
    "back": "pour",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "markering",
    "back": "mark",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skopa",
    "back": "scoop",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trycka",
    "back": "press",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "knapp",
    "back": "button",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "timer",
    "back": "timer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "slå på",
    "back": "turn on"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "matchande",
    "back": "matching",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "port",
    "back": "port",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pc",
    "back": "PC",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "adapter",
    "back": "adapter",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vaktmästare",
    "back": "caretaker",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fjärrkontroll",
    "back": "remote control",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "personlig",
    "back": "personal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kod",
    "back": "code",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dubbelsidig",
    "back": "double sided",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "reception",
    "back": "reception",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fylla på",
    "back": "refill"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "korridor",
    "back": "corridor, hallway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "it-avdelning",
    "back": "IT department",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vara sist",
    "back": "be last"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "larm",
    "back": "alarm",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hemlig",
    "back": "secret",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "telefonsamtal",
    "back": "phone conversation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "övrig",
    "back": "other",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kö",
    "back": "queue, line",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bussbolag",
    "back": "bus company",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "längesedan",
    "back": "a long time ago",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "betalkort",
    "back": "credit card, debit card",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spärra",
    "back": "block",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "störa",
    "back": "disturb",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ingå",
    "back": "be included",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fikarum",
    "back": "break room",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "Jag är ledsen.",
    "back": "I’m sorry"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ha fullt upp",
    "back": "be kept busy"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ge upp",
    "back": "give up"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "senaste",
    "back": "latest",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spellista",
    "back": "playlist",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hörlurar",
    "back": "earphones",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "personalavdelning",
    "back": "human resources department",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "support",
    "back": "support",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "var god dröj",
    "back": "please hold"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sitta i telefon",
    "back": "be on the phone"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "återkomma",
    "back": "get back, return",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekonomiavdelning",
    "back": "finance department",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "formell",
    "back": "formal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mall",
    "back": "template",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kontaktuppgift",
    "back": "contact information",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tandklinik",
    "back": "dental clinic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leverans",
    "back": "delivery",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "reduktion",
    "back": "reduction",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "assimilation",
    "back": "assimilation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förändring",
    "back": "change",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "binda",
    "back": "bind",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ödla",
    "back": "lizard",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "insekt",
    "back": "insect",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "grädde",
    "back": "cream",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "badkläder",
    "back": "swimwear",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tydlig",
    "back": "clear",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ämnesrad",
    "back": "subject line",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hälsningsfras",
    "back": "greeting",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "modell",
    "back": "model",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "anmäla",
    "back": "report, register",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vabb",
    "back": "stay home from work to care for a sick child",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjukdom",
    "back": "illness",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "offert",
    "back": "quote",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ledighet",
    "back": "time off",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ledighetsansökan",
    "back": "leave application",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter18_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter18",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vikarie",
    "back": "substitute",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kropp",
    "back": "body",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kroppen",
      "form2": "kroppar",
      "form3": "kropparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arm",
    "back": "arm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "armen",
      "form2": "armar",
      "form3": "armarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "häl",
    "back": "heel",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hälen",
      "form2": "hälar",
      "form3": "hälarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hals",
    "back": "throat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "halsen",
      "form2": "halsar",
      "form3": "halsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "knä",
    "back": "knee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "knät",
      "form2": "knän",
      "form3": "knäna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "näsa",
    "back": "nose",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "näsan",
      "form2": "näsor",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "axel",
    "back": "shoulder",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "axeln",
      "form2": "axlar",
      "form3": "axlarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bröst",
    "back": "chest",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bröstet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "brösten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svårt att andas",
    "back": "hard to breathe",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huvud",
    "back": "head",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "huvudet",
      "form2": "huvuden",
      "form3": "huvudena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "öra",
    "back": "ear",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "örat",
      "form2": "öron",
      "form3": "öronen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ögon",
    "back": "eye",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ögat",
      "form2": "ögon",
      "form3": "ögonen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mun",
    "back": "mouth",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "munnen",
      "form2": "munnar",
      "form3": "munnarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tand",
    "back": "tooth",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tanden",
      "form2": "tänder",
      "form3": "tänderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tunga",
    "back": "tongue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tungan",
      "form2": "tungor",
      "form3": "tungorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mage",
    "back": "stomach",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "magen",
      "form2": "magar",
      "form3": "magarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rygg",
    "back": "back",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ryggen",
      "form2": "ryggar",
      "form3": "ryggarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hand",
    "back": "hand",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "handen",
      "form2": "händer",
      "form3": "händerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "finger",
    "back": "finger",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fingret",
      "form2": "fingrar",
      "form3": "fingrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ben",
    "back": "leg",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "benet",
      "form2": "ben",
      "form3": "benen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fot",
    "back": "foot",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "foten",
      "form2": "fötter",
      "form3": "fötterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hjärta",
    "back": "heart",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjärtat",
      "form2": "hjärtan",
      "form3": "hjärtana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lungor",
    "back": "lungs",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lungen",
      "form2": "lungor",
      "form3": "lungorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ont i magen",
    "back": "stomach ache",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ont i huvudet",
    "back": "headache",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ont i ryggen",
    "back": "back pain",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ont i halsen",
    "back": "sore throat",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "feber",
    "back": "fever",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "febern",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "feberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hosta",
    "back": "cough",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hostan",
      "form2": "hostor",
      "form3": "hostorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förkylning",
    "back": "cold",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förkylningen",
      "form2": "förkylningar",
      "form3": "förkylningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "allergi",
    "back": "allergy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "allergin",
      "form2": "allergier",
      "form3": "allergierna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skada",
    "back": "injury",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skadan",
      "form2": "skador",
      "form3": "skadorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blod",
    "back": "blood",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blodet",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": "bloden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjukhus",
    "back": "hospital",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjukhuset",
      "form2": "sjukhus",
      "form3": "sjukhusen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läkare",
    "back": "doctor",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läkaren",
      "form2": "läkare",
      "form3": "läkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjuksköterska",
    "back": "nurse",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjuksköterskan",
      "form2": "sjuksköterskor",
      "form3": "sjuksköterskorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "medicin",
    "back": "medicine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "medicinen",
      "form2": "mediciner",
      "form3": "medicinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "recept",
    "back": "prescription",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "receptet",
      "form2": "recept",
      "form3": "recepten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vårdcentral",
    "back": "health center",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vårdcentralen",
      "form2": "vårdcentraler",
      "form3": "vårdcentralerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta medicin",
    "back": "take medicine",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "boka tid",
    "back": "book an appointment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "gå till läkaren",
    "back": "go to the doctor",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "känna sig sjuk",
    "back": "feel sick",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "smärta",
    "back": "pain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "smärtan",
      "form2": "smärtor",
      "form3": "smärtorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "symptom",
    "back": "symptom",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "symptomet",
      "form2": "symptom",
      "form3": "symptomen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "apotek",
    "back": "pharmacy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "apoteket",
      "form2": "apotek",
      "form3": "apoteken"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tablett",
    "back": "tablet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tabletten",
      "form2": "tabletter",
      "form3": "tabletterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vaccin",
    "back": "vaccine",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vaccinet",
      "form2": "vacciner",
      "form3": "vaccinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "undersökning",
    "back": "examination",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "undersökningen",
      "form2": "undersökningar",
      "form3": "undersökningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjukdom",
    "back": "illness",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjukdomen",
      "form2": "sjukdomar",
      "form3": "sjukdomarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sköta",
    "back": "take care of",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sköter",
      "form2": "skötte",
      "form3": "skött"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vila",
    "back": "rest",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vilar",
      "form2": "vilade",
      "form3": "vilat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frisk",
    "back": "healthy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "friskt",
      "form2": "friska",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sjuk",
    "back": "sick",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sjukt",
      "form2": "sjuka",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bli frisk",
    "back": "get well",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vara sjuk",
    "back": "be sick",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "må dåligt",
    "back": "feel unwell",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "må bra",
    "back": "feel well",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "yr",
    "back": "dizzy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "yrt",
      "form2": "yra",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trött",
    "back": "tired",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "trött",
      "form2": "trötta",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "svag",
    "back": "weak",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svagt",
      "form2": "svaga",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "illamående",
    "back": "nauseous",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "illamående",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "värk",
    "back": "ache",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "värken",
      "form2": "värkar",
      "form3": "värkarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ha ont",
    "back": "be in pain",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter19_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter19",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta hand om",
    "back": "take care of",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "notis",
    "back": "news item",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rubrik",
    "back": "headline",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "underrubrik",
    "back": "subheading",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stiga",
    "back": "rise",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blixthalka",
    "back": "black ice",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "guldvinst",
    "back": "gold win, gold medal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetslöshet",
    "back": "unemployment",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå ner",
    "back": "go down"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "överraskning",
    "back": "surprise",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "urtidsdjur",
    "back": "prehistoric animal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "oväntad",
    "back": "unexpected",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fynd",
    "back": "discovery, find",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vind",
    "back": "wind",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hockeymästare",
    "back": "hockey champion",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skånsk",
    "back": "from Skåne (southern Sweden), Scanian",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "monster",
    "back": "monster",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bostadslån",
    "back": "mortgage",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kaos",
    "back": "chaos",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trafik",
    "back": "traffic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arbetsförmedling",
    "back": "employment agency",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "riksbank",
    "back": "the national bank",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "meddela",
    "back": "announce",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höja",
    "back": "raise",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "styrränta",
    "back": "key interest rate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "procentenhet",
    "back": "percentage point",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "chefsekonom",
    "back": "chief economist",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förvånad",
    "back": "surprised",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höjning",
    "back": "raise",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rekordlåg",
    "back": "record low",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "binda",
    "back": "bind",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "marginal",
    "back": "margin, leeway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "succé",
    "back": "success",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "scen",
    "back": "stage, scene",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "göra comeback",
    "back": "come back, make a comeback"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "applåd",
    "back": "applause",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regi",
    "back": "direction",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "scenografi",
    "back": "set design, scenography",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föreställning",
    "back": "performance, show",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "upptäcka",
    "back": "discover",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fossil",
    "back": "fossil",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dinosaurie",
    "back": "dinosaur",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "huggtand",
    "back": "fang",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rovdjur",
    "back": "predator",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "art",
    "back": "species",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vara släkt med",
    "back": "be related to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "upptäckt",
    "back": "discovery",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "arkeolog",
    "back": "archaeologist",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ställa ut",
    "back": "exhibit"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "motorväg",
    "back": "highway",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ishalka",
    "back": "icy road conditions",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vinterdäck",
    "back": "winter tires",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "köra i diket",
    "back": "drive into a ditch"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krocka",
    "back": "crash",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "allvarlig",
    "back": "serious",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skadad",
    "back": "wounded",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försening",
    "back": "delay",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "busstrafik",
    "back": "bus traffic",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flyta",
    "back": "float",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kuvert",
    "back": "envelope",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skraplott",
    "back": "scratch-off ticket",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skrap",
    "back": "a scratch",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "storvinst",
    "back": "big win",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nationalpark",
    "back": "national park",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förstasida",
    "back": "front page",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "riva",
    "back": "tear, demolish",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "onyttig",
    "back": "unhealthy",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sämre",
    "back": "worse",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kakljud",
    "back": "cookie sound",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bankanställd",
    "back": "bank employee",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stjäla",
    "back": "steal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ekonominyheter",
    "back": "financial news",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "börs",
    "back": "stock exchange",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "euro",
    "back": "euro",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dollar",
    "back": "dollar",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "stå i",
    "back": "is worth"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inflation",
    "back": "inflation",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Norrland",
    "back": "Norrland, northern region of Sweden",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Svealand",
    "back": "Svealand, central region of Sweden",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Götaland",
    "back": "Götaland, southern region of Sweden",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sändning",
    "back": "broadcast",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skandal",
    "back": "scandal",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vetenskapsnyhet",
    "back": "science news",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "demonstrera",
    "back": "demonstrate",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kulturhistoriker",
    "back": "cultural historian",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "roa sig",
    "back": "amuse oneself"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "namninsamling",
    "back": "petition",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rädda",
    "back": "save, rescue",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "demonstrant",
    "back": "demonstrator, protester",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kamp",
    "back": "struggle, fight",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "undersöka",
    "back": "investigate, examine",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bita",
    "back": "bite",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "småkaka",
    "back": "cookie",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "testperson",
    "back": "test subject, participant",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bedöma",
    "back": "assess",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "onödig",
    "back": "unnecessary",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bageriindustri",
    "back": "bakery industry",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "otrevlig",
    "back": "unpleasant",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "trettiosjuårig",
    "back": "thirty-seven-year-old",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "packa upp",
    "back": "unpack"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bland",
    "back": "among",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_101",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "giftspindel",
    "back": "poisonous spider",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_102",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spindel",
    "back": "spider",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_103",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glasburk",
    "back": "glass jar",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_104",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spindelexpert",
    "back": "spider expert",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_105",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "krypa in",
    "back": "crawl in"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_106",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "terrarium",
    "back": "terrarium",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_107",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "spela in",
    "back": "record"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_108",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "omväxlande väder",
    "back": "changeable weather"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_109",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varierad",
    "back": "varied",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_110",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "årstid",
    "back": "season",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_111",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "höst",
    "back": "autumn, fall",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_112",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vinter",
    "back": "winter",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_113",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ostadig",
    "back": "unsteady",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_114",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "aprilväder",
    "back": "April weather, unsteady weather",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_115",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "moln",
    "back": "cloud",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_116",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dygnsmedeltemperatur",
    "back": "daily average temperature",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_117",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "grader Celsius",
    "back": "degrees Celsius, degrees centigrade"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_118",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rekord",
    "back": "record",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_119",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "regnig",
    "back": "rainy",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_120",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "blåsig",
    "back": "windy",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_121",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fast",
    "back": "but",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_122",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minusgrad",
    "back": "negative degree",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_123",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "snöig",
    "back": "snowy",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_124",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mild",
    "back": "mild",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_125",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Sibirien",
    "back": "Siberia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_126",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Golfströmmen",
    "back": "the Gulf Stream",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_127",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Mexiko",
    "back": "Mexico",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_128",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "Skandinavien",
    "back": "Scandinavia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_129",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förvånande",
    "back": "surprising",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_130",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ankomst",
    "back": "arrival",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_131",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "definition",
    "back": "definition",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_132",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "solens upp- och nedgång",
    "back": "sunrise and sunset"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_133",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarsolstånd",
    "back": "summer solstice",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_134",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vintersolstånd",
    "back": "winter solstice",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_135",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ull",
    "back": "wool",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_136",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lager",
    "back": "layer",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_137",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta av",
    "back": "take off"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_138",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tjock",
    "back": "thick",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter20_139",
    "chapter": "Chapter20",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dryck",
    "back": "drink",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "röd",
    "back": "red",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rött",
      "form2": "röda",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "blå",
    "back": "blue",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "blått",
      "form2": "blåa",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "grön",
    "back": "green",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grönt",
      "form2": "gröna",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "gul",
    "back": "yellow",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "gult",
      "form2": "gula",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "svart",
    "back": "black",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "svart",
      "form2": "svarta",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "vit",
    "back": "white",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vitt",
      "form2": "vita",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "brun",
    "back": "brown",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "brunt",
      "form2": "bruna",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "rosa",
    "back": "pink",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rosa",
      "form2": "rosa",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "lila",
    "back": "purple",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lila",
      "form2": "lila",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "orange",
    "back": "orange",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "orange",
      "form2": "orange",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "grå",
    "back": "gray",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "grått",
      "form2": "gråa",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "beige",
    "back": "beige",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "beige",
      "form2": "beige",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "turkos",
    "back": "turquoise",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "turkost",
      "form2": "turkosa",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "silver",
    "back": "silver",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "silver",
      "form2": "silver",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "guld",
    "back": "gold",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "guld",
      "form2": "guld",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "mörk",
    "back": "dark",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mörkt",
      "form2": "mörka",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "ljus",
    "back": "light",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ljust",
      "form2": "ljusa",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "färgglad",
    "back": "colorful",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "färgglatt",
      "form2": "färgglada",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "randig",
    "back": "striped",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "randigt",
      "form2": "randiga",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "color"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "adjective",
    "front": "prickig",
    "back": "spotted",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "prickigt",
      "form2": "prickiga",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "cirkel",
    "back": "circle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "cirkeln",
      "form2": "cirklar",
      "form3": "cirklarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "fyrkant",
    "back": "square",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fyrkanten",
      "form2": "fyrkanter",
      "form3": "fyrkanterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "triangel",
    "back": "triangle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "triangeln",
      "form2": "trianglar",
      "form3": "trianglarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "rektangel",
    "back": "rectangle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rektangeln",
      "form2": "rektanglar",
      "form3": "rektanglarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "oval",
    "back": "oval",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ovalen",
      "form2": "ovaler",
      "form3": "ovalerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kub",
    "back": "cube",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kuben",
      "form2": "kuber",
      "form3": "kuberna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "sfär",
    "back": "sphere",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sfären",
      "form2": "sfärer",
      "form3": "sfärerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "pyramid",
    "back": "pyramid",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pyramiden",
      "form2": "pyramider",
      "form3": "pyramiderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "stjärna",
    "back": "star",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stjärnan",
      "form2": "stjärnor",
      "form3": "stjärnorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "hjärta",
    "back": "heart",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hjärtat",
      "form2": "hjärtan",
      "form3": "hjärtana"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "linje",
    "back": "line",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "linjen",
      "form2": "linjer",
      "form3": "linjerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "punkt",
    "back": "point",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "punkten",
      "form2": "punkter",
      "form3": "punkterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "hörn",
    "back": "corner",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hörnet",
      "form2": "hörn",
      "form3": "hörnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kant",
    "back": "edge",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kanten",
      "form2": "kanter",
      "form3": "kanterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "diamant",
    "back": "diamond",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "diamanten",
      "form2": "diamanter",
      "form3": "diamanterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "halvcirkel",
    "back": "semicircle",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "halvcirkeln",
      "form2": "halvcirklar",
      "form3": "halvcirklarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "polygon",
    "back": "polygon",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "polygonen",
      "form2": "polygoner",
      "form3": "polygonerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kon",
    "back": "cone",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konen",
      "form2": "koner",
      "form3": "konerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "cylinder",
    "back": "cylinder",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "cylindern",
      "form2": "cylindrar",
      "form3": "cylindrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "shape"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "båge",
    "back": "arc",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bågen",
      "form2": "bågar",
      "form3": "bågarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "äpple",
    "back": "apple",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "äpplet",
      "form2": "äpplen",
      "form3": "äpplena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "banan",
    "back": "banana",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bananen",
      "form2": "bananer",
      "form3": "bananerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "apelsin",
    "back": "orange",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "apelsinen",
      "form2": "apelsiner",
      "form3": "apelsinerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "bröd",
    "back": "bread",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "brödet",
      "form2": "bröd",
      "form3": "bröden"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "ost",
    "back": "cheese",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "osten",
      "form2": "ostar",
      "form3": "ostarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "mjölk",
    "back": "milk",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mjölken",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "vatten",
    "back": "water",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vattnet",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kaffe",
    "back": "coffee",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kaffet",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "te",
    "back": "tea",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "teet",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kött",
    "back": "meat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köttet",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kyckling",
    "back": "chicken",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kycklingen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "fisk",
    "back": "fish",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fisken",
      "form2": "fiskar",
      "form3": "fiskarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "ris",
    "back": "rice",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "riset",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "pasta",
    "back": "pasta",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pastan",
      "form2": "pastor",
      "form3": "pastorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "potatis",
    "back": "potato",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "potatisen",
      "form2": "potatisar",
      "form3": "potatisarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "soppa",
    "back": "soup",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "soppan",
      "form2": "soppor",
      "form3": "sopporna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "sallad",
    "back": "salad",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "salladen",
      "form2": "sallader",
      "form3": "salladerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "ägg",
    "back": "egg",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ägget",
      "form2": "ägg",
      "form3": "äggen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "glass",
    "back": "ice cream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "glassen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "choklad",
    "back": "chocolate",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "chokladen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "skjorta",
    "back": "shirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skjortan",
      "form2": "skjortor",
      "form3": "skjortorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "byxor",
    "back": "pants",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byxorna",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "jacka",
    "back": "jacket",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jackan",
      "form2": "jackor",
      "form3": "jackorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "klänning",
    "back": "dress",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klänningen",
      "form2": "klänningar",
      "form3": "klänningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kjol",
    "back": "skirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kjolen",
      "form2": "kjolar",
      "form3": "kjolarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "tröja",
    "back": "sweater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tröjan",
      "form2": "tröjor",
      "form3": "tröjorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "t-shirt",
    "back": "t-shirt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "t-shirten",
      "form2": "t-shirts",
      "form3": "t-shirterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kappa",
    "back": "coat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kappan",
      "form2": "kappor",
      "form3": "kapporna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "mössa",
    "back": "hat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "mössan",
      "form2": "mössor",
      "form3": "mössorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "hatt",
    "back": "hat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hatten",
      "form2": "hattar",
      "form3": "hattarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "skor",
    "back": "shoes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skorna",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "strumpor",
    "back": "socks",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "strumporna",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "handskar",
    "back": "gloves",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "handskarna",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "scarf",
    "back": "scarf",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "scarfen",
      "form2": "scarfer",
      "form3": "scarferna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "bälte",
    "back": "belt",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bältet",
      "form2": "bälten",
      "form3": "bältena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "jeans",
    "back": "jeans",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jeansen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "shorts",
    "back": "shorts",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "shortsen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "kostym",
    "back": "suit",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kostymen",
      "form2": "kostymer",
      "form3": "kostymerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "pyjamas",
    "back": "pajamas",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pyjamasen",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter21_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter21",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "tags": [
      "clothing"
    ],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "noun",
    "front": "stövlar",
    "back": "boots",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stövlarna",
      "form2": "-",
      "form3": "-"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "borste",
    "back": "brushes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "borsten",
      "form2": "borstar",
      "form3": "borstarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "orolig",
    "back": "worried",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "oroligt",
        "oroliga"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lägga",
    "back": "lay",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lägger",
      "form2": "lade",
      "form3": "lagt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dags",
    "back": "time to (do something)",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "äta",
    "back": "eaten",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "äter",
      "form2": "åt",
      "form3": "ätit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tänka",
    "back": "thinking",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tänker",
      "form2": "tänkte",
      "form3": "tänkt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "kunna",
    "back": "be able to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hålla",
    "back": "holding",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "håller",
      "form2": "höll",
      "form3": "hållit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bredvid",
    "back": "next to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "mörk",
    "back": "dark",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "mörkt",
        "mörka"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "natt",
    "back": "the night",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "natten",
      "form2": "nätter",
      "form3": "nätterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kasta",
    "back": "throws",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kastar",
      "form2": "kastade",
      "form3": "kastat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "frukost",
    "back": "breakfast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "frukosten",
      "form2": "frukostar",
      "form3": "frukostarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stolt",
    "back": "proud",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "stolt",
        "stolta"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stanna",
    "back": "stay",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stannar",
      "form2": "stannade",
      "form3": "stannat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stund",
    "back": "while",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "stunden",
      "form2": "stunder",
      "form3": "stunderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "köpa",
    "back": "buy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "köper",
      "form2": "köpte",
      "form3": "köpt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "utflykt",
    "back": "excursion",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "utflykten",
      "form2": "utflykter",
      "form3": "utflykterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "djur",
    "back": "animal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "djuret",
      "form2": "djur",
      "form3": "djuren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bondgård",
    "back": "farm",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bondgården",
      "form2": "bondgårdar",
      "form3": "bondgårdarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "längst fram",
    "back": "at the front"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "träffa",
    "back": "meet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "träffar",
      "form2": "träffade",
      "form3": "träffat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bonde",
    "back": "the farmer",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bonden",
      "form2": "bönder",
      "form3": "bönderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "unge",
    "back": "kids",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ungen",
      "form2": "ungar",
      "form3": "ungarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kalv",
    "back": "calves",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kalven",
      "form2": "kalvar",
      "form3": "kalvarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "föl",
    "back": "foal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fölet",
      "form2": "föl",
      "form3": "fölen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kliva ur",
    "back": "getting out",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kliver ur",
      "form2": "klev ur",
      "form3": "klivit ur"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tyst",
    "back": "quiet",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "tyst",
        "tysta"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "stilla",
    "back": "still",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fortsätta",
    "back": "continues",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fortsätter",
      "form2": "fortsatte",
      "form3": "fortsatt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "växa",
    "back": "growing",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "växer",
      "form2": "växte",
      "form3": "vuxit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tugga",
    "back": "chews",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tuggar",
      "form2": "tuggade",
      "form3": "tuggat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "hela tiden",
    "back": "all the time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tuggummi",
    "back": "chewing gum",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tuggummit",
      "form2": "tuggummin",
      "form3": "tuggummina"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "idisslare",
    "back": "ruminants",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "idisslaren",
      "form2": "idisslare",
      "form3": "idisslarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bred",
    "back": "wide",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "brett",
        "breda"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "leda till",
    "back": "leads to",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "leder till",
      "form2": "ledde till",
      "form3": "lett till"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "framför",
    "back": "in front"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fler",
    "back": "more",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "annan",
    "back": "other",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "annat",
        "andra"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "intill",
    "back": "next to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klippa av",
    "back": "cut off",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klipper av",
      "form2": "klippte av",
      "form3": "klippt av"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ull",
    "back": "wool",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ullen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "päls",
    "back": "fur",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pälsen",
      "form2": "pälsar",
      "form3": "pälsarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "år",
    "back": "the year",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "året",
      "form2": "år",
      "form3": "åren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "använda",
    "back": "uses",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "använder",
      "form2": "använde",
      "form3": "använt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "garn",
    "back": "yarn",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "garnet",
      "form2": "garn",
      "form3": "garnerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "peka",
    "back": "points",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pekar",
      "form2": "pekade",
      "form3": "pekat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fot",
    "back": "feet",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "foten",
      "form2": "fötter",
      "form3": "fötterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter22_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter22",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hov",
    "back": "hooves",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hoven",
      "form2": "hovar",
      "form3": "hovarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sliten",
    "back": "worn out",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "slitet",
        "slitna"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "därför",
    "back": "therefore",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "järn",
    "back": "iron",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "järnet",
      "form2": "järn",
      "form3": "järnen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "platt",
    "back": "flat",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "platt",
        "platta"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spika fast",
    "back": "nails firmly",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spikar fast",
      "form2": "spikade fast",
      "form3": "spikat fast"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ont",
    "back": "hurt",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nagel",
    "back": "nails",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nageln",
      "form2": "naglar",
      "form3": "naglarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jultröja",
    "back": "christmas sweater",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jultröjan",
      "form2": "jultröjor",
      "form3": "jultröjorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "julkula",
    "back": "christmas ball",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "julkulan",
      "form2": "julklor",
      "form3": "julklorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "adventsljusstake",
    "back": "advent candlestick",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "adventsljusstaken",
      "form2": "adventsljusstakar",
      "form3": "adventsljusstakarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lussekatt",
    "back": "lussecat",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lussekattens",
      "form2": "lussekatter",
      "form3": "lussekatterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "julafton",
    "back": "christmas eve",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "julaftonen",
      "form2": "julaftnar",
      "form3": "julaftnarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "julkalender",
    "back": "advent calendar",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "julkalendern",
      "form2": "julkalendrar",
      "form3": "julkalendrarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "pepparkaka",
    "back": "gingerbread",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "pepparkakan",
      "form2": "pepparkakor",
      "form3": "pepparkakorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "God jul!",
    "back": "Merry christmas!"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lucia",
    "back": "lucia",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jultomte",
    "back": "santa claus",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jultomten",
      "form2": "jultomtar",
      "form3": "jultomtarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bara",
    "back": "only",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skoj",
    "back": "fun",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samla",
    "back": "collects",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "samlar",
      "form2": "samlade",
      "form3": "samlat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kille",
    "back": "guy",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "killen",
      "form2": "killar",
      "form3": "killarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "shouts",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ropar",
      "form2": "ropade",
      "form3": "ropat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "heja",
    "back": "cheers",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "hejar",
      "form2": "hejade",
      "form3": "hejat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "efter en stund",
    "back": "after a while"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spelare",
    "back": "the players",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "spelaren",
      "form2": "spelare",
      "form3": "spelarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "vila",
    "back": "to rest"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "byta",
    "back": "changes",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "byter",
      "form2": "bytte",
      "form3": "bytt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "glad",
    "back": "cheerful",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "glatt",
        "glada"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sparka",
    "back": "kicked",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sparkar",
      "form2": "sparkade",
      "form3": "sparkat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sitt eget",
    "back": "his own"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_031",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "på",
    "back": "on",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_032",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kon",
    "back": "cones",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "konen",
      "form2": "koner",
      "form3": "konerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_033",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lätt hänt",
    "back": "easily happened"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_034",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "båda",
    "back": "both",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_035",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "flera",
    "back": "several",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_036",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "just då",
    "back": "right then"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_037",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plan",
    "back": "field",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "planen",
      "form2": "planer",
      "form3": "planerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_038",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "överraskning",
    "back": "surprise",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "överraskningen",
      "form2": "överraskningar",
      "form3": "överraskningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_039",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "spännande",
    "back": "exciting",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_040",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hemligt",
    "back": "secretly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_041",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ställa sig",
    "back": "stands",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "ställer sig",
      "form2": "ställde sig",
      "form3": "ställt sig"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_042",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "klump",
    "back": "lump",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "klumpen",
      "form2": "klumpar",
      "form3": "klumparna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_043",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "varsin sak",
    "back": "each thing"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_044",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "bärnsten",
    "back": "amber",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bärnstenen",
      "form2": "bärnstenar",
      "form3": "bärnstenarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_045",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bara",
    "back": "only"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_046",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bara heter så",
    "back": "just called that"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_047",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "komma ihåg",
    "back": "remember",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kommer ihåg",
      "form2": "kom ihåg",
      "form3": "kommit ihåg"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_048",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "havets botten",
    "back": "bottom of the sea"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_049",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "följa med vågorna",
    "back": "follow the waves"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_050",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sand",
    "back": "the sand",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sanden",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_051",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "låg den där",
    "back": "was it there"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_052",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inuti",
    "back": "inside",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_053",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "djur",
    "back": "animal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "djuret",
      "form2": "djur",
      "form3": "djuren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_054",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fästing",
    "back": "tick",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fästingen",
      "form2": "fästingar",
      "form3": "fästingarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_055",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "längst fram",
    "back": "at the front"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_056",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "brun låda",
    "back": "brown box",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "bruna lådan",
      "form2": "bruna lådor",
      "form3": "bruna lådorna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_057",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "lyfta av locket",
    "back": "lifts off the lid",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "lyfter av locket",
      "form2": "lyfte av locket",
      "form3": "lyft av locket"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_058",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ta upp",
    "back": "takes up",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "tar upp",
      "form2": "tog upp",
      "form3": "tagit upp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_059",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "försiktigt",
    "back": "gently",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_060",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lika stor",
    "back": "equal size"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_061",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "går ett sus genom",
    "back": "a whisper passes through"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_062",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "fågelspindel",
    "back": "tarantula",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "fågelspindeln",
      "form2": "fågelspindlar",
      "form3": "fågelspindlarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_063",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "krypa",
    "back": "crawling",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "kryper",
      "form2": "kröp",
      "form3": "krupit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_064",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sakta",
    "back": "slowly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_065",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "giftig",
    "back": "toxic",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "giftigt",
        "giftiga"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_066",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "orolig",
    "back": "anxious",
    "forms": {
      "raw": [
        "oroligt",
        "oroliga"
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_067",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tar hon upp",
    "back": "does she pick up"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_068",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tittat färdigt",
    "back": "finished watching"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_069",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lägg tillbaka",
    "back": "put back"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_070",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "rymmer iväg",
    "back": "runs away"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_071",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skolavslutning",
    "back": "lower level of graduation",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skolavslutningen",
      "form2": "skolavslutningar",
      "form3": "skolavslutningarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_072",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "ha",
    "back": "has",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "har",
      "form2": "hade",
      "form3": "haft"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_073",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bott hos",
    "back": "lived with"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_074",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ett tag",
    "back": "for a while"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_075",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "för att",
    "back": "to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_076",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "läsa upp",
    "back": "read out",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "läser upp",
      "form2": "läste upp",
      "form3": "läst upp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_077",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dikt",
    "back": "poem",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "dikten",
      "form2": "dikter",
      "form3": "dikterna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_078",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "skriva",
    "back": "written",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "skriver",
      "form2": "skrev",
      "form3": "skrivit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_079",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "fast hon kan",
    "back": "although she can"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_080",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "utantill",
    "back": "by heart"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_081",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "scen",
    "back": "the stage",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "scenen",
      "form2": "scener",
      "form3": "scenerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_082",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "idrottshall",
    "back": "sports hall",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "idrottshallen",
      "form2": "idrottshallar",
      "form3": "idrottshallarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_083",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "jäst",
    "back": "yeast",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "jästen",
      "form2": null,
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_084",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ur minnet",
    "back": "out of memory"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_085",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "berg",
    "back": "mountain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "berget",
      "form2": "berg",
      "form3": "bergen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_086",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "högar med",
    "back": "piles of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_087",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "rektor",
    "back": "principal",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "rektorn",
      "form2": "rektorer",
      "form3": "rektorerna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_088",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hålla ett tal",
    "back": "gives a speech",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "håller ett tal",
      "form2": "höll ett tal",
      "form3": "hållit ett tal"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_089",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "varandra",
    "back": "each other"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_090",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "tänk att",
    "back": "imagine that"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_091",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nästan",
    "back": "almost",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_092",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "i höst",
    "back": "in the autumn"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_093",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "olika",
    "back": "different",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_094",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "program",
    "back": "program (school program)",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "programmet",
      "form2": "program",
      "form3": "programmen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_095",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "naturvetenskapsprogrammet",
    "back": "the natural science program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "naturvetenskapsprogrammet",
      "form2": "naturvetenskapsprogram",
      "form3": "naturvetenskapsprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_096",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "samhällsvetenskapsprogrammet",
    "back": "the social science program",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "samhällsvetenskapsprogrammet",
      "form2": "samhällsvetenskapsprogram",
      "form3": "samhällsvetenskapsprogrammen"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_097",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "få bra betyg",
    "back": "to get good grades"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_098",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "börja",
    "back": "begin",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "börjar",
      "form2": "började",
      "form3": "börjat"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_099",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "bli",
    "back": "become"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter23_100",
    "chapter": "Chapter23",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vuxen",
    "back": "adult",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vuxen",
      "form2": "vuxna",
      "form3": "vuxna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_001",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sommarlov",
    "back": "summer holiday",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "sommarlovet",
      "form2": "sommarlov",
      "form3": "sommarloven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_002",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "plötsligt",
    "back": "suddenly",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_003",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "inse",
    "back": "realize",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "inser",
      "form2": "insåg",
      "form3": "insett"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_004",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "samtidigt",
    "back": "at the same time"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_005",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "sista",
    "back": "last",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_006",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "sista dagen",
    "back": "last day"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_007",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "tillsammans",
    "back": "together",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_008",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "under",
    "back": "during",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_009",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hela",
    "back": "whole",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_010",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "år",
    "back": "year",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "året",
      "form2": "år",
      "form3": "åren"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_011",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minnas",
    "back": "remember",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minns",
      "form2": "mindes",
      "form3": "mint"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_012",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "första dagen",
    "back": "the first day"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_013",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "nervös",
    "back": "nervous",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "nervöst",
      "form2": "nervösa",
      "form3": null
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_014",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "se fram emot",
    "back": "look forward to"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_015",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "framtid",
    "back": "future",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "framtiden",
      "form2": "framtider",
      "form3": "framtiderna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_016",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "dröm",
    "back": "dream",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "drömmen",
      "form2": "drömmar",
      "form3": "drömmarna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_017",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "gå i uppfyllelse",
    "back": "come true"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_018",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "kanske",
    "back": "maybe",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_019",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "åtminstone",
    "back": "at least"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_020",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "hålla kontakten",
    "back": "stay in touch",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "håller kontakten",
      "form2": "höll kontakten",
      "form3": "hållit kontakten"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_021",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "ta hand om",
    "back": "take care"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_022",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "varandra",
    "back": "each other",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_023",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "alltid",
    "back": "always",
    "forms": null
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_024",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "oavsett vad",
    "back": "no matter what"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_025",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "vänskap",
    "back": "friendship",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "vänskapen",
      "form2": "vänskaper",
      "form3": "vänskaperna"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_026",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "minne",
    "back": "memories",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "minnet",
      "form2": "minnen",
      "form3": "minnena"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_027",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "förbli",
    "back": "remain",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "förblir",
      "form2": "förblev",
      "form3": "förblivit"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_028",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "för resten av",
    "back": "for the rest of"
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_029",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "word",
    "partOfSpeech": "unknown",
    "front": "liv",
    "back": "life",
    "forms": {
      "form1": "livet",
      "form2": "liv",
      "form3": "liven"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "chapter24_030",
    "chapter": "Chapter24",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "tags": [],
    "type": "phrase",
    "front": "lycka till",
    "back": "good luck"
  }
]